<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.8/publication" xmlns:n2016="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.8/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="425421-2019" EDITION="2019175"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>19-433729-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190926</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>175</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20190911</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2019/S 175-425421</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425421-2019:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>FR</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV><REF_NOTICE><NO_DOC_OJS>2019/S 154-378787</NO_DOC_OJS></REF_NOTICE></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20190906</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20190923 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="2">Additional information</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="2">Submission for one lot only</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP3EA</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EUF - Teknisk bistand til gennemførelse af støtteprogrammet for maritim sikkerheds- og sikringsstrategi i Centralafrika (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale, PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EEF - Technische Hilfe für die Umsetzung des Programms zur Unterstützung der Strategie für Sicherheit und Meeressicherheit in Zentralafrika (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes - PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EDF - Technical assistance to implement the Support Programme to the Maritime Security Strategy in Central Africa (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale (PASSMAR))</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>FED - Asistencia técnica para la implementación del programa de apoyo a la estrategia de seguridad y protección marítima en África Central (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EKR - Tekninen tuki meriturva- ja meriturvallisuusstrategian tukiohjelman täytäntöön panemiseksi Keski-Afrikassa (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>FED - Assistance technique pour la mise en œuvre du programme d’appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritime en Afrique Centrale (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>ΕΤΑ - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την υλοποίηση του προγράμματος στήριξης στη στρατηγική για την προστασία και την ασφάλεια στη θάλασσα στην Κεντρική Αφρική (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>FES - Assistenza tecnica per l'attuazione del programma di sostegno alla strategia di sicurezza marittima in Africa centrale (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EOF - Technische bijstand voor de tenuitvoerlegging van het programma ter ondersteuning van de strategie voor maritieme veiligheid en beveiliging in Centraal-Afrika (Passmar)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>FED - Assistência técnica para a implementação do programa de apoio à estratégia de segurança e proteção marítimas na África Central (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EUF - Tekniskt bistånd för genomförandet av stödprogrammet för strategi för sjösäkerhet och sjöfartsskydd i Centralafrika (Passmar)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>ERF - Technická pomoc při realizaci Programu podpory strategie námořní bezpečnosti ve střední Africe (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EAF - Tehniline abi Kesk-Aafrika meresõiduohutuse ja turvalisuse strateegia toetusprogrammi (Passmar) rakendamisel</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EFA - Szakmai segítségnyújtás a közép-afrikai tengeri biztonsági és védelmi stratégiát támogató program (PASSMAR) végrehajtásához</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EPF - Techninė pagalba Centrinės Afrikos jūrų saugumo ir saugos strategijos rėmimo programai įgyvendinti (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EAF - Tehniskā palīdzība Atbalsta programmas jūras drošuma un drošības stratēģijai Centrālajā Āfrikā (PASSMAR) īstenošanai</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>FEŻ - Għajnuna teknika għall-implimentazzjoni tal-programm ta' appoġġ għall-istrateġija ta' sikurezza u ta' sigurtà marittima fl-Afrika Ċentrali (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>EFR - Pomoc techniczna na rzecz wdrożenia programu wsparcia strategii bezpieczeństwa i ochrony na morzu w Afryce Środkowej (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>ERF - Odborná pomoc pri realizácii programu na podporu stratégie námornej ochrany a bezpečnosti v strednej Afrike (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale – PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>ERS - Tehnična pomoč pri izvajanju Podpornega programa za strategijo pomorske varnosti in zaščite v Srednji Afriki (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>CEF - Cúnamh teicniúil chun an Clár Tacaíochta a chur chun feidhme i leith na Straitéise Slándála Muirí san Afraic Láir (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale (PASSMAR))</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>ЕФР - Техническа помощ за изпълнение на програмата за помощ за стратегията за морска сигурност и безопасност в Централна Африка (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>FED - Asistență tehnică pentru punerea în aplicare a programului de sprijin pentru strategia de siguranță și securitate maritimă în Africa Centrală (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>ERF - Tehnička pomoć za provedbu Programa podrške strategiji morske zaštite i sigurnosti u središnjoj Africi (PASSMAR)</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Die Europäische Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">The European Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Unión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan unioni</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">L'Union européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">De Europese Unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">A União Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska unionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Liit</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Az Európai Unió</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Sąjunga</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Savienība</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Unjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Unia Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska únia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska unija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An tAontas Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски съюз</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Uniunea Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska unija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: EUF - Teknisk bistand til gennemførelse af støtteprogrammet for maritim sikkerheds- og sikringsstrategi i Centralafrika (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale, PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Udbudsreference: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Berigtigelse til udbudsbekendtgørelse</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement til Den Europæiske Unions Tidende, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>I stedet for:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Ordregivende myndighed</P><P>Den Europæiske Union, Bruxelles, Belgien, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen, for og på vegne af den centralafrikanske region repræsenteret ved Det Centralafrikanske Økonomiske Fællesskab (CEEAC).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Valgbarhed</P><P>[...]</P><P>Deltagelse i udbuddet er åben på lige vilkår for juridiske personer (der deltager enten individuelt eller i en sammenslutning — konsortium — af ansøgere), der er etableret i en af Den Europæiske Unions medlemsstater, AVS-lande eller et land eller territorium bemyndiget af AVS-EØF-partnerskabsaftalen, hvorunder programmet finansieres (se også punkt 29 nedenfor). Deltagelse er ligeledes åben for internationale organisationer og offentlige samarbejdsorganer i EU-medlemsstater.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Sidste frist for indgivelse af ansøgninger</P><P>Sidste frist for modtagelse af ansøgninger er 23.9.2019 (12.00), lokal tid.</P><P>Ansøgninger, der sendes til den ordregivende myndigheder efter sidste frist, vil ikke blive taget i betragtning.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Indgivelse af ansøgninger</P><P>Ansøgninger skal indgives på fransk og udelukkende sendes til den ordregivende myndighed:</P><P>— ved personlig indlevering,</P><P>— ved kurertjeneste med levering af buddet direkte til den ordregivende myndighed mod en underskrevet og dateret kvittering til følgende adresse: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Læses:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Ordregivende myndighed</P><P>Den Europæiske Union, Bruxelles, Belgien, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen, for og på vegne af den centralafrikanske region repræsenteret ved Det Centralafrikanske Økonomiske Fællesskab (CEEAC).</P><P>Den ordregivende myndighed kan anmodes om præciseringer på følgende e-mailadresse: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu senest 21 dage før sidste frist for indgivelse af bud anført i punkt 23 herunder.</P><P>Præciseringer vil blive offentliggjort på webstedet for Generaldirektoratet for Internationalt Samarbejde og Udvikling senest 5 dage før sidste frist.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Valgbarhed</P><P>[...]</P><P>Deltagelse i udbuddet er åben på lige vilkår for juridiske personer, der deltager enten individuelt eller i en sammenslutning (et konsortium) af ansøgere, der er etableret i en af Den Europæiske Unions medlemsstater, AVS-lande eller et land eller territorium bemyndiget af AVS-EF-partnerskabsaftalen, hvorunder programmet finansieres (se også punkt 29 nedenfor).</P><P>Deltagelse er ligeledes åben for internationale organisationer.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Sidste frist for indgivelse af ansøgninger</P><P>Tilbudsgivernes opmærksomhed henledes på det faktum, at ansøgningerne kan indsendes på 2 forskellige måder: enten pr. offentlig post eller privat kurertjeneste eller ved personlig indlevering.</P><P>I det første tilfælde skal ansøgningen/buddet sendes inden dato- og tidsfristen for indgivelse, med poststemplets eller indleveringsbevisets dato som bevis(1), mens det i det andet tilfælde er modtagelseskvitteringen, der udleveres på tidspunktet for leveringen af ansøgningen, der tjener som bevis.</P><P>23.9.2019 kl. 12:00 lokal tid.</P><P>Ansøgninger, der sendes til den ordregivende myndigheder efter sidste frist, vil ikke blive taget i betragtning.</P><P>Den ordregivende myndighed kan af administrative effektivitetshensyn afvise alle ansøgninger eller bud, der indgives rettidigt til posttjenesten, men som grundet årsager uden for den ordregivende myndigheds</P><P>kontrol er modtaget efter den faktiske godkendelsesdato for rapporten om prækvalifikationslisten eller evalueringsrapporten, hvis det at godtage ansøgningerne, der er sendt rettidigt men modtaget for sent, risikerer at forsinke evalueringsproceduren betragteligt eller rejser tvivl om allerede vedtagne og meddelte beslutninger.</P><P>(1) Det anbefales at bruge rekommanderet post, da poststemplet kan være ulæseligt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Indgivelse af ansøgninger</P><P>Ansøgninger skal indgives på fransk og udelukkende sendes til den ordregivende myndighed:</P><P>— enten via postvæsnet eller pr. kurér, hvor gældende dato for afsendelse vil fremgå af poststemplet eller datoen på kvitteringen for levering til:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— eller ved aflevering direkte i den ordregivende myndigheds lokaler enten af ansøgeren personligt eller af pågældendes repræsentant mod en underskrevet og dateret modtagelseskvittering, hvor gældende dato vil fremgå af kvitteringen, på følgende adresse:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle andre bestemmelser og betingelser i udbudsbekendtgørelsen forbliver uændrede. Disse ændringer eller rettelser vil være at betragte som en integreret del heraf.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: EEF - Technische Hilfe für die Umsetzung des Programms zur Unterstützung der Strategie für Sicherheit und Meeressicherheit in Zentralafrika (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes - PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Berichtigung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement zum Amtsblatt der Europäischen Union, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Die Europäische Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Anstatt:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</P><P>Europäische Union, Brüssel, Belgien, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission, im Auftrag und für Rechnung der Region Zentralafrika, vertreten durch die Wirtschaftsgemeinschaft zentralafrikanischer Staaten (Communauté économique des États de l'Afrique centrale — CEEAC),</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Teilnahmeberechtigung</P><P>[...]</P><P>Gleichrangig teilnahmeberechtigt an dem Auftrag sind alle juristischen Personen, die entweder als Einzelbieter oder in einem Zusammenschluss — Konsortium — aus Bietern teilnehmen und die in einem Mitgliedstaat der Europäischen Union, in einem AKP-Staat oder einem der Länder oder Gebiete ansässig sind, die im Rahmen des AKP-EG-Partnerschaftsabkommens, aus dem das Programm finanziert wird, zur Teilnahme zugelassen sind (siehe auch Ziffer 29 unten). Die Teilnahme steht auch internationalen Organisationen und öffentlichen Kooperationsagenturen der Mitgliedsstaaten der Europäischen Union offen.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Schlusstermin für die Einreichung von Bewerbungen:</P><P>Die Bewerbungsfrist wurde auf den 23.9.2019 (12:00), Ortszeit, festgelegt.</P><P>Bewerbungen, die nach dieser Frist beim öffentlichen Auftraggeber eingehen, werden nicht berücksichtigt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Verfahren zur Einreichung der Bewerbungen</P><P>Die Bewerbungen sind in französischer Sprache und ausschließlich an den öffentlichen Auftraggeber zu übermitteln:</P><P>— per Boten,</P><P>— per Eilkurierdienst, der die Bewerbung direkt beim öffentlichen Auftraggeber abgibt, und zwar gegen eine unterzeichnete und datierte Empfangsbescheinigung, unter der Anschrift: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, E-Mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>muss es heißen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</P><P>Europäische Union, Brüssel, Belgien, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission, im Auftrag und für Rechnung der Region Zentralafrika, vertreten durch die Wirtschaftsgemeinschaft zentralafrikanischer Staaten (Communauté économique des États de l'Afrique centrale — CEEAC),</P><P>Einzelheiten können beim öffentlichen Auftraggeber spätestens 21 Tage vor der in Abschnitt 23 unten angegebenen Frist für die Einreichung der Angebote eingeholt werden und dies bei folgender E-Mail-Adresse: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>Sie werden auf der Webseite der DG Internationale Zusammenarbeit und Entwicklung spätestens 5 Tage vor der Frist veröffentlicht.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Teilnahmeberechtigung</P><P>[...]</P><P>Gleichrangig teilnahmeberechtigt an dem Auftrag sind alle juristischen Personen, die entweder als Einzelbieter oder in einem Zusammenschluss — Konsortium — aus Bietern teilnehmen und die in einem Mitgliedstaat der Europäischen Union, in einem AKP-Staat oder einem der Länder oder Gebiete ansässig sind, die im Rahmen des AKP-EG-Partnerschaftsabkommens, aus dem das Programm finanziert wird, zur Teilnahme zugelassen sind (siehe auch Ziffer 29 unten).</P><P>Teilnahmeberechtigt sind ebenfalls internationale Organisationen.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Schlusstermin für die Einreichung von Bewerbungen:</P><P>Der Bewerber wird darauf hingewiesen, dass es zwei verschiedene Systeme für die Einreichung von Angeboten gibt: 1. der normale Postweg oder der private Kurierdienst, 2. die persönliche Aushändigung.</P><P>Im ersten Fall muss die Bewerbung oder das Angebot vor der Frist für die Einreichung (Datum des Poststempels oder der Quittung) versendet werden (1). Im zweiten Fall zählt die Empfangsbestätigung zum Zeitpunkt der Lieferung der Bewerbung/ des Angebots als Beweis.</P><P>23.9.2019 (12:00) Ortszeit.</P><P>Bewerbungen, die nach dieser Frist beim öffentlichen Auftraggeber eingehen, werden nicht berücksichtigt.</P><P>Der öffentliche Auftraggeber kann aus Gründen der administrativen Effizienz Bewerbungen ablehnen, die rechtzeitig bei der Post eingegangen, jedoch aus nicht von ihm zu vertretenden</P><P>Gründen nach dem Datum der Billigung der Auswahlliste eingegangen sind, wenn die Annahme der rechtzeitig eingereichten, aber verspätet zugestellten Bewerbungen das Bewertungsverfahren unverhältnismäßig lange hinauszögern oder bereits getroffene und weitergegebene Entscheidungen in Frage stellen könnte.</P><P>(1) Es wird empfohlen, die Anschreiben per Einschreiben zu versenden, falls der Poststempel nicht deutlich lesbar sein sollte.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Verfahren zur Einreichung der Bewerbungen</P><P>Die Bewerbungen sind in französischer Sprache und ausschließlich an den öffentlichen Auftraggeber zu übermitteln:</P><P>— auf dem Postweg oder per Kurierdienst, wobei das Aufgabedatum – der Poststempel oder das Datum der Empfangsbestätigung – gilt, an:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABUN, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— oder durch direkte persönliche Abgabe in den Räumlichkeiten des öffentlichen Auftraggebers durch den Bewerber oder einen bevollmächtigten Vertreter des Bewerbers gegen eine unterzeichnete und datierte Empfangsbestätigung, wobei die Empfangsbestätigung maßgeblich ist, an folgende Adresse:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABUN, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle anderen Daten und Bedingungen der Auftragsbekanntmachung bleiben unverändert. Die vorliegenden Änderungen oder Berichtigungen sind wesentlicher Bestandteil der Auftragsbekanntmachung.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: EDF - Technical assistance to implement the Support Programme to the Maritime Security Strategy in Central Africa (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale (PASSMAR))</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Publication reference: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Corrigendum to contract notice</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement to the Official Journal of the European Union, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Instead of:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Contracting authority</P><P>European Union, Brussels, Belgium, represented by the European Commission on behalf of and for the account of the Economic Community of Central African States (ECCAS),</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Eligibility</P><P>[...]</P><P>Participation in the contract is open on equal terms to all legal entities participating either individually or as part of a grouping — consortium — of tenderers established in one of the Member States of the European Union, ACP States or in a country or territory authorised by the ACP-EC Partnership Agreement under which the programme is financed (also see point 29 below). Participation is also open to international organisations and public cooperation agencies of Member States of the European Union.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Final date for submission of applications</P><P>The deadline for receiving applications is 12.00 (local time) on 23.9.2019.</P><P>Applications submitted to the contracting authority after the deadline will not be considered.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Application submission procedures</P><P>Applications must be submitted in French only and sent to the contracting authority:</P><P>— by bearer,</P><P>— by express courier service directly submitting the application to the contracting authority, against a signed and dated acknowledgment of receipt, to the following address: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, email: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Read:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Contracting authority</P><P>European Union, Brussels, Belgium, represented by the European Commission on behalf of and for the account of the Economic Community of Central African States (ECCAS),</P><P>Details may be requested from the Contracting Authority at the following email address: ‘DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu’ no later than 21 days before the deadline for submission of tenders listed in section 23 below.</P><P>Clarifications will be published on the website of DG International Cooperation and Development at the latest 5 days before the deadline for submission.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Eligibility</P><P>[...]</P><P>Participation in the contract is open on equal terms to all legal entities participating either individually or as part of a grouping — consortium — of tenderers established in one of the Member States of the European Union, ACP States or in a country or territory authorised by the ACP-EC Partnership Agreement under which the programme is financed (also see point 29 below).</P><P>Participation is also open to international organisations.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Final date for submission of applications</P><P>The candidate’s attention is drawn to the fact that there are 2 different systems for sending the application: by post or by courier service, or delivered by hand.</P><P>In the first case, the application must be sent before the deadline for submission, the postmark or deposit receipt being proof (1), and in the second case, the acknowledgement of receipt given at the time of delivery of the application will serve as proof.</P><P>23.9.2019 (12.00), local time.</P><P>Applications submitted to the contracting authority after the deadline will not be considered.</P><P>The contracting authority may, for reasons of administrative efficiency, reject any application submitted in time to the postal service but received, for reasons beyond its</P><P>control, after the effective date of approval of the pre-selection report, if the fact of accepting applications submitted in time but arriving late may excessively delay the evaluation process, or call into question decisions already taken and communicated.</P><P>(1) The use of registered mail is recommended in case the postmark is not readable.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Application submission procedures</P><P>Applications must be submitted in French only and sent to the contracting authority:</P><P>— either by post or by courier service, in which case the evidence will be constituted by the postmark or the date of the deposit slip, to the following address:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— or hand delivered by the candidate in person or by their agent directly to the premises of the Contracting Authority in return for a signed and dated receipt, in which case the evidence shall be constituted by this acknowledgement of receipt, to:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>All other terms and conditions of the contract notice remain unchanged. These alterations or corrections form an integral part of the contract notice.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: FED - Asistencia técnica para la implementación del programa de apoyo a la estrategia de seguridad y protección marítima en África Central (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referencia de publicación: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificativo del anuncio de contrato</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento al Diario Oficial de la Unión Europea, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Unión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>En lugar de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Órgano de contratación</P><P>Unión Europea, Bruselas, Bélgica, representada por la Comisión Europea, en nombre y por cuenta de la región de África Central, representada por la Comunidad Económica de los Estados del África Central (CEEAC).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Criterios de elegibilidad</P><P>[...]</P><P>La participación en el concurso está abierta, en igualdad de condiciones, a todas las personas jurídicas que participen a título individual o en una agrupación (consorcio) de licitadores, establecidas en uno de los Estados miembros de la Unión Europea, en los Estados ACP o en un país o territorio autorizado por el Acuerdo de Asociación ACP-CE en el marco del cual se financia el programa (véase también el punto 29 a continuación). La participación estará abierta también a las organizaciones internacionales y a las agencias públicas de cooperación de los Estados miembros.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Fecha límite para la presentación de las candidaturas</P><P>La fecha límite de recepción de ofertas será el 23.9.2019 a las 12:00 (hora local).</P><P>No se tendrán en cuenta las solicitudes enviadas al órgano de contratación después de dicha fecha límite.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modo de envío de las solicitudes</P><P>Las solicitudes deberán enviarse exclusivamente en francés al órgano de contratación:</P><P>— en mano,</P><P>— o por correo privado dirigido al órgano de contratación contra acuse de recibo firmado y fechado, a la siguiente dirección: Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABÓN, correo electrónico: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Léase:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Órgano de contratación</P><P>Unión Europea, Bruselas, Bélgica, representada por la Comisión Europea, en nombre y por cuenta de la región de África Central, representada por la Comunidad Económica de los Estados del África Central (CEEAC).</P><P>Los detalles pueden solicitarse a la Autoridad Contratante a la siguiente dirección de correo electrónico: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu, a más tardar 21 días antes de la fecha límite para la presentación de las ofertas indicada en la sección 23.</P><P>Las aclaraciones se publicarán en el sitio web de la DG Cooperación Internacional y Desarrollo a más tardar 5 días antes de la fecha límite de presentación</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Criterios de elegibilidad</P><P>[...]</P><P>La participación en el concurso está abierta, en igualdad de condiciones, a todas las personas jurídicas que participen a título individual o en una agrupación (consorcio) de licitadores, establecidas en uno de los Estados miembros de la Unión Europea, en los Estados ACP o en un país o territorio autorizado por el Acuerdo de Asociación ACP-CE en el marco del cual se financia el programa (véase también el punto 29 a continuación).</P><P>La participación también estará abierta a organizaciones internacionales.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Fecha límite para la presentación de las candidaturas</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que existen 2 sistemas de envío de las solicitudes: uno por correo oficial o privado y otro por entrega en mano.</P><P>En el primer caso, la solicitud deberá enviarse antes de la fecha límite de presentación, de lo que dará fe el matasellos de correos o el recibo de depósito(1), pero en el segundo, el acuse de recibo expedido en el momento de la recepción de la solicitud servirá de prueba.</P><P>23.9.2019, a las 12:00 (hora local).</P><P>No se tendrán en cuenta las solicitudes enviadas al órgano de contratación después de dicha fecha límite.</P><P>Por razones de eficacia administrativa, el órgano de contratación podrá rechazar toda solicitud presentada a tiempo al servicio postal pero recibida, por razones ajenas a su</P><P>voluntad, después de la fecha efectiva de aprobación del informe de preselección, si la aceptación de las solicitudes presentadas a tiempo pero recibidas tarde puede retrasar indebidamente el procedimiento de evaluación o poner en tela de juicio decisiones ya adoptadas y comunicadas.</P><P>(1) Se recomienda utilizar el correo certificado para evitar la eventual ilegibilidad del matasellos.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modo de envío de las solicitudes</P><P>Las solicitudes deberán enviarse exclusivamente en francés al órgano de contratación:</P><P>— Ya sea por correo oficial o privado, de la que darán fe el matasellos o la fecha de recepción del depósito, a la siguiente dirección:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABÓN, correo electrónico: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— O entrega a mano directamente en las instalaciones del órgano de contratación por parte del candidato en persona o por un representante del candidato, con acuse de recibo firmado y fechado, en cuyo caso dará fe dicho acuse de recibo, a la siguiente dirección:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABÓN, correo electrónico: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>El resto de los términos y condiciones del presente anuncio de contrato permanecen sin cambios. Estas modificaciones o correcciones formarán parte integrante del anuncio de licitación.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: EKR - Tekninen tuki meriturva- ja meriturvallisuusstrategian tukiohjelman täytäntöön panemiseksi Keski-Afrikassa (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ilmoituksen viite: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hankintailmoitusta koskeva oikaisuilmoitus</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopan unionin virallisen lehden täydennysosa, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan unioni</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Oikaistava tieto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Hankintaviranomainen</P><P>Euroopan unioni, Bryssel, Belgia, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio Keski-Afrikan valtioiden talousyhteisön (ECCAS) kautta edustettujen Keski-Afrikan valtioiden nimissä ja tiliin,</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Valintakelpoisuus</P><P>[...]</P><P>Sopimusmenettelyyn voivat osallistua samoin ehdoin oikeushenkilöt (joko yksittäisenä tarjoajana tai tarjoajien ryhmittymän (konsortion) jäsenenä), jotka ovat sijoittautuneet johonkin Euroopan unionin jäsenvaltioon, AKT-valtioon tai AKT–EY-kumppanuussopimuksessa, jonka perusteella ohjelma rahoitetaan, hyväksyttyyn maahan tai hyväksytylle alueelle (katso myös jäljempänä kohta 29). Tarjousmenettelyyn voivat osallistua myös kansainväliset järjestöt ja Euroopan unionin jäsenvaltioiden julkisen yhteistyön virastot.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Hakemusten jättämisen määräaika</P><P>Hakemusten vastaanottamisen määräaika on 23.9.2019 klo 12:00 paikallista aikaa.</P><P>Huomioon ei oteta hakemuksia, jotka toimitetaan hankintaviranomaiselle kyseisen määräajan jälkeen.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Hakemusten jättäminen</P><P>Ranskan kielellä laaditut hakemukset tulee toimittaa yksinomaan hankintaviranomaiselle:</P><P>— lähetin välityksellä,</P><P>— pikalähettipalvelun välityksellä suoraan hankintaviranomaiselle allekirjoitettua ja päivättyä vastaanottokuittia vastaan seuraavaan osoitteeseen: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, sähköpostiosoite: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Oikaisu:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Hankintaviranomainen</P><P>Euroopan unioni, Bryssel, Belgia, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio Keski-Afrikan valtioiden talousyhteisön (ECCAS) kautta edustettujen Keski-Afrikan valtioiden nimissä ja tiliin,</P><P>Selvennyspyyntöjä voidaan lähettää hankintaviranomaiselle seuraavaan sähköpostiosoitteeseen DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu viimeistään 21 päivää ennen jäljempänä kohdassa 23 ilmoitettua hakemusten jättämisen määräaikaa.</P><P>Selvennykset julkaistaan kansainvälisen yhteistyön ja kehitysasioiden PO:n verkkosivuilla vähintään 5 päivää ennen hakemusten jättämisen määräaikaa.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Valintakelpoisuus</P><P>[...]</P><P>Sopimusmenettelyyn voivat osallistua samoin ehdoin oikeushenkilöt (joko yksittäisenä tarjoajana tai tarjoajien ryhmittymän (konsortion) jäsenenä), jotka ovat sijoittautuneet johonkin Euroopan unionin jäsenvaltioon, AKT-valtioon tai AKT–EY-kumppanuussopimuksessa, jonka perusteella ohjelma rahoitetaan, hyväksyttyyn maahan tai hyväksytylle alueelle (katso myös jäljempänä kohta 29).</P><P>Tarjousmenettelyyn voivat osallistua myös kansainväliset järjestöt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Hakemusten jättämisen määräaika</P><P>Hakijoita pyydetään ottamaan huomioon, että hakemukset voidaan toimittaa 2 seuraavalla tavalla: postitse tai yksityisellä lähettipalvelulla tai henkilökohtaisesti toimitettuna.</P><P>Ensimmäisessä tapauksessa hakemus on lähetettävä ennen hakemusten jättämisen määräpäivää ja -aikaa ja todisteena käy postileima tai todistus postinjakelusta, mutta paikalle tuotaessa todisteena on kuitti hakemusasiakirjalähetyksen perille viemisestä (1).</P><P>23.9.2019 (12:00), paikallista aikaa.</P><P>Huomioon ei oteta hakemuksia, jotka toimitetaan hankintaviranomaiselle kyseisen määräajan jälkeen.</P><P>Hankintaviranomainen voi hallinnolliseen tehokkuuteen liittyvistä syistä hylätä hakemuksen, joka on toimitettu hyvissä ajoin postipalveluun mutta joka on vastaanotettu mistä tahansa hankintaviranomaisesta riippumattomasta syystä esivalintaluettelon hyväksynnän voimaantulon jälkeen, mikäli määräajan puitteissa jätettyjen mutta myöhässä saapuneiden hakemusten hyväksyminen aiheuttaisi huomattavaa viivästystä arviointimenettelylle tai vaarantaisi jo tehdyt ja ilmoitetut päätökset.</P><P/><P>(1) On suositeltavaa käyttää kirjattua lähetystä, mikäli postileima ei olisi luettavissa.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Hakemusten jättäminen</P><P>Ranskan kielellä laaditut hakemukset tulee toimittaa yksinomaan hankintaviranomaiselle:</P><P>— joko postitse tai lähettipalvelun välityksellä, jolloin todisteena on postileima tai vastaanottokuitin päivämäärä osoitteeseen:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— tai siten, että hakija tai hakijan valtuuttama henkilö toimittaa hakemuksen henkilökohtaisesti hankintaviranomaisen tiloihin allekirjoitettua ja päivättyä vastaanottokuittia vastaan (jolloin vastaanottokuittia käytetään todisteena) seuraavaan osoitteeseen:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Kaikki muut hankintailmoituksen kohdat ja ehdot pysyvät muuttumattomina. Kyseiset muutokset tai korjaukset ovat olennainen osa hankintailmoitusta.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: FED - Assistance technique pour la mise en œuvre du programme d’appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritime en Afrique Centrale (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Référence de publication: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Corrigendum de l’Avis de marché</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplément au Journal officiel de l'Union européenne, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L'Union européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, BELGIQUE,</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Au lieu de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Pouvoir adjudicateur</P><P>L'Union européenne, Bruxelles, BELGIQUE, représentée par la Commission européenne au nom et pour le compte de la région d’Afrique Centrale représentée par la Communauté économique des États de l’Afrique Centrale (CEEAC).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Éligibilité</P><P>[...]</P><P>La participation au marché est ouverte à égalité de conditions à toutes les personnes morales (participant individuellement ou dans le cadre d'un groupement — consortium — de soumissionnaires), qui sont établies dans un État membre de l'Union européenne, dans un État ACP, ou dans un pays ou sur un territoire autorisé par l'accord de partenariat ACPCE en vertu duquel le programme est financé (voir également le point 29 ci-après). La participation est également ouverte aux organisations internationales et aux agences publiques de coopération des États membres de l’Union européenne.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Date limite de soumission des candidatures</P><P>La date limite de réception des candidatures est fixée au 23.9.2019 à 12:00 (heure locale).</P><P>Il ne sera pas tenu compte des candidatures envoyées au pouvoir adjudicateur après cette date limite.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalités d'envoi des candidatures</P><P>Les candidatures doivent être transmises en français exclusivement au pouvoir adjudicateur:</P><P>— par porteur,</P><P>— par services de messagerie express déposant directement la candidature auprès du pouvoir adjudicateur, contre accusé de réception signé et daté, à l'adresse suivante: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville Gabon, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Lire:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Pouvoir adjudicateur</P><P>L'Union européenne, Bruxelles, BELGIQUE, représentée par la Commission européenne au nom et pour le compte de la région d’Afrique Centrale représentée par la Communauté économique des États de l’Afrique Centrale (CEEAC).</P><P>Des précisions peuvent être demandées au pouvoir adjudicateur à l’adresse de courrier électronique suivante DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu au plus tard 21</P><P>jours avant la date limite de soumission des offres indiquée à la section 23 ci-dessous.</P><P>Les précisions seront publiées sur le site internet de la DG Coopération internationale et développement au plus tard 5 jours avant la date limite de soumission</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Éligibilité</P><P>[...]</P><P>La participation au marché est ouverte à égalité de conditions à toutes les personnes morales (participant individuellement ou dans le cadre d'un groupement - consortium - de</P><P>soumissionnaires), qui sont établies dans un état membre de l'Union européenne, dans un état ACP, ou dans un pays ou sur un territoire autorisé par l'accord de partenariat ACP-CE en vertu duquel le programme est financé (voir également le point 29 ci-après). La participation est également ouverte aux organisations internationales.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Date limite de soumission des candidatures</P><P>L’attention du candidat est attirée sur le fait qu'il existe 2 systèmes différents pour l’envoi des candidatures: un par courrier postal ou messagerie express privée, et l’autre par</P><P>remise en main propre.</P><P>Dans le premier cas, la candidature doit être envoyée avant la date limite de soumission, le cachet de la poste ou le récépissé de dépôt faisant foi(1), mais dans le deuxième cas, c’est l’accusé de réception délivré au moment de la réception de la candidature qui sert de preuve.</P><P>23.9.2019 à 12:00 (heure locale).</P><P>Il ne sera pas tenu compte des candidatures envoyées au pouvoir adjudicateur après cette date limite.</P><P>Le pouvoir adjudicateur peut, pour des raisons d’efficacité administrative, rejeter toute candidature soumise à temps au service postal mais reçue, pour des raisons échappant à son</P><P>contrôle, après la date effective d’approbation du rapport de présélection, si le fait d’accepter des candidatures soumises à temps, mais arrivées tardivement risque de retarder exagérément la procédure d’évaluation ou de remettre en cause des décisions déjà prises et communiquées.</P><P>(1) Il est recommandé de procéder à un envoi recommandé, dans le cas où le cachet de la poste ne serait pas lisible.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalités d'envoi des candidatures</P><P>Les candidatures doivent être transmises en français exclusivement au pouvoir adjudicateur:</P><P>— soit par la poste ou par messagerie, auxquels cas le cachet de la poste ou la date du récépissé de dépôt fait foi, à:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville Gabon, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— soit par dépôt directement dans les locaux du pouvoir adjudicateur par le candidat en personne ou par tout mandataire du candidat, contre accusé de réception signé et daté.</P><P>Auquel cas l’accusé de réception fait foi, à l’adresse suivante:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville Gabon, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Tous les autres termes et conditions de l'avis de marché demeurent inchangés. Les présentes modifications ou corrections font partie intégrante de l’avis de marché.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: ΕΤΑ - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την υλοποίηση του προγράμματος στήριξης στη στρατηγική για την προστασία και την ασφάλεια στη θάλασσα στην Κεντρική Αφρική (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Αριθμός αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Διορθωτικό στην προκήρυξη σύμβασης</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Συμπλήρωμα στην Επίσημη Εφημερίδα της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Αντί:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Αναθέτουσα αρχή</P><P>Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση, Βρυξέλλες, Βέλγιο, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, εξ ονόματος και για λογαριασμό της περιφέρειας της Κεντρικής Αφρικής εκπροσωπούμενης από την Οικονομική κοινότητα των κρατών της κεντρικής Αφρικής (ΟΚΚΚΑ).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Επιλεξιμότητα</P><P>[...]</P><P>Η συμμετοχή στον διαγωνισμό είναι ελεύθερη, επί ίσοις όροις, για όλα τα νομικά πρόσωπα που συμμετέχουν είτε ατομικά είτε σε όμιλο — κοινοπραξία — υποψηφίων, τα οποία είναι εγκατεστημένα σε κράτη μέλη της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης, σε κράτη ΑΚΕ ή σε χώρες ή εδάφη που νομιμοποιούνται από τη συμφωνία εταιρικής σχέσης ΑΚΕ-ΕΚ στο πλαίσιο της οποίας χρηματοδοτείται το πρόγραμμα (βλέπε επίσης σημείο 29 κατωτέρω). Η συμμετοχή είναι επίσης ανοικτή σε διεθνείς οργανισμούς και δημόσιους οργανισμούς συνεργασίας των κρατών μελών της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Λήξη της προθεσμίας υποβολής των υποψηφιοτήτων</P><P>Η προθεσμία παραλαβής των υποψηφιοτήτων λήγει στις 23.9.2019 στις 12:00 (τοπική ώρα).</P><P>Δεν θα ληφθούν υπόψη υποψηφιότητες που θα αποσταλούν εκπρόθεσμα στην αναθέτουσα αρχή.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Όροι αποστολής των υποψηφιοτήτων</P><P>Οι υποψηφιότητες πρέπει να υποβληθούν στα γαλλικά αποκλειστικά στην αναθέτουσα αρχή ως εξής:</P><P>—μέσω εκπροσώπου,</P><P>— με υπηρεσίες ιδιωτικού ταχυδρομείου καταθέτοντας απευθείας την υποψηφιότητα στην αναθέτουσα αρχή έναντι απόδειξης παραλαβής φέρουσας υπογραφή και ημερομηνία στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση : délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, ΓΚΑΜΠΟΝ, Ηλεκτρονικό Ταχυδρομείο: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Διάβαζε:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Αναθέτουσα αρχή</P><P>Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση, Βρυξέλλες, Βέλγιο, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, εξ ονόματος και για λογαριασμό της περιφέρειας της Κεντρικής Αφρικής εκπροσωπούμενης από την Οικονομική κοινότητα των κρατών της κεντρικής Αφρικής (ΟΚΚΚΑ).</P><P>Διευκρινίσεις μπορούν να ζητηθούν από την Αναθέτουσα Αρχή στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu, το αργότερο 21 ημέρες πριν από την προθεσμία υποβολής των προσφορών που αναφέρεται στο σημείο 23 κατωτέρω.</P><P>Οι διευκρινίσεις θα δημοσιευθούν στον ιστότοπο της ΓΔ Διεθνούς Συνεργασίας και Ανάπτυξης το αργότερο 5 ημέρες πριν από την προθεσμία υποβολής.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Επιλεξιμότητα</P><P>[...]</P><P>Η συμμετοχή στον διαγωνισμό είναι ελεύθερη, επί ίσοις όροις, για όλα τα νομικά πρόσωπα που συμμετέχουν είτε ατομικά είτε σε όμιλο — κοινοπραξία — υποψηφίων, τα οποία είναι εγκατεστημένα σε κράτη μέλη της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης, σε κράτη ΑΚΕ ή σε χώρες ή εδάφη που νομιμοποιούνται από τη συμφωνία εταιρικής σχέσης ΑΚΕ-ΕΚ στο πλαίσιο της οποίας χρηματοδοτείται το πρόγραμμα (βλέπε επίσης σημείο 29 κατωτέρω).</P><P>Η συμμετοχή είναι επίσης ανοικτή για τους διεθνείς οργανισμούς.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Λήξη της προθεσμίας υποβολής των υποψηφιοτήτων</P><P>Εφιστάται η προσοχή του υποψηφίου στο γεγονός ότι υπάρχουν 2 διαφορετικά συστήματα για την αποστολή υποψηφιοτήτων: το ένα είναι το ταχυδρομείο ή η ιδιωτική ταχυδρομική υπηρεσία, το άλλο είναι η ιδιόχειρη κατάθεση.</P><P>Στην πρώτη περίπτωση, η υποψηφιότητα πρέπει να έχει αποσταλεί πριν από την ημερομηνία υποβολής, οπότε η σφραγίδα του ταχυδρομείου ή η απόδειξη παραλαβής αποτελούν αποδεικτικά στοιχεία(1), ενώ στη δεύτερη περίπτωση, θα χρησιμεύσει ως αποδεικτικό στοιχείο η απόδειξη παραλαβής που δίδεται κατά την παράδοση της υποψηφιότητας.</P><P>23.9.2019 στις 12:00 τοπική ώρα.</P><P>Δεν θα ληφθούν υπόψη υποψηφιότητες που θα αποσταλούν εκπρόθεσμα στην αναθέτουσα αρχή.</P><P>Η αναθέτουσα αρχή μπορεί, για λόγους διοικητικής αποτελεσματικότητας, να απορρίψει κάθε υποψηφιότητα που υποβλήθηκε εγκαίρως στην ταχυδρομική υπηρεσία αλλά παρελήφθη, για οποιονδήποτε λόγο πέρα από</P><P>από τον έλεγχό της, μετά την ημερομηνία έναρξης ισχύος της έγκρισης της αναφοράς προεπιλογής, αν η αποδοχή των υποψηφιοτήτων που υποβλήθηκαν εγκαίρως αλλά παρελήφθησαν καθυστερημένα θα καθυστερούσε σημαντικά τη διαδικασία αξιολόγησης ή θα έθετε σε κίνδυνο τις ήδη ληφθείσες και κοινοποιηθείσες αποφάσεις.</P><P>(1) Συνιστάται να γίνει αποστολή με συστημένη επιστολή σε περίπτωση που η σφραγίδα ταχυδρομείου δεν είναι ευανάγνωστη.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Όροι αποστολής των υποψηφιοτήτων</P><P>Οι υποψηφιότητες πρέπει να υποβληθούν στα γαλλικά αποκλειστικά στην αναθέτουσα αρχή ως εξής:</P><P>— είτε ταχυδρομικώς ή με υπηρεσία ταχυμεταφορών, στην οποία περίπτωση αποτελούν αποδεικτικά στοιχεία η σφραγίδα του ταχυδρομείου ή η ημερομηνία στο δελτίο κατάθεσης, στη διεύθυνση:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, ΓΚΑΜΠΟΝ, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— είτε ιδιοχείρως από τον υποψήφιο ή από εκπρόσωπό του απευθείας στις εγκαταστάσεις της αναθέτουσας αρχής, λαμβάνοντας υπογεγραμμένη και χρονολογημένη απόδειξη παραλαβής, στην οποία περίπτωση αποτελεί αποδεικτικό στοιχείο η παρούσα απόδειξη παραλαβής, στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, ΓΚΑΜΠΟΝ, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Όλοι οι λοιποί όροι και προϋποθέσεις της προκήρυξης σύμβασης παραμένουν αμετάβλητοι. Οι παρούσες τροποποιήσεις ή διορθώσεις αποτελούν αναπόσπαστο τμήμα της προκήρυξης του διαγωνισμού.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: FES - Assistenza tecnica per l'attuazione del programma di sostegno alla strategia di sicurezza marittima in Africa centrale (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Riferimento della pubblicazione: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rettifica al bando di gara</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplemento alla Gazzetta ufficiale dell'Unione europea, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>anziché:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Ente appaltante</P><P>Unione europea, Bruxelles, Belgio, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea, in nome e per conto della regione dell’Africa Centrale rappresentata dalla Comunità economica degli Stati dell'Africa centrale (CEEAC).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Ammissibilità</P><P>[...]</P><P>La partecipazione all'appalto è aperta, a parità di condizioni, a tutte le persone giuridiche (che partecipano a titolo individuale o nell'ambito di un raggruppamento — consorzio — di offerenti), stabilite in uno Stato membro dell'Unione europea, in uno Stato ACP o in un paese o territorio autorizzato dall'accordo di partenariato ACP-CE in virtù del quale viene finanziato il programma (cfr. anche il successivo punto 29). La partecipazione è aperta anche a organizzazioni internazionali e agenzie pubbliche di cooperazione degli Stati membri dell'Unione Europea.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termine ultimo per la presentazione delle candidature</P><P>Il termine ultimo per il ricevimento delle candidature è fissato per il 23.9.2019 alle 12:00 (ora locale).</P><P>Non saranno prese in considerazione le candidature inviate all'ente appaltante dopo tale termine.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalità di invio delle candidature</P><P>Le candidature dovranno essere trasmesse in lingua francese esclusivamente all'ente appaltante:</P><P>— tramite latore,</P><P>— per corriere espresso, consegnando la candidatura direttamente presso l'amministrazione aggiudicatrice, dietro rilascio di una ricevuta firmata e datata, al seguente indirizzo: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>leggi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Ente appaltante</P><P>Unione europea, Bruxelles, Belgio, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea, in nome e per conto della regione dell’Africa Centrale rappresentata dalla Comunità economica degli Stati dell'Africa centrale (CEEAC).</P><P>È possibile richiedere chiarimenti all'ente appaltante al seguente indirizzo di posta elettronica: «DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu» entro e non oltre 21 giorni prima del termine ultimo per la presentazione delle offerte indicato alla sezione 23 sottostante.</P><P>Le informazioni saranno pubblicate sul sito web della DG Cooperazione internazionale e sviluppo entro e non oltre 5 giorni prima del termine ultimo per la presentazione delle offerte.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Ammissibilità</P><P>[...]</P><P>La partecipazione all'appalto è aperta, a parità di condizioni, a tutte le persone giuridiche che partecipano a titolo individuale o nell'ambito di un raggruppamento — consorzio — di offerenti, stabilite in uno Stato membro dell'Unione europea, in uno Stato ACP o in un paese o territorio autorizzato dall'accordo di partenariato ACP-CE in virtù del quale viene finanziato il programma (cfr. anche il successivo punto 29).</P><P>La partecipazione è altresì aperta alle organizzazioni internazionali.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termine ultimo per la presentazione delle candidature</P><P>Si segnala ai candidati che esistono 2 sistemi differenti per l'invio delle candidature: tramite posta o corriere privato espresso, oppure con consegna personale a mano.</P><P>Nel primo caso, la candidatura dovrà essere inviata entro il termine ultimo di presentazione, e il timbro postale o la ricevuta di deposito faranno fede (1), nel secondo caso, sarà invece l'avviso di ricevimento rilasciato al momento del ricevimento a costituire la prova.</P><P>23.9.2019, alle ore 12:00 (ora locale).</P><P>Non saranno prese in considerazione le candidature inviate all'ente appaltante dopo tale termine.</P><P>Per motivi di efficienza amministrativa, l'ente appaltante potrà rifiutare qualsiasi candidatura presentata in tempo al servizio postale ma ricevuta, per ragioni che sfuggono al suo</P><P>controllo, dopo la data effettiva di approvazione del rapporto di preselezione, se il fatto di accettare delle candidature presentate in tempo, ma pervenute in ritardo, rischia di ritardare eccessivamente la procedura di valutazione o di mettere in discussione delle decisioni già prese e comunicate.</P><P>(1) Si consiglia di ricorrere alla posta raccomandata nel caso in cui il timbro postale non sia leggibile.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalità di invio delle candidature</P><P>Le candidature dovranno essere trasmesse in lingua francese esclusivamente all'ente appaltante:</P><P>— per posta o servizio di corriere, nel qual caso farà fede il timbro postale o la data della ricevuta di consegna, presso:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— tramite consegna diretta presso i locali dell'ente appaltante da parte del candidato o di qualsiasi mandatario del candidato, con il rilascio dell'avviso di ricevimento firmato e datato, nel qual caso fa fede l'avviso di ricevimento, pervenuto all'indirizzo seguente:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Tutte le altre condizioni del bando di gara rimangono immutate. Le presenti modifiche o correzioni costituiscono parte integrante del bando di gara.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: EOF - Technische bijstand voor de tenuitvoerlegging van het programma ter ondersteuning van de strategie voor maritieme veiligheid en beveiliging in Centraal-Afrika (Passmar)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referentie van de bekendmaking: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificatie van de aankondiging van opdracht</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement op het Publicatieblad van de Europese Unie, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>De Europese Unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>In plaats van:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Aanbestedende dienst:</P><P>Europese Unie, Brussel, België, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie, in naam en voor rekening van de Economische Gemeenschap van Centraal-Afrikaanse Staten (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Deelname:</P><P>[...]</P><P>Deelname aan de opdracht staat onder gelijke voorwaarden open voor alle rechtspersonen (die hetzij individueel, hetzij in een combinatie (consortium) van inschrijvers deelnemen) die gevestigd zijn in een lidstaat van de Europese Unie, in een ACS-land of in een land of gebied dat geautoriseerd wordt door de ACS-EG-Partnerschapsovereenkomst in het kader waarvan het programma wordt gefinancierd (zie ook punt 29 hierna). Deelname staat ook open voor internationale organisaties en openbare samenwerkingsagentschappen van de lidstaten van de Europese Unie.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Uiterste datum voor het indienen van de aanvragen:</P><P>De uiterste datum voor de ontvangst van de aanvragen is vastgelegd op 23.9.2019 om 12:00 (plaatselijke tijd).</P><P>Er wordt geen rekening gehouden met aanvragen die na deze uiterste datum naar de aanbestedende dienst zijn verstuurd.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Wijze van indiening van de aanvragen:</P><P>Aanvragen mogen uitsluitend in het Frans bij de aanbestedende dienst worden ingediend:</P><P>— per koerier,</P><P>— door een koeriersdienst die de aanvraag rechtstreeks tegen de ondertekende en gedateerde ontvangstbevestiging indient bij de aanbestedende dienst op het volgende adres: Europese Unie, délégation au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Te lezen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Aanbestedende dienst:</P><P>Europese Unie, Brussel, België, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie, in naam en voor rekening van de Economische Gemeenschap van Centraal-Afrikaanse Staten (ECCAS).</P><P>Nadere inlichtingen kunnen worden aangevraagd bij de aanbestedende dienst op het volgende e-mailadres: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu, uiterlijk 21 dagen vóór de uiterste datum voor het indienen van de inschrijvingen zoals vermeld in punt 23 hieronder.</P><P>De verduidelijkingen zullen uiterlijk 5 dagen vóór de uiterste termijn voor de indiening op de website van DG Internationale Samenwerking en Ontwikkeling worden bekendgemaakt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Deelname:</P><P>[...]</P><P>Deelname aan de opdracht staat onder gelijke voorwaarden open voor alle rechtspersonen (die hetzij individueel, hetzij in een combinatie (consortium) van inschrijvers deelnemen) die gevestigd zijn in een lidstaat van de Europese Unie, in een ACS-land of in een land of gebied dat geautoriseerd wordt door de ACS-EG-Partnerschapsovereenkomst in het kader waarvan het programma wordt gefinancierd (zie ook punt 29 hierna).</P><P>Deelname staat eveneens open voor internationale organisaties.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Uiterste datum voor het indienen van de aanvragen:</P><P>De aandacht van de gegadigde wordt gevestigd op het feit dat er 2 verschillende systemen zijn voor het verzenden van aanvragen: per post of particuliere koeriersdienst en via persoonlijke overhandiging.</P><P>In het eerste geval moet de aanvraag worden verzonden vóór de uiterste datum van indiening, waarbij het poststempel of het ontvangstbewijs (1) geldt als bewijs, maar in het tweede geval geldt de ontvangstbevestiging die wordt overhandigd op het moment van de ontvangst van de aanvraag als bewijs.</P><P>23.9.2019 12:00, plaatselijke tijd.</P><P>Er wordt geen rekening gehouden met aanvragen die na deze uiterste datum naar de aanbestedende dienst zijn verstuurd.</P><P>De aanbestedende dienst kan, om redenen van administratieve doelmatigheid, bij de postdienst tijdig ingediende aanvragen afwijzen die, om redenen waarop de aanbestedende dienst geen</P><P>invloed heeft, na de datum van inwerkingtreding van het voorselectieverslag, indien het feit van het aanvaarden van aanvragen die tijdig zijn ingediend maar te laat aankomen het evaluatieproces kan vertragen of beslissingen die al zijn genomen en gecommuniceerd ter discussie stellen.</P><P>(1) Het wordt aangeraden aangetekend te verzenden voor het geval het poststempel niet leesbaar zou zijn.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Wijze van indiening van de aanvragen:</P><P>Aanvragen mogen uitsluitend in het Frans bij de aanbestedende dienst worden ingediend:</P><P>— ofwel per post of per koeriersdienst (waarbij het poststempel of de datum van het ontvangstbewijs als bewijs geldt) bij:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— ofwel door rechtstreekse afgifte van de aanvraag door de gegadigde of een gemachtigde van de gegadigde in de kantoren van de aanbestedende dienst in ruil voor een gedateerd en ondertekend ontvangstbewijs (waarbij het ontvangstbewijs als bewijs geldt) op het volgende adres:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle andere voorwaarden van de aankondiging van opdracht blijven ongewijzigd. Onderhavige wijzigingen of correcties maken integraal deel uit van de aankondiging van opdracht.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: FED - Assistência técnica para a implementação do programa de apoio à estratégia de segurança e proteção marítimas na África Central (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referência da publicação: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Retificativo ao anúncio de concurso</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento do Jornal Oficial da União Europeia, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>A União Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Em vez de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Entidade adjudicante</P><P>União Europeia, Bruxelas, Bélgica, representada pela Comissão Europeia, em nome e por conta da região da África Central representada pela Comunidade Económica dos Estados da África Central (CEEAC).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Elegibilidade</P><P>[...]</P><P>A participação no concurso está aberta, em condições de igualdade, a todas as pessoas coletivas que participam individualmente ou num agrupamento (consórcio) de proponentes, estabelecidas num dos Estados-Membros da União Europeia, num Estado ACP ou num país ou território autorizado pelo Acordo de Parceria ACP-CE no quadro do qual o programa é financiado (ver igualmente o ponto 29 infra). A participação está igualmente aberta às organizações internacionais e aos agentes públicos de cooperação dos Estados-Membros da União Europeia.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Data-limite para apresentação das candidaturas</P><P>A data-limite de receção das candidaturas está estabelecida em 23.9.2019 às 12:00 (hora local).</P><P>As candidaturas enviadas à entidade adjudicante após esta data-limite não serão tidas em conta.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalidades de envio das candidaturas</P><P>As candidaturas devem ser apresentadas em francês exclusivamente à entidade adjudicante:</P><P>— por mensageiro,</P><P>— por serviços de correio expresso que entreguem a candidatura diretamente junto da entidade adjudicante, contra aviso de receção assinado e datado, no endereço seguinte: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABÃO, endereço de correio eletrónico: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Ler:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Entidade adjudicante</P><P>União Europeia, Bruxelas, Bélgica, representada pela Comissão Europeia, em nome e por conta da região da África Central representada pela Comunidade Económica dos Estados da África Central (CEEAC).</P><P>Podem ser pedidas mais informações à entidade adjudicante para o seguinte endereço eletrónico: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu, o mais tardar até 21 dias antes da data-limite de apresentação das propostas indicada no ponto 23 abaixo.</P><P>As informações serão publicadas no sítio internet da DG Cooperação Internacional e Desenvolvimento, o mais tardar, 5 dias antes da data-limite.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Elegibilidade</P><P>[...]</P><P>A participação no concurso está aberta, em condições de igualdade, a todas as pessoas coletivas que participam individualmente ou num agrupamento (consórcio) de proponentes, estabelecidas num dos Estados-Membros da União Europeia, nos Estados ACP ou num país ou território autorizado pelo Acordo de Parceria ACP-CE no quadro do qual o programa é financiado (ver igualmente o ponto 29 infra).</P><P>A participação está também aberta a organizações internacionais.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Data-limite para apresentação das candidaturas</P><P>Chama-se à atenção do candidato para o facto de que existem 2 sistemas diferentes para o envio das candidaturas: um por correio postal ou por correio expresso privado; o outro por entrega em mão própria.</P><P>No primeiro caso, a candidatura deve ser enviada antes da data-limite de apresentação, servindo como comprovativo o carimbo postal ou o recibo de entrega (1), mas, no segundo caso, é o recibo de receção entregue aquando da receção da candidatura que serve de prova.</P><P>23.9.2019 às 12:00 (hora local).</P><P>As candidaturas enviadas à entidade adjudicante após esta data-limite não serão tidas em conta.</P><P>A entidade adjudicante pode, por razões de eficácia administrativa, rejeitar qualquer candidatura apresentada a tempo nos serviços postais, mas recebida, por razões externas ao seu</P><P>controlo, após a data efetiva de aprovação do relatório de pré-seleção, se o facto de aceitar as candidaturas apresentadas a tempo, mas rececionadas tardiamente, poder originar o atraso exagerado do processo de avaliação ou colocar em causa decisões já tomadas e comunicadas.</P><P>(1) Aconselha-se o envio por carta registada como segurança caso o carimbo postal não seja legível.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalidades de envio das candidaturas</P><P>As candidaturas devem ser apresentadas em francês exclusivamente à entidade adjudicante:</P><P>— seja por via postal ou serviço de correio por mensageiro, fazendo fé a data do envio, o carimbo dos correios ou a data do recibo de entrega:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABÃO, endereço eletrónico: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— seja por depósito direto nos locais da entidade adjudicante pessoalmente pelo candidato ou por qualquer representante do candidato, contra recibo de receção assinado e datado, servindo este, neste caso, como comprovativo, no seguinte endereço:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABÃO, endereço eletrónico: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Os restantes pontos e condições do anúncio de concurso permanecem inalterados. As presentes modificações ou correções são parte integrante do anúncio de concurso.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: EUF - Tekniskt bistånd för genomförandet av stödprogrammet för strategi för sjösäkerhet och sjöfartsskydd i Centralafrika (Passmar)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Publikationsreferens: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rättelse till upphandlingsmeddelande</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Tillägg till Europeiska unionens officiella tidning, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska unionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>I stället för:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Upphandlande myndighet</P><P>Europeiska unionen, Bryssel, Belgien, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen till förmån för och på uppdrag av den Centralafrikanska regionen representerad av Centralafrikanska staternas ekonomiska gemenskap (Eccas).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Behörighet</P><P>[...]</P><P>Deltagande i upphandlingen är öppet på lika villkor för juridiska personer som deltar antingen enskilt eller som del av en grupp – ett konsortium – av anbudsgivare, vilka är etablerade i någon av Europeiska unionens medlemsstater, i någon AVS-stat eller i ett land eller territorium, som ges behörighet genom AVS–EU-partnerskapsavtalet, inom vilket programmet finansieras (se även punkt 29 nedan). Deltagandet är också öppet för internationella organisationer och för offentliga samarbets- organ i EU:s medlemsstater.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Sista datum för inlämning av ansökningar</P><P>Sista datum för mottagande av ansökningar är den 23.9.2019 kl. 12:00, lokal tid.</P><P>Ansökningar som skickas till den upphandlande myndigheten efter att tidsfristen har löpt ut kommer inte att beaktas.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Inlämning av ansökningar</P><P>Ansökningar ska avfattas på franska och endast skickas till den upphandlande myndigheten:</P><P>— med bud,</P><P>— via express budtjänst som överlämnar ansökan direkt hos den upphandlande myndigheten mot ett signerat och daterat mottagningsbevis till följande adress: Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-post: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Skall det stå:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Upphandlande myndighet</P><P>Europeiska unionen, Bryssel, Belgien, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen till förmån för och på uppdrag av den Centralafrikanska regionen representerad av Centralafrikanska staternas ekonomiska gemenskap (Eccas).</P><P>Förtydliganden kan begäras från den upphandlande myndigheten på följande e-postadress: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu senast 21 dagar före det sista datum för inlämning av anbuden som anges i avsnitt 23 nedan.</P><P>Förtydligandena kommer att publiceras på webben för GD internationellt samarbete och utveckling senast 5 dagar före sista datum för inlämning av anbud.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Behörighet</P><P>[...]</P><P>Deltagande i upphandlingen är öppet på lika villkor för juridiska personer som deltar antingen enskilt eller som del av en grupp – ett konsortium – av anbudsgivare, vilka är etablerade i någon av Europeiska unionens medlemsstater, i någon AVS-stat eller i ett land eller territorium som ges behörighet genom AVS–EU-partnerskapsavtalet inom vilket programmet finansieras (se även punkt 29 nedan).</P><P>Deltagande är även öppet för internationella organisationer.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Sista datum för inlämning av ansökningar</P><P>Den sökande uppmärksammas på att det finns 2 olika system för att skicka in anbuden: via post eller budtjänst och genom direkt överlämning.</P><P>I det första fallet ska ansökan skickas före tidsfristen för inlämning, där poststämpel eller inlämningskvitto utgör bevis på giltighet (1), medan det i det andra fallet är mottagningsbeviset vid leverans av ansökan som utgör beviset.</P><P>23.9.2019 kl 12:00 (lokal tid).</P><P>Ansökningar som skickas till den upphandlande myndigheten efter att tidsfristen har löpt ut kommer inte att beaktas.</P><P>Den upphandlande myndigheten kan av administrativa effektivitetsskäl avvisa ansökningar, som inlämnats i tid till posten men som av skäl som ligger bortom myndighetens</P><P>kontroll, mottagits efter det egentliga datumet för godkännande av rapporten för förhandsval, om accepterande av ansökningar, som lämnats in i tid men som inkommit för sent, riskerar att starkt försena utvärderingsförfarandet eller ifrågasätta redan tagna och kommunicerade beslut.</P><P>(1) Rekommenderat brev förordas eftersom en poststämpel kan vara oläsbar.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Inlämning av ansökningar</P><P>Ansökningar ska avfattas på franska och endast skickas till den upphandlande myndigheten:</P><P>– antingen via post eller bud, då poststämpeln eller datumet på leveranskvittot utgör bevis för att tidsfristen har respekterats, till:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-post: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>– eller genom direkt överlämning i den upphandlande myndighetens lokaler av den sökande personligen eller genom ombud, i utbyte mot ett daterat och undertecknat mottagningsbevis, till följande adress:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-post: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alla andra villkor i meddelandet om upphandling förblir oförändrade. Dessa ändringar eller rättelser utgör en integrerad del av meddelandet om upphandling.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: ERF - Technická pomoc při realizaci Programu podpory strategie námořní bezpečnosti ve střední Africe (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenční číslo: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tisková oprava oznámení o zakázce</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Úřednímu věstníku Evropské unie, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namísto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Veřejný zadavatel</P><P>Evropská unie, Brusel, Belgie, zastoupená Evropskou komisí jménem a ve prospěch středoafrického regionu zastoupeného Hospodářským společenstvím středoafrických států (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Způsobilost</P><P>[...]</P><P>Účast v zakázce je otevřena za stejných podmínek pro fyzické osoby účastnící se buď samostatně nebo jako v seskupení (konsorciu) uchazečů, které mají sídlo v 1 z členských států Evropské unie, států AKT nebo v zemi či na území oprávněných Dohodou o partnerství mezi AKT–ES, v rámci které je program financován (viz také bod 29 níže). Účast na zakázce je také otevřena mezinárodním organizacím a veřejným agenturám spolupráce Členských států Evropské unie.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Lhůta na podání přihlášek</P><P>Konečná lhůta pro podání přihlášek je 23.9.2019 ve 12:00 místního času.</P><P>Přihlášky podané veřejnému zadavateli po tomto termínu nebudou vzaty v úvahu.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Způsoby podání přihlášek</P><P>Přihlášky musí být vypracovány výhradně ve francouzštině a předány veřejnému zadavateli:</P><P>— osobně,</P><P>— expresní kurýrní službou, která doručí přihlášku přímo veřejnému zadavateli, s podepsaným a datovaným potvrzením o převzetí, na následující adresu: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, email: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Čtěte:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Veřejný zadavatel</P><P>Evropská unie, Brusel, Belgie, zastoupená Evropskou komisí jménem a ve prospěch středoafrického regionu zastoupeného Hospodářským společenstvím středoafrických států (ECCAS).</P><P>Podrobnosti mohou být vyžádány od zadavatele na následující e-mailové adrese DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu nejpozději 21 dní před uplynutím lhůty pro podání nabídky uvedené v části 23 níže.</P><P>Podrobnosti budou zveřejněné na internetové stránce GŘ mezinárodní spolupráce a rozvoje nejpozději 5 dní před konečnou lhůtou.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Způsobilost</P><P>[...]</P><P>Účast v zakázce je otevřena za stejných podmínek pro fyzické osoby účastnící se buď samostatně nebo jako v seskupení (konsorciu) uchazečů, které mají sídlo v 1 z členských států Evropské unie, států AKT nebo v zemi či na území oprávněných Dohodou o partnerství mezi AKT–ES, v rámci které je program financován (viz také bod 29 níže).</P><P>Účast je otevřená také mezinárodním organizacím.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Lhůta na podání přihlášek</P><P>Uchazeč musí vzít na vědomí, že existují 2 různé systémy pro zasílání přihlášek: první poštou či soukromou kurýrní službou a druhý osobním doručením.</P><P>V prvním případě musí být přihláška poslána před konečnou lhůtou pro jejich podání, za důkaz o datu odeslání bude považováno (1) poštovní razítko nebo podací lístek. V druhém případě je důkazem o datu podání potvrzení o přijetí přihlášky, které bude vystaveno v okamžiku jejího předání.</P><P>23.9.2019 v 12:00 místního času.</P><P>Přihlášky podané veřejnému zadavateli po tomto termínu nebudou vzaty v úvahu.</P><P>Veřejný zadavatel může z důvodů administrativní účinnosti zamítnout každou přihlášku podanou včas poštovní službě, která však dojde z důvodů mimo jeho</P><P>kontrolu po datu účinnosti schválení zprávy o předběžném výběru, pokud by přijetí přihlášek podaných včas (avšak obdržených pozdě) mohl zpomalit proces hodnocení nebo zpochybnit rozhodnutí, která již byla přijata a oznámena.</P><P>(1) V případě, že by poštovní razítko nebylo čitelné, se doporučuje odeslat doporučenou zásilku.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Způsoby podání přihlášek</P><P>Přihlášky musí být vypracovány výhradně ve francouzštině a předány veřejnému zadavateli:</P><P>— buď poštou nebo doručovatelskou službou, přičemž bude rozhodující datum na razítku pošty nebo datum na potvrzení o doručení, na adresu:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— nebo uložením na níže uvedenou adresu přímo v prostorách veřejného zadavatele uchazečem osobně nebo jakýmkoli zástupcem uchazeče oproti podepsanému a datovanému potvrzení o přijetí, přičemž bude rozhodující potvrzení o přijetí:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Veškeré další smluvní podmínky oznámení o zakázce zůstávají beze změn. Tyto změny či opravy tvoří nedílnou součást oznámení o zakázce.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: EAF - Tehniline abi Kesk-Aafrika meresõiduohutuse ja turvalisuse strateegia toetusprogrammi (Passmar) rakendamisel</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avaldamise viide: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hanketeate parandus</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopa Liidu Teataja täiendus, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Liit</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Enne:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Hankija:</P><P>Euroopa Liit, Brüssel, Belgia, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon, Kesk-Aafrika piirkonna eest ja nimel, keda esindab Kesk-Aafrika Riikide Majandusühendus (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Sobivus</P><P>[...]</P><P>Hankes võivad osaleda võrdsetel tingimustel kas üksikult või pakkujate ühenduses (konsortsiumis) juriidilised isikud, kes on asutatud mis tahes Euroopa Liidu liikmesriigis, AKV riigis või riigis või territooriumil, mis on selleks volitatud AKV ja EÜ vahelise koostöölepinguga, mille alusel programmi rahastatakse (vt ka punkti 29 allpool). Hankes võivad osaleda ka rahvusvahelised organisatsioonid ja ELi liikmesriikide avalikud koostööorganisatsioonid.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Taotluste esitamise tähtpäev</P><P>Taotluste laekumise tähtpäev on 23.9.2019 kell 12:00 (kohaliku aja järgi).</P><P>Pärast seda tähtaega saadetud taotlusi ei võeta arvesse.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Taotluste esitamise kord</P><P>Taotlused tuleb koostada prantsuse keeles ja saata vaid hankijale:</P><P>— käsipostiga,</P><P>— kulleriteenusega otse hankijale, allkirjastatud ning kuupäevastatud kviitungi vastu aadressil: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-post: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Uus versioon:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Hankija:</P><P>Euroopa Liit, Brüssel, Belgia, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon, Kesk-Aafrika piirkonna eest ja nimel, keda esindab Kesk-Aafrika Riikide Majandusühendus (ECCAS).</P><P>Täiendavaid selgitusi võib hankijalt küsida e-posti teel „DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu“ hiljemalt 21 päeva enne punktis 23 märgitud taotluste esitamise tähtpäeva.</P><P>Selgitused avaldatakse rahvusvahelise koostöö ja arengu peadirektoraadi veebilehel hiljemalt 5 päeva enne mainitud tähtpäeva.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Sobivus</P><P>[...]</P><P>Hankes võivad osaleda võrdsetel tingimustel kas üksikult või pakkujate ühenduses (konsortsiumis) juriidilised isikud, kes on asutatud mis tahes Euroopa Liidu liikmesriigis, AKV riigis või riigis või territooriumil, mis on selleks volitatud AKV ja EÜ vahelise koostöölepinguga, mille alusel programmi rahastatakse (vt ka punkti 29 allpool).</P><P>Osaleda võivad ka rahvusvahelised organisatsioonid.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Taotluste esitamise tähtpäev</P><P>Kandidaatidel on oluline teada, et taotluste esitamiseks on kaks võimalust: esiteks postiga või kiirkulleriteenusega kirja saatmine ja teiseks käsipostiga kohaletoimetamine.</P><P>Esimesel juhul peab kandidatuuri või pakkumise saatma enne esitamise tähtpäeva – kuupäeva tõendab postitempel või laekumist tõendav kviitung (1), teisel juhul tõendab kuupäeva kandidatuuri/pakkumise kohaletoimetamise hetkel väljastatud kättesaamise kinnitus.</P><P>23.9.2019 kell 12:00 (kohaliku aja järgi).</P><P>Pärast seda tähtaega saadetud taotlusi ei võeta arvesse.</P><P>Hankija võib tõhusa halduse eesmärgil jätta kõrvale kõik taotlused või pakkumised, mis on edastatud postiasutusele õigel ajal ja saabunud hankijast sõltumatul põhjusel pärast eelvalikuraporti või hindamisraporti kinnitamise tähtpäeva,</P><P>kui õigel ajal edastatud ja liiga hilja saabunud taotluste või pakkumiste arvessevõtmine pikendaks oluliselt hindamise protseduuri või ohustaks juba langetatud ja avalikustatud otsust.</P><P>(1) Soovitatav on saata tähitud kiri, sest postitempel võib olla loetamatu.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Taotluste esitamise kord</P><P>Taotlused tuleb koostada prantsuse keeles ja saata vaid hankijale:</P><P>– kas postiga või kullerteenuse vahendusel (sel juhul rakendataks lähetamise kuupäeva, mida tõendaks postitempel või üleandmiskviitungi kuupäev) aadressile:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-post: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>– või isiklikult osaleja või vahendaja kaudu hankijale kohale toimetades allkirjastatud ja kuupäevaga vastuvõtmise kviitungi vastu, mille puhul tõendab pakkumise vastavust laekumise tähtajale vastuvõtmise kviitung, järgmisele aadressile:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-post: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Kõik muud hanketeate tingimused jäävad muutmata. Siinsed muudatused või parandused on selle lahutamatu osa.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: EFA - Szakmai segítségnyújtás a közép-afrikai tengeri biztonsági és védelmi stratégiát támogató program (PASSMAR) végrehajtásához</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>A közzététel hivatkozási száma: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Szerződési felhívás helyesbítése</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Kiegészítés az Európai Unió Hivatalos Lapjához, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Az Európai Unió</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüsszel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>A következő helyett:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Ajánlatkérő</P><P>Európai Unió, Brüsszel, Belgium, amelyet az Európai Bizottság képvisel a Közép-afrikai Államok Gazdasági Közössége (ECCAS) által képviselt közép-afrikai régió nevében és képviseletében.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Jogosultság</P><P>[...]</P><P>A szerződésben történő részvételre egyenlő feltételek mellett jogosult az Európai Unió tagállamaiból, az AKCS-államokból, továbbá a program finanszírozásának keretéül szolgáló AKCS–EK partnerségi megállapodás alapján engedélyezett országokból, illetve területekről származó minden jogi személy (akár egyénileg, akár csoportosulásban \[konzorciumban] jelentkezik) (lásd a lenti 29. pontot is). Nemzetközi szervezetek és az uniós tagállamok állami együttműködési ügynökségei is részt vehetnek.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. A jelentkezések benyújtásának határideje</P><P>A jelentkezések beérkezésének határideje: 23.9.2019 (12:00), helyi idő szerint.</P><P>A fenti határidő után beérkezett jelentkezéseket az ajánlatkérő figyelmen kívül hagyja.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. A jelentkezések benyújtásának módja</P><P>A jelentkezéseket francia nyelven kell benyújtani, kizárólag az ajánlatkérő részére:</P><P>— postaszolgálattal,</P><P>— expressz futárszolgálattal közvetlenül az ajánlatkérő részére az alábbi címre, dátummal és aláírással ellátott átvételi elismervény ellenében: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON; e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Helyesen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Ajánlatkérő</P><P>Európai Unió, Brüsszel, Belgium, amelyet az Európai Bizottság képvisel a Közép-afrikai Államok Gazdasági Közössége (ECCAS) által képviselt közép-afrikai régió nevében és képviseletében.</P><P>Pontosítás legkésőbb az alábbi 23. pontban közölt pályázatbenyújtási határidő előtt 21 nappal kérhető az ajánlatkérőtől a DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu e-mail-címen.</P><P>A pontosításokat a Nemzetközi Együttműködés és a Fejlesztés Főigazgatósága honlapján teszik közzé legkésőbb 5 nappal a pályázatbenyújtási határidő lejárta előtt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Jogosultság</P><P>[...]</P><P>A szerződésben történő részvételre egyenlő feltételek mellett jogosult az Európai Unió tagállamaiból, az AKCS-államokból, továbbá a program finanszírozásának keretéül szolgáló AKCS–EK partnerségi megállapodás alapján engedélyezett országokból, illetve területekről származó minden jogi személy (akár egyénileg, akár csoportosulásban \[konzorciumban] jelentkezik) (lásd a lenti 29. pontot is).</P><P>A részvételre nemzetközi szervezetek is jogosultak.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. A jelentkezések benyújtásának határideje</P><P>Felhívjuk a jelentkezők figyelmét, hogy a jelentkezések beküldése 2 módon történhet: postai úton vagy magán futárszolgálattal, illetve személyes kézbesítéssel.</P><P>Az első esetben a jelentkezést a benyújtási határidő előtt kell elküldeni, amit a postabélyegző vagy az átvételi elismervény igazol(1), míg a második esetben a jelentkezés átvételének időpontjában kapott átvételi elismervény szolgál igazolásként.</P><P>23.9.2019, 12:00 helyi idő szerint.</P><P>A fenti határidő után beérkezett jelentkezéseket az ajánlatkérő figyelmen kívül hagyja.</P><P>Az ajánlatkérő adminisztrációs hatékonysági okokból visszautasíthatja azokat a jelentkezéseket, amelyeket időben adtak fel a postán, de az ajánlatkérő által nem befolyásolható okból a szűkített listát tartalmazó jelentés jóváhagyási dátuma után érkeztek be, amennyiben az időben feladott, de határidőn túl beérkezett jelentkezések elfogadása jelentősen hátráltatná az értékelési eljárást, vagy érintené a már meghozott és kiküldött határozatokat.</P><P/><P>(1) Ha a postai bélyegző nem olvasható, javasoljuk, hogy ajánlott küldeményt küldjön.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. A jelentkezések benyújtásának módja</P><P>A jelentkezéseket francia nyelven kell benyújtani, kizárólag az ajánlatkérő részére:</P><P>— postai úton vagy futárszolgálattal – amely esetben a feladás napját a postabélyegző vagy a feladóvevényen szereplő dátum igazolja – a következő részére:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— vagy személyes kézbesítés útján, melynek keretében maga a jelentkező vagy annak megbízottja az ajánlatkérő helyszínén átadja a dokumentációt, amiről dátummal és aláírással ellátott elismervényt kap – amely esetben az átvétel napját ez az átvételi elismervény igazolja – a következő címen:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Az ajánlati felhívás többi feltétele változatlan marad. A fenti módosítások, illetve javítások az ajánlati felhívás elválaszthatatlan részét képezik.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: EPF - Techninė pagalba Centrinės Afrikos jūrų saugumo ir saugos strategijos rėmimo programai įgyvendinti (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Nuoroda į publikaciją: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Skelbimo apie pirkimą klaidų ištaisymas</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Europos Bendrijos Oficialiojo Leidinio priedas, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Sąjunga</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Briuselis</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Vietoj:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Perkančioji organizacija</P><P>Europos Sąjunga, Briuselis, Belgija, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos Centrinės Afrikos valstybių vardu ir jos naudai, atstovaujama Centrinės Afrikos valstybių ekonominės bendrijos (CAVEB).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Teisė dalyvauti</P><P>[...]</P><P>Dalyvauti konkurse lygiomis teisėmis gali juridiniai asmenys, dalyvaujantys individualiai arba kaip konkurso dalyvių grupės (konsorciumo) dalis, kurie yra įsikūrę vienoje iš Europos Sąjungos valstybių narių, AKR valstybių arba šalyje ar teritorijoje, kurioje galioja AKR ir EB partnerystės susitarimas, pagal kurį finansuojama programa (taip pat žr. 29 punktą toliau). Dalyvauti gali ir Europos Sąjungos valstybių narių tarptautinės organizacijos bei viešojo bendradarbiavimo agentūros.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Paraiškų teikimo terminas</P><P>Galutinis paraiškų gavimo terminas – 23.9.2019 (12:00) vietos laiku.</P><P>Į paraiškas, pateiktas perkančiajai organizacijai po šio termino, atsižvelgiama nebus.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Paraiškų teikimo procedūros</P><P>Paraiškos turi būti parengtos prancūzų kalba ir siunčiamos tiesiogiai perkančiajai organizacijai:</P><P>– per kurjerį;</P><P>– per kurjerio tarnybą tiesiogiai pateikdama paraišką perkančiajai organizacijai, pasirašant gavimo patvirtinimą su data, šiuo adresu: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABONAS, el paštas delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Turi būti:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Perkančioji organizacija</P><P>Europos Sąjunga, Briuselis, Belgija, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos Centrinės Afrikos valstybių vardu ir jos naudai, atstovaujama Centrinės Afrikos valstybių ekonominės bendrijos (CAVEB).</P><P>Dėl paaiškinimų galima kreiptis į perkančiąją organizaciją šiuo el. pašto adresu: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu ne vėliau kaip likus 21 dienai iki pasiūlymų pateikimo termino, nurodyto 23 skyriuje.</P><P>Paaiškinimai bus paskelbti Tarptautinio bendradarbiavimo ir vystymosi GD interneto svetainėje ne vėliau kaip likus 5-ioms dienoms iki galutinės paraiškos pateikimo datos.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Teisė dalyvauti</P><P>[...]</P><P>Dalyvauti konkurse lygiomis teisėmis gali juridiniai asmenys, dalyvaujantys individualiai arba kaip konkurso dalyvių grupės (konsorciumo) dalis, kurie yra įsikūrę 1 iš Europos Sąjungos valstybių narių, AKR valstybių arba šalyje ar teritorijoje, kurioje galioja AKR ir EB partnerystės susitarimas, pagal kurį finansuojama programa (taip pat žr. 29 punktą).</P><P>Konkurse taip pat gali dalyvauti ir tarptautinės organizacijos.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Paraiškų teikimo terminas</P><P>Atkreipiamas kandidato dėmesys į tai, kad yra dvi skirtingos paraiškų siuntimo sistemos: viena – paštu arba per privatų kurjerį, o kita – pristatymas asmeniškai.</P><P>Pirmuoju atveju paraiška turi būti išsiųsta iki paraiškos pateikimo termino, pašto antspaudas arba išsiuntimo kvito data būtų įrodymas (1), bet antruoju atveju, patvirtinimo kvitas, išduotas paraiškos gavimo metu, būtų laikomas įrodymu.</P><P>23.9.2019 (12:00) vietos laiku.</P><P>Į paraiškas, pateiktas perkančiajai organizacijai po šio termino, atsižvelgiama nebus.</P><P>Dėl administracinio efektyvumo perkančioji organizacija gali atmesti bet kokią paraišką, pateiktą paštui laiku, tačiau gautą dėl nuo jo nepriklausančių priežasčių,</P><P>įsigaliojus išankstinės atrankos ataskaitos patvirtinimo datai, jei laiku pateiktų, bet vėluojančių paraiškų priėmimo faktas pernelyg užvilkintų vertinimo procedūrą arba paneigtų jau priimtus ir praneštus sprendimus.</P><P>(1) Rekomenduojama siųsti registruotu paštu, jei pašto antspaudas būtų neįskaitomas.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Paraiškų teikimo procedūros</P><P>Paraiškos turi būti parengtos prancūzų kalba ir siunčiamos tiesiogiai perkančiajai organizacijai:</P><P>– paštu ar per kurjerį, tokiu atveju pašto antspaudas arba išsiuntimo kvito data įrodoma gavimo data:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABONAS, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>– arba tiesiogiai pristatant į perkančiosios organizacijos biurą asmeniškai kandidato arba jo įgaliotojo asmens, pasirašant priėmimo kvitą su data, tuo atveju įrodymas bus priėmimo kvitas, šiuo adresu:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABONAS, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Visos kitos skelbimo apie pirkimą sąlygos ir nuostatos lieka nepakeistos. Šie skelbimo pakeitimai arba pataisymai yra neatskiriama jo dalis.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: EAF - Tehniskā palīdzība Atbalsta programmas jūras drošuma un drošības stratēģijai Centrālajā Āfrikā (PASSMAR) īstenošanai</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Atsauce uz publikāciju: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Labojums paziņojumā par līgumu</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Eiropas Savienības Oficiālā Vēstneša pielikums, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Savienība</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brisele</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Šī teksta vietā:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</P><P>Eiropas Savienība, Brisele, Beļģija, ko Centrālās Āfrikas valstu ekonomikas kopienas (ECCAS) vārdā un interesēs pārstāv Eiropas Komisija</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Tiesības pretendēt</P><P>[...]</P><P>Vienādas tiesības piedalīties līgumā ir juridiskām personām (individuāli vai pretendentu grupas – konsorcija – sastāvā), kuras reģistrētas kādā no Eiropas Savienības dalībvalstīm, ĀKK valstī vai valstī vai teritorijā, kas noteikta ĀKK un EK partnerattiecību nolīgumā, kura ietvaros programma tiek finansēta (sk. arī turpmāk 29. punktu). Tiesības piedalīties ir arī starptautiskām organizācijām un Eiropas Savienības dalībvalstu publiskajām sadarbības aģentūrām.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Pieteikumu iesniegšanas termiņš</P><P>Pieteikumu saņemšanas termiņš ir 23.9.2019 (12:00) pēc vietējā laika.</P><P>Neviens pieteikums, kas līgumslēdzējai iestādei tiks nosūtīts pēc minētā termiņa, netiks izskatīts.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Pieteikumu iesniegšana</P><P>Pieteikumi jāsagatavo franču valodā un jānosūta tikai un vienīgi līgumslēdzējai iestādei kādā no šiem veidiem:</P><P>— iesniedzot personīgi,</P><P>— ar ekspreskurjera pakalpojumu palīdzību iesniedzot pieteikumu tieši līgumslēdzējai iestādei apmaiņā pret parakstītu un datētu kvīti par saņemšanu šādā adresē: Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABONA, e-pasts: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Jābūt:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</P><P>Eiropas Savienība, Brisele, Beļģija, ko Centrālās Āfrikas valstu ekonomikas kopienas (ECCAS) vārdā un interesēs pārstāv Eiropas Komisija</P><P>Skaidrojumus no līgumslēdzējas iestādes var pieprasīt, rakstot uz e-pasta adresi DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu ne vēlāk kā 21 dienu pirms piedāvājumu iesniegšanas termiņa, kas norādīts turpmāk 23. punktā.</P><P>Skaidrojumi tiks publicēti Starptautiskās sadarbības un attīstības ĢD tīmekļa vietnē ne vēlāk kā 5 dienas pirms iesniegšanas termiņa.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Tiesības pretendēt</P><P>[...]</P><P>Vienādas tiesības piedalīties līgumā ir juridiskām personām (individuāli vai pretendentu grupas – konsorcija – sastāvā), kuras reģistrētas kādā no Eiropas Savienības dalībvalstīm, ĀKK valstī vai valstī vai teritorijā, kas noteikta ĀKK un EK partnerattiecību nolīgumā, kura ietvaros programma tiek finansēta (sk. arī turpmāk 29. punktu).</P><P>Tiesības piedalīties ir arī starptautiskām organizācijām.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Pieteikumu iesniegšanas termiņš</P><P>Lūdzam kandidātus pievērst uzmanību, ka ir 2 dažādas pieteikumu iesniegšanas sistēmas – 1. veids ir izmantot pastu vai privātā pasta pakalpojumu, bet 2. veids – iesniegt personīgi.</P><P>1. gadījumā pieteikums jānosūta līdz pieteikumu iesniegšanas termiņam, kā to apliecinās pasta zīmogs vai sūtījuma nodošanas kvīts datums(1), bet 2. gadījumā pierādījums būs saņemšanas apstiprinājums pieteikuma saņemšanas brīdī.</P><P>23.9.2019 plkst. 12:00 (pēc vietējā laika)</P><P>Neviens pieteikums, kas līgumslēdzējai iestādei tiks nosūtīts pēc minētā termiņa, netiks izskatīts.</P><P>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde administratīvās efektivitātes iemeslu dēļ var noraidīt pieteikumus, kas pastā ir iesniegti laikus, taču līgumslēdzēja iestāde tos ir saņēmusi (kāda iemesla dēļ ārpus tās kontroles)</P><P>pēc izraudzīto kandidātu saraksta spēkā stāšanās datuma, ja šo pieteikumu, kas tika iesniegti laikus, bet saņemti pēc termiņa, pieņemšana būtiski kavētu izvērtēšanas procedūru vai apstrīdētu jau pieņemtos un izziņotos lēmumus.</P><P>(1) Ieteicams izmantot ierakstīta pasta sūtījuma pakalpojumu, jo pasta zīmogs var būt nesalasāms.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Pieteikumu iesniegšana</P><P>Pieteikumi jāsagatavo franču valodā un jānosūta tikai un vienīgi līgumslēdzējai iestādei kādā no šiem veidiem:</P><P>— Pa pastu vai ar kurjeru (šajā gadījumā nosūtīšanas datumu apliecina pasta zīmogs vai sūtījuma nodošanas kvīts datums), nosūtot uz šādu adresi:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABONA, e-pasts: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— Nododot personīgi (pašam dalībniekam vai starpniekam tieši līgumslēdzējas iestādes telpās) apmaiņā pret parakstītu un datētu kvīti, un apliecinājums šajā gadījumā ir šis saņemšanas apstiprinājums, šādā adresē:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABONA, e-pasts: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Visi pārējie paziņojuma par līgumu noteikumi un nosacījumi paliek nemainīgi. Šie labojumi vai izmaiņas ir neatņemama paziņojuma par līgumu daļa.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: FEŻ - Għajnuna teknika għall-implimentazzjoni tal-programm ta' appoġġ għall-istrateġija ta' sikurezza u ta' sigurtà marittima fl-Afrika Ċentrali (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tiswija lill-avviż ta' kuntratt</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement tal-Gurnal Ufficjali ta’ l-Unjoni Ewropea’, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L-Unjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussell</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Minflok:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</P><P>l-Unjoni Ewropea, Brussell, il-Belġju, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea, f'isem u għar-reġjun tal-Afrika Ċentrali rrappreżentat mill-Komunità Ekonomika tal-Istati tal-Afrika Ċentrali (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. L-eliġibbiltà</P><P>[...]</P><P>Fil-kuntratt jistgħu jieħdu sehem indaqs il-persuni naturali u l-entitajiet legali (li qegħdin jieħdu sehem jew b'mod individwali jew bħala parti minn grupp — konsorzju — ta' dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti) li huma mwaqqfa f'wieħed mill-Istati Membri tal-Unjoni Ewropea, l-Istati tal-AKP jew f'pajjiż jew territorju awtorizzat mill-Ftehim ta' Sħubija bejn l-AKP u l-KE li jiffinanzja l-programm (ara wkoll il-punt 29 hawn taħt). Jistgħu jieħdu sehem ukoll l-organizzazzjonijiet internazzjonali u l-aġenziji pubbliċi ta' kooperazzjoni tal-Istati Membri tal-Unjoni Ewropea.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Id-data tal-għeluq biex jaslu l-applikazzjonijiet</P><P>Id-data tal-għeluq biex jaslu l-applikazzjonijiet hija fit-23.9.2019 f'12:00 (ħin lokali).</P><P>Mhux se jitqiesu applikazzjonijiet mibgħuta lill-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt wara din id-data tal-għeluq.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Kif għandhom jintbagħtu l-applikazzjonijiet</P><P>L-applikazzjonijiet għandhom jitħejjew bil-Franċiż u għandhom jintbagħtu biss lill-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt:</P><P>— b'kurrier,</P><P>— permezz ta' servizzi ta' messaġġiera espress li jibagħtu direttament l-applikazzjoni lill-awtorità li qiegħda b'firma u data, fl-indirizz li ġej: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, IL-GABON, Email: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Aqra:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</P><P>l-Unjoni Ewropea, Brussell, il-Belġju, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea, f'isem u għar-reġjun tal-Afrika Ċentrali rrappreżentat mill-Komunità Ekonomika tal-Istati tal-Afrika Ċentrali (ECCAS).</P><P>Jistgħu jinkisbu kjarifiki mill-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt fl-indirizz elettroniku li ġej "ELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu mhux aktar tard minn 21 jum qabel id-data tal-għeluq għat-tfigħ tal-applikazzjonijiet mogħtija fit-taqsima 23 hawn taħt.</P><P>Il-kjarifiki għandhom jiġu ppubblikati fuq is-sit tal-Internet tad-DĠ tal-Kooperazzjoni Internazzjonali u l-Iżvilupp sa mhux iktar tard minn 5 ijiem qabel id-data tal-għeluq għat-tfigħ tal-offerti.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. L-eliġibbiltà</P><P>[...]</P><P>Fil-kuntratt jistgħu jieħdu sehem indaqs il-persuni naturali u l-entitajiet legali li qegħdin jieħdu sehem jew b'mod individwali jew bħala parti minn grupp — konsorzju — ta' dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti li huma mwaqqfa f'1 mill-Istati Membri tal-Unjoni Ewropea, l-Istati tal-AKP jew f'pajjiż jew territorju awtorizzat mill-Ftehim ta' Sħubija bejn l-AKP u l-KE li jiffinanzja l-programm (ara wkoll il-punt 29 hawn taħt).</P><P>Jistgħu jieħdu sehem ukoll organizzazzjonijiet internazzjonali.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Id-data tal-għeluq biex jaslu l-applikazzjonijiet</P><P>Tinġibed l-attenzjoni tal-kandidat għall-fatt li jeżistu 2 sistemi differenti għall-kunsinna tal-kandidaturi: waħda bil-posta jew b'kurrier espress privat, u l-oħra bil-kunsinna bl-idejn.</P><P>Fl-ewwel każ, l-applikazzjoni għandha tintbagħat qabel id-data tal-għeluq tal-wasla, bit-timbru tal-posta jew l-irċevuta tad-depożitu jservu ta' prova ta' dan(1), iżda fit-tieni każ, ir-rekord tal-wasla mogħtija fil-mument tar-riċeviment tal-applikazzjoni sservi ta' prova.</P><P>nhar id-23.9.2019 fl-12:00 ħin lokali.</P><P>Mhux se jitqiesu applikazzjonijiet mibgħuta lill-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt wara din id-data tal-għeluq.</P><P>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt tista', għal raġunijiet amministrattivi, tirrifjuta kwalunkwe applikazzjoni mressqa fil-ħin li s-servizz postali iżda li jaslu, għal raġunijiet lil hinn mill-kontroll</P><P>tagħhom, wara d-data effettiva ta' approvazzjoni tar-rapport ta' kwalifika, jekk il-fatt li jiġu aċċettati applikazzjonijiet imressqa fil-ħin, iżda li jaslu tard jirriskjaw li jdewmu b'mod sostanzjali l-proċedura ta' evalwazzjoni jew li jikkompromettu deċiżjonijiet li diġà ttieħdu u ġew innotifikati.</P><P>(1) Huwa rrakkomandat li tintuża l-posta rreġistrata fil-każ li t-timbru tal-posta ma jkunx jinqara.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Kif għandhom jintbagħtu l-applikazzjonijiet</P><P>L-applikazzjonijiet għandhom jitħejjew bil-Franċiż u għandhom jintbagħtu biss lill-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt:</P><P>— bil-posta jew permezz ta' kurrier, u f'dan il-każ it-timbru tal-posta jew id-data fuq l-irċevuta tal-kunsinna, lil:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, IL-GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— jew bl-idejn mogħtija mill-kandidat personalment jew minn rappreżentant tal-kandidat direttament lill-bini tal-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt, bi skambju għal riċevuta ffirmata u ddatata, f'liema każ il-prova għandha tkun kostitwita minn dan ir-rikonoxximent ta' riċevuta, fl-indirizz li ġej:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, IL-GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>It-termini u l-kundizzjonijiet l-oħrajn kollha tal-avviż ta' kuntratt jibqgħu ma jinbidlux. Dawn l-emendi jew tiswijiet jagħmlu parti integrali minnu.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: EFR - Pomoc techniczna na rzecz wdrożenia programu wsparcia strategii bezpieczeństwa i ochrony na morzu w Afryce Środkowej (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Numer referencyjny publikacji: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sprostowanie ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplement do Dziennika Urzędowego Unii Europejskiej, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unia Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruksela</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Zamiast:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Instytucja zamawiająca</P><P>Unia Europejska, Bruksela, Belgia, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską działającą w imieniu i na rzecz Afryki Środkowej, reprezentowanej przez Wspólnotę Gospodarczą Państw Afryki Środkowej (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Kwalifikacja</P><P>[...]</P><P>Uczestnictwo w zamówieniu jest otwarte na równych warunkach dla wszystkich osób prawnych uczestniczących indywidualnie lub w grupie — konsorcjum — oferentów z siedzibą w państwach członkowskich Unii Europejskiej, w państwach AKP i w krajach lub na terytoriach dopuszczonych na podstawie umowy o partnerstwie AKP–WE, na mocy której program jest finansowany (zob. również pkt 29 poniżej). Udział otwarty jest również dla organizacji międzynarodowych i publicznych agencji ds. współpracy należących do krajów członkowskich Unii Europejskiej.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termin składania wniosków</P><P>Termin przyjmowania wniosków wyznaczono na 23.9.2019, godz. 12:00 czasu lokalnego.</P><P>Wnioski przesłane do instytucji zamawiającej po tym terminie nie będą brane pod uwagę.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Sposób składania wniosków</P><P>Wnioski należy przesyłać do zamawiającego, wyłącznie w języku francuskim:</P><P>— za pośrednictwem doręczyciela,</P><P>— za pośrednictwem ekspresowej przesyłki kurierskiej, składając wniosek bezpośrednio do instytucji zamawiającej, za potwierdzeniem odbioru z podpisem i datą, na następujący adres: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Powinno być:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Instytucja zamawiająca</P><P>Unia Europejska, Bruksela, Belgia, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską działającą w imieniu i na rzecz Afryki Środkowej, reprezentowanej przez Wspólnotę Gospodarczą Państw Afryki Środkowej (ECCAS).</P><P>Szczegółowe informacje można uzyskać od instytucji zamawiającej pod następującym adresem e-mail: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu najpóźniej 21 dni przed upływem terminu składania wniosków określonego w punkcie 23 poniżej.</P><P>Wyjaśnienia zostaną opublikowane w witrynie internetowej DG ds. Współpracy Międzynarodowej i Rozwoju, najpóźniej na 5 dni przed upływem terminu składania ofert.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Kwalifikacja</P><P>[...]</P><P>Uczestnictwo w zamówieniu jest otwarte na równych warunkach dla wszystkich osób prawnych uczestniczących indywidualnie lub w grupie — konsorcjum — oferentów z siedzibą w państwach członkowskich Unii Europejskiej, w państwach AKP i w krajach lub na terytoriach dopuszczonych na podstawie umowy o partnerstwie AKP–WE, na mocy której program jest finansowany (zob. również pkt 29 poniżej).</P><P>Uczestnictwo jest również otwarte dla organizacji międzynarodowych.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termin składania wniosków</P><P>Zwraca się uwagę wnioskodawcy na fakt, że istnieją 2 różne systemy wysyłania wniosków: za pośrednictwem poczty lub prywatnych usług kuriera albo za doręczeniem osobistym.</P><P>W pierwszym przypadku wniosek powinien zostać wysłany przed upływem terminu składania wniosków, przy czym decyduje data stempla pocztowego lub data potwierdzenia nadania (1), natomiast w drugim przypadku decydujące jest potwierdzenie odbioru wniosku otrzymane przy odbiorze.</P><P>23.9.2019, 12:00, czasu lokalnego.</P><P>Wnioski przesłane do instytucji zamawiającej po tym terminie nie będą brane pod uwagę.</P><P>Instytucja zamawiająca może, z uwagi na skuteczność administracyjną, odrzucić każdy wniosek złożony na czas do służby pocztowej, ale otrzymany, z przyczyn od niej</P><P>niezależnych, po faktycznej dacie zatwierdzenia sprawozdania ze wstępnego wyboru, jeżeli przyjęcie wniosków złożonych na czas, ale otrzymanych z opóźnieniem, mogłoby niepotrzebnie opóźnić procedurę oceny lub podważyć decyzje już podjęte i ogłoszone.</P><P>(1) Zaleca się wysyłanie poczty listem poleconym na wypadek sytuacji, gdyby znaczek pocztowy nie był czytelny.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Sposób składania wniosków</P><P>Wnioski należy przesyłać do zamawiającego, wyłącznie w języku francuskim:</P><P>— pocztą lub przesyłką kurierską, w tym przypadku decyduje data stempla pocztowego lub data potwierdzenia nadania, na adres:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— osobiście przez kandydata lub przez przedstawiciela kandydata, za potwierdzeniem odbioru opatrzonym podpisem i datą stanowiącym dowód doręczenia, bezpośrednio do siedziby instytucji zamawiającej znajdującej się pod poniższym adresem:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Pozostałe warunki wymienione w ogłoszeniu o zamówieniu nie ulegają zmianie. Niniejsze zmiany lub poprawki stanowią integralną część ogłoszenia o zamówieniu.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: ERF - Odborná pomoc pri realizácii programu na podporu stratégie námornej ochrany a bezpečnosti v strednej Afrike (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale – PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčné číslo: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Korigendum k oznámeniu o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Príloha k Úradnému vestníku Európskej únie, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska únia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namiesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Verejný obstarávateľ</P><P>Európska únia, Brusel, Belgicko, zastúpená Európskou komisiou v mene a v záujme Stredoafrického regiónu zastúpeného Hospodárskym spoločenstvom stredoafrických štátov (ECCAS),</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Spôsobilosť</P><P>[...]</P><P>Účasť na obstarávaní je otvorená za rovnakých podmienok pre právne subjekty zúčastňujúce sa samostatne alebo v zoskupení – konzorciu – uchádzačov, ktoré boli založené v 1 z členských štátov Európskej únie, krajinách AKT alebo v krajine alebo na území oprávnenom Dohodou o partnerstve AKT – ES, v rámci ktorej je program financovaný (pozri aj bod 29 nižšie). Účasť na obstarávaní je takisto otvorená pre medzinárodné organizácie a verejné agentúry pre spoluprácu s členskými štátmi Európskej únie.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Konečný termín predloženia prihlášok:</P><P>Konečný termín prijatia prihlášok je 23.9.2019 o 12:00 (miestneho času).</P><P>Prihlášky odoslané verejnému obstarávateľovi po tomto konečnom termíne sa nebudú brať do úvahy.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Spôsob predloženia prihlášok</P><P>Prihlášky musia byť vypracované vo francúzštine a zaslané výlučne obstarávateľovi:</P><P>— doručiteľom,</P><P>— expresnou kuriérskou službou, ktorá doručí prihlášku priamo obstarávateľovi, oproti podpísanej a datovanej potvrdenke o prijatí, na túto adresu: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Viď:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Verejný obstarávateľ</P><P>Európska únia, Brusel, Belgicko, zastúpená Európskou komisiou v mene a v záujme Stredoafrického regiónu zastúpeného Hospodárskym spoločenstvom stredoafrických štátov (ECCAS),</P><P>Žiadosti o objasnenie je možné zaslať verejnému obstarávateľovi e-mailom na adresu: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu a to aspoň 21 dní pred konečným termínom predloženia ponúk uvedeným v bode 23 nižšie.</P><P>Objasnenia budú zverejnené na webovej stránke Generálneho riaditeľstva pre medzinárodnú spoluprácu a rozvoj najneskôr 5 dní pred konečným termínom predloženia ponúk.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Spôsobilosť</P><P>[...]</P><P>Účasť na obstarávaní je otvorená za rovnakých podmienok pre právne subjekty zúčastňujúce sa samostatne alebo v zoskupení – konzorciu – uchádzačov, ktoré boli založené v 1 z členských štátov Európskej únie, krajinách AKT alebo v krajine alebo na území oprávnenom Dohodou o partnerstve AKT – ES, v rámci ktorej je program financovaný (pozri aj bod 29 nižšie).</P><P>Účasť je otvorená aj pre medzinárodné organizácie.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Konečný termín predloženia prihlášok:</P><P>Uchádzačov upozorňujeme, že existujú 2 rôzne spôsoby odoslania prihlášok, a to buď poštou, prípadne súkromnou doručovateľskou službou, alebo osobným doručením.</P><P>V prvom prípade musí byť prihláška odoslaná pred konečným termínom predloženia, pričom dôkazom bude poštová pečiatka alebo podací lístok(1), ale v druhom prípade bude dôkazom potvrdenie o prijatí vydané v čase prijatia prihlášky.</P><P>23.9.2019 o 12:00 (miestneho času).</P><P>Prihlášky odoslané verejnému obstarávateľovi po tomto konečnom termíne sa nebudú brať do úvahy.</P><P>Verejný obstarávateľ môže z dôvodov administratívnej efektívnosti zamietnuť všetky prihlášky, ktoré síce boli poštou odoslané včas, ale z dôvodov nad rámec kontroly obstarávateľa boli doručené po dátume schválenia správy o zostavení užšieho zoznamu, a to v prípade, že by prijatie týchto včas odoslaných, ale neskoro prijatých prihlášok významne oneskorilo postup hodnotenia alebo by sa tým spochybnili už prijaté a zverejnené rozhodnutia.</P><P/><P>(1) Odporúča sa odoslanie doporučenou poštou, pretože sa môže stať, že poštová pečiatka nebude čitateľná.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Spôsob predloženia prihlášok</P><P>Prihlášky musia byť vypracované vo francúzštine a zaslané výlučne obstarávateľovi:</P><P>— buď poštou alebo kuriérskou službou (v tomto prípade bude potvrdením o dodržaní konečného termínu doručenia ponúk poštová pečiatka alebo doklad o doručení) na adresu:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— alebo osobným doručením uchádzačom alebo jeho zástupcom priamo verejnému obstarávateľovi oproti podpísanému a datovanému potvrdeniu o prijatí (v tomto prípade bude potvrdením o dodržaní konečného termínu doručenia ponúk potvrdenie o prijatí) na adresu:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Všetky ostatné podmienky oznámenia o obstarávaní zostávajú nezmenené. Tieto zmeny alebo opravy tvoria jeho neoddeliteľnú súčasť.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: ERS - Tehnična pomoč pri izvajanju Podpornega programa za strategijo pomorske varnosti in zaščite v Srednji Afriki (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčna številka objave: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Popravek obvestila o naročilu</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Uradnemu listu Evropske unije, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselj</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Naročnik</P><P>Evropska unija, Bruselj, Belgija, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija, v imenu in za račun srednjeafriške regije, ki jo zastopa Gospodarska skupnost srednjeafriških držav (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Upravičenost</P><P>[...]</P><P>V naročilu lahko pod enakimi pogoji sodelujejo vse pravne osebe (ki sodelujejo samostojno ali kot del skupine – konzorcija – ponudnikov), ki imajo sedež v državi članici Evropske unije, državi AKP ali v državi ali na ozemlju, upravičenem na podlagi Sporazuma o partnerstvu AKP-ES, v okviru katerega se program financira (glejte tudi točko 29 spodaj). Sodelujejo lahko tudi mednarodne organizacije in javni organi za sodelovanje med državami članicami Evropske unije.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Skrajni rok za oddajo prijav</P><P>Skrajni rok za sprejemanje prijav je 23.9.2019 (12:00) po lokalnem času.</P><P>Prijave, ki bodo naročniku poslane po tem skrajnem roku, se ne bodo upoštevale.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Način pošiljanja prijav</P><P>Prijave je treba pripraviti v francoščini in poslati izključno naročniku:</P><P>— po prinosniku,</P><P>— po hitri kurirski službi neposredno naročniku, v zameno za podpisano in datirano potrdilo o prejemu, na naslednji naslov: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, rue de l’Union européenne 473, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, E‑naslov: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Beri:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Naročnik</P><P>Evropska unija, Bruselj, Belgija, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija, v imenu in za račun srednjeafriške regije, ki jo zastopa Gospodarska skupnost srednjeafriških držav (ECCAS).</P><P>Zahtevke za pojasnila lahko pošljete naročniku na elektronski naslov DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu najpozneje 21 dni pred skrajnim rokom za oddajo ponudb, navedenim v oddelku 23 spodaj.</P><P>Pojasnila bodo objavljena na spletnem mestu GD za mednarodno sodelovanje in razvoj najpozneje 5 dni pred skrajnim rokom za oddajo.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Upravičenost</P><P>[...]</P><P>Sodelovanje v naročilu je pod enakimi pogoji odprto za pravne subjekte, ki sodelujejo samostojno ali kot del skupine – konzorcija – ponudnikov, ustanovljene v 1 izmed držav članic Evropske unije, držav AKP ali v državi ali na ozemlju, ki ga pooblašča Partnerski sporazum AKP–ES, v okviru katerega se program financira (glej tudi točko 29 spodaj).</P><P>Sodelujejo lahko tudi mednarodne organizacije.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Skrajni rok za oddajo prijav</P><P>Kandidati naj bodo pozorni na to, da obstajata 2 različna sistema za oddajo prijav: prvi je po pošti ali zasebni kurirski službi, drugi pa z osebno vročitvijo.</P><P>V prvem primeru je treba prijavo poslati do skrajnega roka za oddajo, pri čemer kot dokazilo o pravočasnosti velja poštni žig ali datum potrdila o oddaji pošiljke(1), v drugem primeru pa kot dokazilo o pravočasnosti velja potrdilo o prejemu, izdano ob prejemu prijave.</P><P>23.9.2019 (12:00) po lokalnem času.</P><P>Prijave, ki bodo naročniku poslane po tem skrajnem roku, se ne bodo upoštevale.</P><P>Naročnik lahko iz razlogov upravne učinkovitosti zavrne katero koli prijavo, ki je bila pravočasno poslana po pošti, vendar jo je naročnik iz razlogov, nad katerimi nima</P><P>nadzora, prejel po datumu odobritve poročila o pripravi seznama v ožji izbor uvrščenih kandidatov, če bi sprejetje teh pravočasno poslanih, a prepozno prejetih prijav znatno zavleklo postopek ocenjevanja ali izpodbijalo že sprejete in priglašene sklepe.</P><P>(1) Priporoča se uporaba priporočene pošte, saj se lahko zgodi, da poštni žig ne bi bil berljiv.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Način pošiljanja prijav</P><P>Prijave je treba pripraviti v francoščini in poslati izključno naročniku:</P><P>— bodisi po pošti ali kurirski službi, pri čemer kot dokazilo o pravočasnosti velja poštni žig ali datum potrdila o oddaji pošiljke, na naslov:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— bodisi z osebno vročitvijo kandidata samega ali njegovega pooblaščenega zastopnika neposredno v prostorih naročnika, v zameno za podpisano in datirano potrdilo o prejemu, pri čemer kot dokazilo o pravočasnosti velja to potrdilo, na naslednji naslov:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Vsi ostali formalni pogoji obvestila o naročilu ostanejo nespremenjeni. Te spremembe ali popravki so sestavni del obvestila o naročilu.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: CEF - Cúnamh teicniúil chun an Clár Tacaíochta a chur chun feidhme i leith na Straitéise Slándála Muirí san Afraic Láir (Programme d'appui à la stratégie de sûreté et de sécurité maritimes en Afrique centrale (PASSMAR))</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ceartúchán ar an bhfógra conartha</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Forlíonaidh d'Iris Oifigiúil an Aontais Eorpaigh, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An tAontas Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>an Bhruiséil</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Seachas:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Údarás conarthach</P><P>An tAontas Eorpach, an Bhruiséil, an Bheilg, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach, ar son agus chun cuntais Chomhphobal Eacnamaíoch Stáit na hAfraice Láir (ECCAS),</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Incháilitheacht</P><P>[...]</P><P>Tá rannpháirtíocht sa chonradh oscailte ar théarmaí comhionanna d'aonáin dhlítheanacha uile ag glacadh páirte ina n-aonar nó mar chuid de ghrúpáil — cuibhreannas — tairgeoirí, atá bunaithe i gceann de Bhallstát an Aontais Eorpaigh, i Stáit ACC nó i dtír nó i gcríoch atá údaraithe faoin gComhaontú Comhpháirtíochta ACC-CE faoina bhfuil an clár á mhaoiniú (féach pointe 29 thíos fosta). Tá rannpháirtíocht oscailte freisin d’eagraíochtaí idirnáisiúnta agus do ghníomhaireachtaí comhair phoiblí Bhallstáit an Aontais Eorpaigh.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. An dáta deiridh chun iarratais a chur isteach</P><P>Is é 12.00 (am áitiúil) an 23.9.2019 an spriocdháta le haghaidh iarratais a fháil.</P><P>Ní bhreithneofar aon tairiscint a thaisctear leis an Údarás Conarthach tar éis an spriocdháta sin.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Nósanna imeachta chun iarratais a chur isteach</P><P>Ní mór iarratais a thaisceadh i bhFraincis amháin agus iad a chur chuig an údarás conarthach:</P><P>— ag iompróir,</P><P>— trí mhearsheirbhís cúiréireachta ag cur isteach an t-iarratas go díreach chuig an údarás conarthach, i gcoinne admhála admhála sínithe agus dátaithe, chuig an seoladh a leanas: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, AN GHABÚIN, email: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Léigh:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Údarás conarthach</P><P>An tAontas Eorpach, an Bhruiséil, an Bheilg, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach, ar son agus chun cuntais Chomhphobal Eacnamaíoch Stáit na hAfraice Láir (ECCAS),</P><P>Féadfar soiléiriú a lorg ón údarás conarthach ag an seoladh ríomhphoist a leanas: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu tráth na déanaí ná 21 lá roimh an spriocdháta chun tairiscintí a chur isteach a liostaítear in alt 23 thíos.</P><P>Foilseofar soiléirithe ar láithreán gréasáin na hArd-Stiúrthóireachta um Chomhar Idirnáisiúnta agus Forbairt ar a dhéanaí 5 lá roimh an spriocdháta chun iarratais a thaisceadh.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Incháilitheacht</P><P>[...]</P><P>Tá rannpháirtíocht sa chonradh oscailte ar théarmaí comhionanna d'aonáin dhlítheanacha uile ag glacadh páirte ina n-aonar nó mar chuid de ghrúpáil — cuibhreannas — tairgeoirí, atá bunaithe i gceann de Bhallstát an Aontais Eorpaigh, i Stáit ACC nó i dtír nó i gcríoch atá údaraithe faoin gComhaontú Comhpháirtíochta ACC-CE faoina bhfuil an clár á mhaoiniú (féach pointe 29 thíos fosta).</P><P>Tá rannpháirtíocht ar oscailt freisin d'eagraíochtaí idirnáisiúnta.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. An dáta deiridh chun iarratais a chur isteach</P><P>Tarraingítear aird an iarrthóra ar an gcaoi gurb ann do 2 chóras éagsúla chun tairiscint a sheoladh: tríd an bpost nó trí sheirbhís chúiréireachta, nó iad a sheachadadh de láimh.</P><P>Sa chéad chás, ní mór an t-iarratas a sheoladh roimh an spriocdháta taiscthe, leis an bpostmharc nó an duillín taisce mar chruthúnas (1), agus sa dara cás is í an admháil fála a thugtar ag am seachadta an iarratais a bheidh mar chruthúnas.</P><P>23.9.2019 (12:00), am áitiúil.</P><P>Ní bhreithneofar aon tairiscint a thaisctear leis an Údarás Conarthach tar éis an spriocdháta sin.</P><P>Féadfaidh an t-údarás conarthach, ar chúiseanna a bhaineann le héifeachtúlacht riaracháin, diúltú d’aon iarratas a chuirtear isteach in am chuig an tseirbhís poist ach a fhaightear, ar chúiseanna nach bhfuil neart</P><P>aige air, tar éis dháta feidhme formheasta na tuairisce réamhroghnúcháin, más amhlaidh go bhféadfaí moill rófhada a chur leis an bpróiseas meastóireachta de dheasca glacadh déanach iarratas a chuirtear isteach in am ach a thagann isteach go déanach, nó más amhlaidh go dtugtar faoi cheist leo cinntí atá déanta agus curtha in iúl cheana féin.</P><P>(1) Moltar úsáid a bhaint as an bpost cláraithe ar eagla nach mbeadh an postmharc inléite.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Nósanna imeachta chun iarratais a chur isteach</P><P>Ní mór iarratais a thaisceadh i bhFraincis amháin agus iad a chur chuig an údarás conarthach:</P><P>— sa phost nó trí sheirbhís chúiréireachta, sa chás sin, is é an postmharc nó dáta an duillín taisce a bheidh ina fhianaise maidir leis an dáta seachadta, chuig:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, AN GHABÚIN, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— nó seachadadh de láimh ag an iarrthóir féin nó ag gníomhaire go díreach chuig áitreabh an údaráis chonarthaigh ach admháil arna síniú agus arna dátú a fháil, agus sa chás sin beidh an admháil seo mar fhianaise ar admháil fála, chuig:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, AN GHABÚIN, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Níl athrú ar bith thairis sin ar théarmaí ná ar choinníollacha an fhógra chonartha. Is dlúthchuid den fhógra conartha iad na hathruithe nó na ceartúcháin seo.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: ЕФР - Техническа помощ за изпълнение на програмата за помощ за стратегията за морска сигурност и безопасност в Централна Африка (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Референтен номер на публикация: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Поправка към обявление за поръчка</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Приложение към Официален вестник на Европейския съюз, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейски съюз</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Брюксел</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Вместо:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Възлагащ орган</P><P>Европейски съюз, Брюксел, Бeлгия, представляван от Европейската комисия, от името и за сметка на Икономическата общност на държавите от Централна Африка (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Право на участие</P><P>[...]</P><P>Участието в поръчката е открито при равни условия за юридически лица, участващи индивидуално или като част от обединение – консорциум – от оференти, които са установени в една от държавите-членки на Европейския съюз, държавите от АКТБ или в държава или територия, упълномощена от Споразумението за партньорство АКТБ-ЕО, по което се финансира програмата (вж. също точка 29 по-долу). Могат да участват и международни организации и публични агенции за сътрудничество на държавите-членки на Европейския съюз.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Краен срок за подаване на заявления</P><P>Крайната дата за получаване на заявленията е 23.9.2019 г.в 12:00 часа, (местно време).</P><P>Заявления за участие, изпратени до възлагащия орган след този краен срок, няма да се взимат предвид.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Как се подават заявленията за участие</P><P>Заявленията се изпращат на френски език единствено до възлагащия орган:</P><P>— по приносител,</P><P>— чрез експресна куриерска служба, която директно депозира заявлението за участие до възлагащия орган, срещу подписана и датирана разписка за получаване на следния адрес: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, ГАБОН, електронна поща: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Да се чете:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Възлагащ орган</P><P>Европейски съюз, Брюксел, Бeлгия, представляван от Европейската комисия, от името и за сметка на Икономическата общност на държавите от Централна Африка (ECCAS).</P><P>Уточнения може да се изискват от възлагащия орган на следния имейл адрес: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu до 21 дни преди крайната дата за подаване на оферти, посочена в раздел 23 по-долу.</P><P>Разясненията ще бъдат публикувани на интернет страницата на ГД „Международно сътрудничество и развитие“ не по-късно от 5 дни преди крайния срок за подаване на оферти.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Право на участие</P><P>[...]</P><P>Участието в поръчката е открито при равни условия за юридически лица, участващи индивидуално или като част от обединение – консорциум – от оференти, които са установени в една от държавите-членки на Европейския съюз, държавите от АКТБ или в държава или територия, упълномощена от Споразумението за партньорство АКТБ-ЕО, по което се финансира програмата (вж. също точка 29 по-долу).</P><P>До участие се допускат и международни организации.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Краен срок за подаване на заявления</P><P>На кандидата се обръща внимание на факта, че съществуват 2 различни системи за изпращане на заявления за участие: по пощата или по куриер и чрез предаване лично.</P><P>В 1-ия случай, заявлението за участие трябва да бъде изпратена преди датата и срока за подаване, което се доказва от пощенското клеймо или разписката за депозиране (1), но във 2-ия случай, за доказателство ще служи обратната разписка, дадена в момента на получаване на заявлението за участие.</P><P>23.9.2019 12:00 (местно време).</P><P>Заявления за участие, изпратени до възлагащия орган след този краен срок, няма да се взимат предвид.</P><P>Възлагащият орган може, с цел административна ефикасност, да отхвърли всяко предложение или оферта, подадени в срок към пощенската услуга, но получени, поради всякакви причини, независещи от</P><P>него, след датата на влизане в сила на одобрението на доклада за предварителен избор, ако приемането на подадените навреме, но пристигнали късно заявления за участие рискува да забави прекалено процедурата по оценка или да върне за разглеждане вече взети и обявени решения.</P><P>(1) Препоръчва се писмото да се изпраща препоръчано в случай, че пощенското клеймо не се чете.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Как се подават заявленията за участие</P><P>Заявленията се изпращат на френски език единствено до възлагащия орган:</P><P>— или по пощата, или по куриер, в който случай ще важат пощенското клеймо или датата на разписката за изпращане, до:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, ГАБОН, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— или чрез директно предаване в помещенията на възлагащия орган лично от кандидата или от всеки негов пълномощник, срещу подписана обратна разписка с дата, в който случай ще бъде използвана обратната разписка, на следния адрес:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, ГАБОН, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Всички други срокове и условия на обявлението за поръчка остават непроменени. Тези изменения или поправки съставляват неделима част от него.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: FED - Asistență tehnică pentru punerea în aplicare a programului de sprijin pentru strategia de siguranță și securitate maritimă în Africa Centrală (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referința publicației: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Erată la anunțul de participare</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplimentul Jurnalului Oficial al Uniunii Europene, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Uniunea Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>În loc de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Autoritatea contractantă</P><P>Uniunea Europeană, Bruxelles, Belgia, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană, în numele și în favoarea regiunii Africii Centrale, reprezentată de Comunitatea Economică a Statelor din Africa Centrală (CEEAC).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Eligibilitate</P><P>[...]</P><P>Participarea la contract este deschisă în condiții de egalitate tuturor persoanelor juridice (care participă fie individual, fie în cadrul unui grup – consorțiu – de ofertanți), care sunt stabilite într-unul dintre statele membre ale Uniunii Europene, într-un stat ACP sau într-o țară sau într-un teritoriu autorizat prin Acordul de parteneriat ACPCE în baza căruia este finanțat programul (a se vedea, de asemenea, punctul 29 de mai jos). Participarea este, de asemenea, deschisă organizațiilor internaționale și agențiilor de cooperare publică ale statelor membre ale Uniunii Europene.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termenul-limită de depunere a candidaturilor</P><P>Termenul-limită de depunere a candidaturilor este 23.9.2019 (12:00), ora locală.</P><P>Candidaturile trimise la autoritatea contractantă după acest termen limită nu vor fi luate în considerare.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalități de depunere a candidaturilor</P><P>Candidaturile trebuie redactate în limba franceză și trimise exclusiv autorității contractante:</P><P>— prin livrare directă,</P><P>— prin servicii de curierat, depunând candidatura direct la autoritatea contractantă, în schimbul unei confirmări de primire semnate și datate, la adresa următoare: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>A se citi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Autoritatea contractantă</P><P>Uniunea Europeană, Bruxelles, Belgia, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană, în numele și în favoarea regiunii Africii Centrale, reprezentată de Comunitatea Economică a Statelor din Africa Centrală (CEEAC).</P><P>Clarificări pot fi solicitate de la Autoritatea Contractantă la următoarea adresă de e-mail: DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu cu cel puțin 21 de zile înainte de termenul limită de depunere a ofertelor enumerate în secțiunea 23 de mai jos.</P><P>Clarificările vor fi publicate pe site-ul DG Cooperare Internațională și Dezvoltare cu cel puțin 5 zile înainte de termenul-limită de depunere.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Eligibilitate</P><P>[...]</P><P>Participarea la contract este deschisă în condiții de egalitate tuturor persoanelor juridice care participă fie individual, fie în cadrul unui grup – consorțiu – de ofertanți și care sunt stabilite în 1 dintre statele membre ale Uniunii Europene, într-un stat ACP sau într-o țară sau într-un teritoriu autorizat prin Acordul de parteneriat ACP-CE în baza căruia este finanțat programul (a se vedea, de asemenea, punctul 29 de mai jos).</P><P>Participarea este deschisă și organizațiilor internaționale.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termenul-limită de depunere a candidaturilor</P><P>Se atrage atenția candidatului asupra faptului că există 2 sisteme diferite pentru trimiterea candidaturilor: una prin poștă sau prin serviciu de curierat privat, iar cealaltă prin livrare manuală.</P><P>În primul caz, candidatura trebuie transmisă înainte de data-limită a depunerii, caz în care data expedierii va fi atestată de ștampila poștală sau de data de pe confirmarea de primire(1), dar în al doilea caz, drept dovadă va servi confirmarea de primire emisă în momentul primirii ofertei.</P><P>23.9.2019 (12:00), ora locală.</P><P>Candidaturile trimise la autoritatea contractantă după acest termen limită nu vor fi luate în considerare.</P><P>Autoritatea contractantă poate, din motive de eficiență administrativă, să respingă orice propunere sau ofertă depusă în termenul stabilit serviciului poștal, dar primită, din motive independente de</P><P>voința sa, după data efectivă a aprobării raportului de preselecție, dacă acceptarea candidaturilor depuse în timp, dar livrate cu întârziere pot întârzia procesul de evaluare în mod exagerat sau să pună la îndoială deciziile deja luate și comunicate.</P><P>(1) Se recomandă utilizarea corespondenței recomandate în cazul în care ștampila poștală nu este lizibilă.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Modalități de depunere a candidaturilor</P><P>Candidaturile trebuie redactate în limba franceză și trimise exclusiv autorității contractante:</P><P>— fie corespondență sau prin curier, caz în care ștampila poștală sau data de pe chitanța de livrare fac dovada; la:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, e-mail: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— fie prin livrare personală la sediul autorității contractante de către candidatul în persoană sau de către orice reprezentant al candidatului, contra unei confirmări de primire semnate și datate, caz în care confirmarea de primire face dovada, la următoarea adresă:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Toți ceilalți termeni și toate celelalte condiții din anunțul de participare rămân neschimbate. Aceste modificări sau rectificări fac parte integrantă din acesta.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: ERF - Tehnička pomoć za provedbu Programa podrške strategiji morske zaštite i sigurnosti u središnjoj Africi (PASSMAR)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Uputa na objavu: EuropeAid/140226/DH/SER/MULTI</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ispravak poziva na nadmetanje</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatak Službenom listu Europske unije, 12.8.2019, 2019/S 154-378787)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Umjesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Javni naručitelj</P><P>Europska unija, Bruxelles, Belgija, koju predstavlja Europska komisija, uime i za račun regije središnje Afrike koju zastupa Gospodarska zajednica srednjoafričkih država (ECCAS).</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Prihvatljivost</P><P>[...]</P><P>Sudjelovanje u ugovoru otvoreno je pod jednakim uvjetima pravnim osobama koje sudjeluju ili samostalno ili kao članovi zajednice — konzorcija — ponuditelja s poslovnim nastanom u 1 od država članica Europske unije, država AKP-a ili u državi ili na teritoriju odobrenom u okviru Sporazuma o partnerstvu AKP-a i EZ-a na temelju kojeg se program financira (vidjeti i točku 29. u nastavku). Sudjelovanje je otvoreno i međunarodnim organizacijama i javnim agencijama za suradnju u državama članicama Europske unije.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Krajnji rok za podnošenje prijava</P><P>Krajnji je datum za zaprimanje prijava 23.9.2019. u 12:00 sati (prema lokalnom vremenu).</P><P>Prijave poslane javnom naručitelju nakon navedenog roka neće se razmatrati.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Način podnošenja prijava</P><P>Prijave trebaju biti sastavljene na francuskom jeziku i poslane isključivo javnom naručitelju:</P><P>— dostavom,</P><P>— korištenjem službe brze dostave izravno javnom naručitelju u zamjenu za potpisanu i datiranu potvrdu o primitku na sljedeću adresu: délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, E-pošta: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Glasi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>5. Javni naručitelj</P><P>Europska unija, Bruxelles, Belgija, koju predstavlja Europska komisija, uime i za račun regije središnje Afrike koju zastupa Gospodarska zajednica srednjoafričkih država (ECCAS).</P><P>Od javnog se naručitelja mogu tražiti pojašnjenja na sljedećoj adresi e-pošte „DELEGATION-GABON-TENDERS@eeas.europa.eu”, najkasnije 21 dan prije roka za dostavu prijava navedenog u točki 23. u nastavku.</P><P>Pojašnjenja će se objaviti na mrežnom mjestu GU za međunarodnu suradnju i razvoj najkasnije 5 dana prije roka za dostavu.</P><P>[...]</P><P>11. Prihvatljivost</P><P>[...]</P><P>Sudjelovanje u ugovoru otvoreno je pod jednakim uvjetima pravnim osobama koje sudjeluju ili samostalno ili kao članovi zajednice — konzorcija — ponuditelja s poslovnim nastanom u 1 od država članica Europske unije, država AKP-a ili u državi ili na teritoriju odobrenom u okviru Sporazuma o partnerstvu AKP-a i EZ-a na temelju kojeg se program financira (vidjeti i točku 29. u nastavku).</P><P>Sudjelovanje je otvoreno i za međunarodne organizacije.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Krajnji rok za podnošenje prijava</P><P>Natjecatelj posebnu pozornost treba obratiti na činjenicu da postoje 2 različita načina slanja prijava: 1. je poštom ili privatnom poštanskom uslugom, a 2. osobnim uručenjem.</P><P>U 1. se slučaju prijava mora poslati prije datuma i roka za podnošenje prijava, evidentirano poštanskim žigom ili dostavnicom(1), dok u 2. slučaju kao dokaz služi potvrda o zaprimljenoj prijavi dana prilikom dostave prijave.</P><P>23.9.2019. u 12:00 sati lokalno vrijeme.</P><P>Prijave poslane javnom naručitelju nakon navedenog roka neće se razmatrati.</P><P>Radi administrativne učinkovitosti javni naručitelj može odbiti svaku ponudu podnesenu na vrijeme poštanskoj službi, ali koja je zaprimljena, iz razloga izvan</P><P>kontrole javnog naručitelja, nakon datuma stupanja na snagu odobrenja izvješća o odabiru, ako bi prihvaćanje ponuda podnesenih na vrijeme, ali koje su kasno zaprimljene, znatno odgodilo postupak ocjene ili ugrozilo odluke koje su već donesene i objavljene.</P><P>(1) Preporučuje se korištenje usluge preporučene pošte jer poštanski žig možda neće biti čitljiv.</P><P>[...]</P><P>25. Način podnošenja prijava</P><P>Prijave trebaju biti sastavljene na francuskom jeziku i poslane isključivo javnom naručitelju:</P><P>— poštom ili dostavljačem, u tom se slučaju dokazom smatra poštanski žig ili datum na dostavnici, na sljedeću adresu:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et-Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>— osobnim uručenjem ili preko ovlaštenog predstavnika, javnom naručitelju u zamjenu za potpisanu potvrdu primitka s naznačenim datumom, u tom se slučaju dokazom smatra potvrda o primitku, na sljedeću adresu:</P><P>Délégation de l'Union européenne au Gabon, pour la Guinée Equatoriale, Sao Tomé-et Principe et la CEEAC, 473 rue de l’Union européenne, le Gué Gué, Libreville, GABON, courriel: delegation-gabon-tenders@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Svi ostali uvjeti poziva na nadmetanje ostaju nepromijenjeni. Izmjene ili ispravci čine sastavni dio poziva na nadmetanje.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>