<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.9/publication" xmlns:n2016="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.9/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" VERSION="R2.0.9.S03.E01" DOC_ID="427425-2019" EDITION="2019175"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>19-437140-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20200908</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>175</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20190911</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2019/S 175-427425</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:427425-2019:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="RS"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>www.novisad.rs</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71240000">Architectural, engineering and planning services</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20190909</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="3">Regional or local authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="8">Other</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>02A01</HEADING><INITIATOR>02</INITIATOR></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Сърбия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Архитектурни и инженерни услуги по изготвяне на планове и чертежи</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Srbsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Architektonické, technické a plánovací služby</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Arkitekt-, ingeniør- og planlægningsvirksomhed</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Dienstleistungen von Architektur- und Ingenieurbüros sowie planungsbezogene Leistungen</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Σερβία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Υπηρεσίες αρχιτέκτονα, μηχανικού και τεχνικού γραφείου</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Architectural, engineering and planning services</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servicios de arquitectura, ingeniería y planificación</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Arhitektuuri-, insener-tehnilise projekteerimise ja planeerimisteenused</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Arkkitehti-, insinööri- ja suunnittelupalvelut</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Serbie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Services d'architecture, d'ingénierie et de planification</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Seirbia, an t</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Architectural, engineering and planning services</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Srbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Arhitektonske usluge, tehničke usluge i usluge planiranja</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Szerbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Építészeti, mérnöki és tervezési szolgáltatások</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servizi architettonici, di ingegneria e pianificazione</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Serbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Architektūros, inžinerijos ir planavimo paslaugos</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Serbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Arhitektūras, inženiertehniskie un plānošanas pakalpojumi</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>is-Serbja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servizzi dwar l-arkitettura, l-inġinerija u l-ippjanar</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Servië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Dienstverlening op het gebied van architectuur, bouwkunde en planning</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Usługi architektoniczne, inżynieryjne i planowania</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Sérvia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Serviços de arquitectura, engenharia e planeamento</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servicii de arhitectură, de inginerie şi de planificare</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Srbsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Architektonické, inžinierske a plánovacie služby</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Srbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Arhitekturne, inženirske in projektantske storitve</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Novi Sad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Arkitekt-, ingenjörs- och planeringstjänster</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Grad Novi Sad</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN"><LEGAL_BASIS VALUE="32014L0024"/><NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/><CONTRACTING_BODY><ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY><OFFICIALNAME>Grad Novi Sad</OFFICIALNAME><TOWN>Novi Sad</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>21000</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="RS"/><E_MAIL>milijana.radovanovic@uprava.novisad.rs</E_MAIL><n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/><URL_GENERAL>www.novisad.rs</URL_GENERAL></ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY><ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/><CA_TYPE VALUE="REGIONAL_AUTHORITY"/><CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/></CONTRACTING_BODY><OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1"><TITLE><P>Non-Binding Public Call for the Collection of Letters of Interest for Landscaping and Construction at the Mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube Call Code: NJP — 3/19</P></TITLE><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="71240000"/></CPV_MAIN><TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/><SHORT_DESCR><P>The City of Novi Sad invites all interested domestic or foreign legal entities (hereinafter: interested persons) to submit non-binding written offers (hereinafter: letters of Interest) for landscaping and construction at the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube into the Danube. For the purpose of this call, landscaping and construction shall mean the remodeling, adaptation and/or construction of commercial, sporting, cultural, entertainment, tourist, congress, exhibition, marketing, catering and/or business infrastructure at the area of the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal. The landscaping and construction can be done in the area bordered on the east and south by the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal and the Danube river, while the defensive line on the so-called ‘špic’ was made in the form of a quay wall, and an earth embankment was built on the north side of the Danube-Tisza-Danube canal.</P></SHORT_DESCR><NO_LOT_DIVISION/><OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1"><n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/><MAIN_SITE><P>Novi Sad, at the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube into the Danube.</P></MAIN_SITE><SHORT_DESCR><P>For illustrative purposes, the conceptual designs awarded at an appropriate architectural competition for a pedestrian-infrastructure bridge over the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal and a business and catering facility located at the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube could be seen at www.novisad.rs</P><P>The conceptual designs presented are for illustrative purposes only and are not binding on the Interested persons. In other words, the Interested persons are free to propose alternative solutions, which may encompass a completely different concept of landscaping and construction in the area of the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube. For illustrative purposes, the conceptual designs awarded at an appropriate architectural competition for a pedestrian-infrastructure bridge over the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal and a business and catering facility located at the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube are shown below. The conceptual designs presented are for illustrative purposes only and are not binding on the Interested persons. In other words, the Interested persons are free to propose alternative solutions, which may encompass a completely different concept of landscaping and construction in the area of the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube. The letter of interest must contain the following information:</P><P>— general information about the Interested person (business name, registered office, company registration number and VAT identification number),</P><P>— financial offer — the proposed amount of investment in landscaping and construction in the area of the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube,</P><P>— framework business plan,</P><P>— outline conceptual design for the implementation of the investment program (which should include the indicative amount of planned investments, as well as the plan, manner and dynamics, i.e. timeframe for the implementation of the investment program) for landscaping and construction at the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube,</P><P>— planned structure and method of financing (e.g. financing from own resources, loans and/or subsidies, etc.).</P><P>Letters of interest and all supporting documents must be signed by the authorized person of the interested person and submitted no later than 8.11.2019 until 12 o'clock noon, to the clerk's office of the City Administration for General Affairs, Trg slobode 1, Novi Sad. Letters of interest shall be submitted by post or direct submission in 2 copies to the clerk’s office of the City Administration for General Affairs, Trg slobode 1, Novi Sad, while simultaneously sending a copy by email to milijana.radovanovic@uprava.novisad.rs no later than 8.11.2019 until 12 o’clock noon. Letters of interest shall be submitted in a sealed envelope, with the mandatory name and code of this call, with the note ‘Letter of interest for landscaping and construction in the area of the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube, call code NJP — 3/19 (for the City Administration for Construction Land and Investments) — do not open’. The name, address and telephone number of the interested person should be clearly displayed on the back of the envelope. Prior to sending the letter of interest, all interested persons will be given access to relevant documentation after signing the confidentiality statement. The confidential data protection statement form can be downloaded at www.novisad.rs</P><P>The interested person shall submit the statement signed by the authorized person by direct submission to the clerk’s office of the City Administration for General Affairs, Trg slobode 1, Novi Sad, while simultaneously sending a copy by email to milijana.radovanovic@uprava.novisad.rs no later than 9.10.2019 until 12 o’clock noon, in 2 copies. All Interested persons will be allowed to visit the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube into the Danube at their request.</P></SHORT_DESCR><INFO_ADD><P>The abovementioned request can be sent by email to milijana.radovanovic@uprava.novisad.rs with the mandatory name and code of this call. All additional information and questions regarding this call may be obtained by sending an email to milijana.radovanovic@uprava.novisad.rs with the mandatory name and code of this call.</P></INFO_ADD></OBJECT_DESCR><DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2020-06-30</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE></OBJECT_CONTRACT><PROCEDURE><NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/></PROCEDURE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFO><INFO_ADD><P>This call is non-binding in its entirety and is published for market research purposes only and in that sense, it does not oblige the City of Novi Sad to initiate any procedure for landscaping and construction at the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube. The City of Novi Sad reserves the right not to initiate the procedure for landscaping and construction in the area of the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube, as well as to modify and supplement the elements of this non-binding public call and bears no responsibility for any costs or damages that such changes would cause to the interested person or third parties. Following an analysis of the letters of interest received, the competent authorities of the City of Novi Sad may initiate an appropriate procedure for landscaping and construction at the mouth of the Danube-Tisza-Danube Canal into the Danube. The analysis of the letters of interest received will be carried out by a working group formed by the City of Novi Sad. The goal of the City of Novi Sad is to improve the quality of life of the local population by attracting investments and creating new jobs, in this case through the regulation of the Danube-Tisza-Danube mouth into the Danube, access roads, bicycle and pedestrian connections with the green and other free surfaces in this area.</P></INFO_ADD><DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2019-09-09</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFO></F01_2014></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>