<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.8/publication" xmlns:n2016="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.8/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="423140-2019" EDITION="2019174"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>19-423264-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20200829</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>174</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20190910</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2019/S 174-423140</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:423140-2019:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20190830</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Ipa - Bistand til gennemførelse af teknisk bistands- og informationsudvekslingsaktiviteter: Levering af logistiske tjenesteydelser og finansiel forvaltning</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Unterstützung bei der Umsetzung von Tätigkeiten im Zusammenhang mit technischer Hilfe und Informationsaustausch (TAIEX): Logistikdienste und Finanzmanagement</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Assistance for the Implementation of Technical Assistance and Information Exchange (TAIEX) Activities: Provision of Logistical Services and Financial Management</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Asistencia para la ejecución de las actividades de la Oficina de Asistencia Técnica e Intercambio de Información (TAIEX): prestación de servicios logísticos y gestión financiera</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Tuki tekniseen tukeen ja tiedonvaihtoon (TAIEX) liittyvien toimien toteuttamista varten: logististen palvelujen ja varainhoidon toimittaminen</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IAP - Soutien en vue de l'exécution des activités relatives à l’assistance technique et l’échange des informations (TAIEX) : Fourniture de services logistiques et gestion financière</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Παροχή βοήθειας για την εφαρμογή των δραστηριοτήτων τεχνικής βοήθειας και ανταλλαγής πληροφοριών: Παροχή υλικοτεχνικών υπηρεσιών και χρηματοοικονομικής διαχείρισης</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Assistenza per l’esecuzione delle attività di assistenza tecnica e di scambio di informazioni (TAIEX): Prestazione di servizi logistici e gestione finanziaria</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Ondersteuning bij de tenuitvoerlegging van de werkzaamheden inzake technische bijstand en informatie-uitwisseling (TAIEX): verstrekking van logistieke diensten en financieel beheer</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Assistência para a implementação das atividades de Intercâmbio de Informações sobre Assistência Técnica (TAIEX): Prestação de serviços logísticos e gestão financeira</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Söd vid implementering av tekniskt stöd och informationsutbyte (Technical Assistance and Information Exchange - TAIEX): Tillhandahållande av logistiktjänster och ekonomisk förvaltning</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>NPP - Podpora při provádění činností technické pomoci a výměny informací (TAIEX): Poskytování logistických služeb a finanční management</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Abi järgmiste tehnilise abi ja teabevahetuse (TAIEX) tegevuste rakendamisel: logistikateenuste osutamine ja finantsjuhtimine</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Támogatás a „technikai segítségnyújtás és információcsere“ (TAIEX) program tevékenységeinek végrehajtásához: logisztikai szolgáltatások biztosítása és pénzügyi irányítási feladatok megvalósítása</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>PNPP - Pagalba įgyvendinant techninės pagalbos ir informacijos mainų (TAIEX) veiklą: Logistinių paslaugų teikimas ir finansų valdymas</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Atbalsts Tehniskās palīdzības un informācijas apmaiņas instrumenta (TAIEX) darbību īstenošanai – loģistikas pakalpojumu un finanšu pārvaldības nodrošināšana</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>SGħQD - Għajnuna għall-Implimentazzjoni ta' Attivitajiet ta' Għajnuna Teknika u Skambju ta' Informazzjoni (TAIEX): Provvista ta' Servizzi Loġistiċi u Mmaniġġjar Finanzjarju</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Wsparcie we wdrażaniu działań z zakresu pomocy technicznej i wymiany informacji (TAIEX): usługi logistyczne i zarządzanie finansami</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Pomoc pri vykonávaní činností technickej pomoci a výmeny informácií (TAIEX): poskytovanie logistických služieb a finančného riadenia</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Pomoč pri izvajanju dejavnosti tehnične pomoči in izmenjave informacij (TAIEX): Zagotavljanje logističnih storitev in finančnega upravljanja</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Cabhair chun gníomhaíochtaí um chúnamh teicniúil agus faisnéise a chur chun feidhme (TAIEX): Soláthar seirbhísí lóistíochta agus bainistíochta airgeadais</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>ИПП - Съдействие при осъществяването на дейности по техническа помощ и обмен на информация (TAIEX): Предоставяне на логистични услуги и финансови управление</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Asistență pentru punerea în aplicare a activităților de asistență tehnică și schimb de informații (TAIEX): Prestarea de servicii logistice și management financiar</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>IPA - Pomoć aktivnostima provedbe Instrumenta tehničke pomoći i razmjene informacija (TAIEX): Pružanje usluga logistike i financijskog upravljanja</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Unión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan unioni</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Union européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">União Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska unionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Liit</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Az Európai Unió</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Sąjunga</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Savienība</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Unjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Unia Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska únia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska unija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An tAontas Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски съюз</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Uniunea Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska unija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Ipa - Bistand til gennemførelse af teknisk bistands- og informationsudvekslingsaktiviteter: Levering af logistiske tjenesteydelser og finansiel forvaltning</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sted: Globalt</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Forhåndsmeddelelse om tjenesteydelser</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Handlingsprogrammet for teknisk bistand og informationsudveksling (TAIEX) 2018-2020 under den multinationale IPA II-ramme/TAIEX-handlingsprogrammet 2018-2020 under de europæiske naboskabsforanstaltninger/handlingsprogrammet for det tyrkisk-cypriotiske fællesskab/det årlige handlingsprogram for partnerskabsinstrumentet til samarbejde med tredjelande/DEVCO's årlige arbejdsprogram vedrørende koordinering og fremme af oplysningsaktiviteter i forbindelse med udviklingsspørgsmål/teknisk bistand inden for rammerne af EFRU og Samhørighedsfonden/Finansiering af LIFE-delprogrammet for miljø/Arbejdsprogrammet for støtteprogrammet for strukturreformer.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen for og på vegne af modtagerlandene, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarbaseret.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formålet med kontrakten er at støtte gennemførelsen af instrumentet for teknisk bistand og informationsudveksling (TAIEX — Technical Assistance and Information Exchange), der støtter »peer to peer«-samarbejde mellem offentlige myndigheder i EU's medlemsstater og myndigheder i partnerlande. Kontrahentens rolle vil være at udføre instrukser, der udstedes af Europa-Kommissionen, og arrangere logistik, særligt for konferencer, workshopper og ekspertmissioner, PR-materiale, osv. Kontrahenten skal også foretage betalinger i forbindelse med logistiske aktiviteter og eksperthonorarer.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Foreløbig dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>November 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det vejledende maksimumsbudget er 32 500 000 EUR i 2 år, med forbehold for vedtagelsen af de respektive finansieringsafgørelser.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 236/2014 af 11.3.2014 om fælles regler og procedurer for gennemførelse af instrumenterne til finansiering af Unionens optræden udadtil</P><P>— Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 231/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et instrument til førtiltrædelsesbistand (IPA II)</P><P>— Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 232/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et europæisk naboskabsinstrument</P><P>— Rådets forordning (EF) nr. 389/2006 af 27.2.2006 om oprettelse af et instrument for økonomisk støtte til fremme af den økonomiske udvikling af det tyrkisk-cypriotiske samfund og om ændring af forordning (EF) nr. 2667/2000 om Det Europæiske Genopbygningsagentur</P><P>— Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 234/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et partnerskabsinstrument for samarbejde med tredjelande</P><P>— Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 233/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et instrument til finansiering af udviklingssamarbejde for perioden 2014-2020</P><P>— Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 1303/2013 af 17.12.2013 om fælles bestemmelser for Den Europæiske Regionaludviklingsfond, Den Europæiske Socialfond, Samhørighedsfonden, Den Europæiske Landbrugsfond for Udvikling af Landdistrikterne og Den Europæiske Hav- og Fiskerifond og om generelle bestemmelser for Den Europæiske Regionaludviklingsfond, Den Europæiske Socialfond, Samhørighedsfonden og Den Europæiske Hav- og Fiskerifond og om ophævelse af Rådets forordning (EF) nr. 1083/2006 og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 1304/2013 af 17.12.2013 om Den Europæiske Socialfond og om ophævelse af Rådets forordning (EF) nr. 1081/2006</P><P>— Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 1293/2013 af 11.12.2013 om oprettelse af et program for miljø- og klimaindsatsen (Life) og om ophævelse af forordning (EF) nr. 614/2007</P><P>— Europa-Parlamentet og Rådets forordning (EU) 2017/825 af 17.5.2017 om oprettelse af støtteprogrammet for strukturreformer i perioden 2017-2020 og ændring af forordning (EU) nr. 1303/2013 og (EU) nr. 1305/2013.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at efter Det Forenede Kongeriges udtræden af EU vil reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande, gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige, alt afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. Hvis en sådan adgang ikke gives ved retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende på tidspunktet for kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P><P>(1) Angiv venligst enhver specificitet, der kan have indflydelse på reglerne for deltagelse (såsom geografisk eller tematisk eller lang-/kortsigtet).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Bemærkninger:</P><P>Der skal være en periode på mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilsvarende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>Der kan ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: IPA - Unterstützung bei der Umsetzung von Tätigkeiten im Zusammenhang mit technischer Hilfe und Informationsaustausch (TAIEX): Logistikdienste und Finanzmanagement</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Standort: Weltweit</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vorinformation für einen Dienstleistungsauftrag</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aktionsprogramm für technische Hilfe und Informationsaustausch (TAIEX) 2018-2020 im Rahmen des Mehrländer-Rahmenprogramms IPA II/TAIEX 2018-2020 im Rahmen des Europäischen Nachbarschaftsprogramms für Maßnahmen/Aktionsprogramms für das jährliche Aktionsprogramm der türkischen Gemeinschaft Zyperns/Partnerschaftsinstrument für die Zusammenarbeit mit Drittländern/DEVCO im Rahmen des jährlichen Arbeitsprogramms zur Koordinierung und Sensibilisierung in Bezug auf Entwicklungsfragen/EFRE und Kohäsionsfonds für die Verwendung von technischer Hilfe/Finanzierung des Life-Teilprogramms für Umwelt/des Arbeitsprogramms für das unterstützende Programm zur strukturellen Reform.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission, im Namen und für Rechnung der begünstigten Länder, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Auf Honorarbasis.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zweck des Auftrags ist die Unterstützung bei der Umsetzung des Instruments für technische Hilfe und Informationsaustausch (TAIEX), mit dem die Zusammenarbeit zwischen den Behörden der EU-Mitgliedstaaten und den Behörden in Partnerländern durch Peer-to-Peer-Zusammenarbeit unterstützt wird. Aufgabe des Auftragnehmers ist die Ausführung von Anweisungen der Europäischen Kommission und die Einführung von Logistik, insbesondere für Konferenzen, Workshops, Expertenmissionen, Werbematerialien usw. Der Auftragnehmer führt auch Zahlungen im Zusammenhang mit logistischen Tätigkeiten und Expertengebühren durch.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagtes Budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Geplanter Zeitpunkt für die Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>November 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zusätzliche Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Das veranschlagte maximale Budget beträgt 32 500 000 EUR für 2 Jahre, vorbehaltlich der Annahme der entsprechenden Finanzierungsbeschlüsse.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Verordnung (EU) Nr. 236/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Vorschriften und Verfahren für die Anwendung der Instrumente der Union für die Finanzierung des auswärtigen Handelns,</P><P>— Verordnung (EU) Nr. 231/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Instruments für Heranführungshilfe (IPA II),</P><P>— Verordnung (EU) Nr. 232/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Europäischen Nachbarschaftsinstruments,</P><P>— Verordnung (EG) Nr. 389/2006 des Rates vom 27.2.2006 zur Schaffung eines finanziellen Stützungsinstruments zur Förderung der wirtschaftlichen Entwicklung der türkischen Gemeinschaft Zyperns und zur Änderung der Verordnung (EG) Nr. 2667/2000 über die Europäische Agentur für Wiederaufbau,</P><P>— Verordnung (EU) Nr. 234/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Partnerschaftsinstruments für die Zusammenarbeit mit Drittstaaten,</P><P>— Verordnung (EU) Nr. 233/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Finanzierungsinstruments für die Entwicklungszusammenarbeit für den Zeitraum 2014-2020,</P><P>— Verordnung (EU) Nr. 1303/2013 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 17.12.2013 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Bestimmungen über den Europäischen Fonds für regionale Entwicklung, den Europäischen Sozialfonds, den Kohäsionsfonds, den Europäischen Landwirtschaftsfonds für die Entwicklung des ländlichen Raums und den Europäischen Meeres- und Fischereifonds sowie zur Festlegung allgemeiner Bestimmungen zum Europäischen Fonds für regionale Entwicklung, zum Europäischen Sozialfonds, zum Kohäsionsfonds und zum Europäischen Meeres- und Fischereifonds und zur Aufhebung der Verordnung des Rates (EG) Nr. 1083/2006; Verordnung (EU) Nr. 1304/2013 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 17.12.2013 über den Europäischen Sozialfonds und zur Aufhebung der Verordnung (EG) des Rates Nr. 1081/2006,</P><P>— Verordnung (EU) Nr. 1293/2013 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.12.2013 über die Einrichtung eines Programms für Umwelt- und Klimapolitik (LIFE) und zur Aufhebung der Verordnung (EG) Nr. 614/2007,</P><P>— Verordnung (EU) 2017/825 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 17.5.2017 über die Aufstellung des Unterstützungsprogramms für strukturelle Reformen für den Zeitraum 2017 bis 2020 und zur Änderung der Verordnungen (EU) Nr. 1303/2013 und (EU) Nr. 1305/2013.</P><P>Es gilt zu beachten, dass für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU in Abhängigkeit des Ausgangs der Verhandlungen die Bestimmungen über den Zugang zu Beschaffungsverfahren der EU für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer gelten werden. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P><P>(1) Bitte geben Sie alle Besonderheiten an, die sich auf die Regeln für die Teilnahme auswirken könnten (z. B. geographisch oder thematisch oder kurz-/mittelfristig).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Hinweise:</P><P>Es muss ein Zeitraum von mindestens 30 Kalendertagen zwischen der Veröffentlichung der Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der entsprechenden Auftragsbekanntmachung liegen.</P><P>Derzeit ist von der Einreichung von Bewerbungen oder Anfragen bezüglich weiterer Auskünfte abzusehen.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: IPA - Assistance for the Implementation of Technical Assistance and Information Exchange (TAIEX) Activities: Provision of Logistical Services and Financial Management</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Location: Globally</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Service Prior Information Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme title</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Technical Assistance and Information Exchange (TAIEX) action programme 2018–2020 under the IPA II multi-country envelope/TAIEX action programme 2018–2020 under the European Neighbourhood-wide measures/action programme for the Turkish Cypriot community/Partnership Instrument annual action programme for cooperation with third countries/DEVCO Annual Work Programme relating to coordination and promotion of awareness on development issues/ERDF and Cohesion Fund for the use of technical assistance/Financing of the Life sub-programme for environment/Work programme for the Structural Reform Support Programme.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting Authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, represented by the European Commission on behalf of and for the account of the beneficiaries, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, BELGIUM</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fee-based.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The purpose of the contract is to support the implementation of the Technical Assistance and Information Exchange (TAIEX) instrument which supports peer to peer cooperation among public authorities of the EU Member States with authorities in partner countries. The role of the contractor will be to execute instructions issued by the European Commission and put in place logistics particularly for conferences, workshops expert missions, promotion materials, etc. The contractor will also carry out payments related to logistical activities and expert fees.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intended timing of publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>November 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The indicative maximum budget is 32 500 000 EUR over 2 years, subject to the adoption of the respective financing decisions.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Regulation (EU) No 236/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 laying down common rules and procedures for the implementation of the Union's instruments for financing external action,</P><P>— Regulation (EU) No 231/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing an Instrument for Pre-accession Assistance (IPA II),</P><P>— Regulation (EU) No 232/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing a European Neighbourhood Instrument,</P><P>— Council Regulation (EC) No 389/2006 of 27.2.2006 establishing an instrument of financial support for encouraging the economic development of the Turkish Cypriot community and amending Council Regulation(EC) No 2667/2000 on the European Agency for Reconstruction,</P><P>— Regulation (EU) No 234/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing a Partnership Instrument for cooperation with third countries,</P><P>— Regulation (EU) No 233/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing a financing instrument for development cooperation for the period 2014-2020,</P><P>— Regulation (EU) No 1303/2013 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 17.12.2013 laying down common provisions on the European Regional Development Fund, the European Social Fund, the Cohesion Fund, the European Agricultural Fund for Rural Development and the European Maritime and Fisheries Fund and laying down general provisions on the European Regional Development Fund, the European Social Fund, the Cohesion Fund and the European Maritime and Fisheries Fund and repealing Council Regulation (EC) No 1083/2006; Regulation (EU) No 1304/2013 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 17.12.2013 on the European Social Fund and repealing Council Regulation (EC) No 1081/2006,</P><P>— Regulation (EU) No 1293/2013 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.12.2013 on the establishment of a Programme for the Environment and Climate Action (LIFE) and repealing Regulation (EC) No 614/2007,</P><P>— Regulation (EU) 2017/825 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 17.5.2017 on the establishment of the structural reform support programme for the period 2017 to 2020 and amending Regulations (EU) No 1303/2013 and (EU) No 1305/2013.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom's withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of negotiations. In case such access is not provided by legal provisions in force at the time of contract award, candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom could be rejected from the procurement procedure.</P><P>(1) Please state any specificity that might have an impact on rules on participation (such as geographic or thematic or long/short term).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Remarks:</P><P>There must be a minimum period of 30 calendar days between the publication of this prior information notice and the publication of the corresponding contract notice.</P><P>No applications or requests for information should be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: IPA - Asistencia para la ejecución de las actividades de la Oficina de Asistencia Técnica e Intercambio de Información (TAIEX): prestación de servicios logísticos y gestión financiera</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lugar: todo el mundo</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anuncio de información previa de contrato de servicios</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de acción 2018-2020 de la Oficina de Asistencia Técnica e Intercambio de Información (TAIEX) en el marco de la dotación plurinacional del IPA II/programa de acción 2018-2020 de la TAIEX en el marco de las medidas a nivel de la Vecindad Europea/programa de acción para la comunidad turcochipriota/programa de acción anual del Instrumento de Colaboración para la cooperación con terceros países/Programa de trabajo anual de la DEVCO relativo a la coordinación y promoción de concienciación sobre cuestiones de desarrollo/FEDER y Fondo de Cohesión para la utilización de asistencia técnica/Financiación del subprograma Life en pos del medio ambiente/Programa de trabajo del programa de apoyo a las reformas estructurales.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Unión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada por la Comisión Europea, en nombre y por cuenta de los beneficiarios, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarios.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El objetivo del contrato es apoyar la ejecución del instrumento de la Oficina de Asistencia Técnica e Intercambio de Información (TAIEX) que respalda la cooperación entre pares entre las autoridades públicas de los Estados miembros de la Unión Europea y las autoridades de los países socios. El rol del contratista será ejecutar las instrucciones impartidas por la Comisión Europea e implementar la logística necesaria, particularmente para conferencias, misiones de expertos, talleres, material promocional, etc. El contratista además realizará los pagos relacionados con las actividades logísticas y los honorarios de los expertos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha prevista de publicación del anuncio de licitación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Noviembre de 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información adicional</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El presupuesto máximo indicativo es de 32 500 000 EUR durante 2 años, sujeto a la adopción de las decisiones de financiación respectivas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 236/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establecen normas y procedimientos de ejecución comunes de los instrumentos de la Unión para la financiación de la acción exterior.</P><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 231/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Ayuda Preadhesión (IAP II).</P><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 232/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento Europeo de Vecindad.</P><P>— Reglamento (CE) n.º 389/2006 del Consejo, de 27.2.2006, por el que se crea un instrumento de ayuda económica para impulsar el desarrollo económico de la comunidad turcochipriota y por el que se modifica el Reglamento (CE) n.º 2667/2000 relativo a la Agencia Europea de Reconstrucción.</P><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 234/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Colaboración para la cooperación con terceros países.</P><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 233/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Financiación de la Cooperación al Desarrollo para el período 2014-2020.</P><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 1303/2013 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 17.12.2013, por el que se establecen disposiciones comunes relativas al Fondo Europeo de Desarrollo Regional, al Fondo Social Europeo, al Fondo de Cohesión, al Fondo Europeo Agrícola de Desarrollo Rural y al Fondo Europeo Marítimo y de la Pesca, y por el que se establecen disposiciones generales relativas al Fondo Europeo de Desarrollo Regional, al Fondo Social Europeo, al Fondo de Cohesión y al Fondo Europeo Marítimo y de la Pesca, y se deroga el Reglamento (CE) no 1083/2006 del Consejo; Reglamento (UE) no 1304/2013 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 17.12.2013, relativo al Fondo Social Europeo y por el que se deroga el Reglamento (CE) no 1081/2006 del Consejo.</P><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 1293/2013 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.12.2013, relativo al establecimiento de un Programa de Medio Ambiente y Acción por el Clima (LIFE) y por el que se deroga el Reglamento (CE) n.º 614/2007.</P><P>— Reglamento (UE) n.º 2017/825 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 17.5.2017, relativo al establecimiento del programa de apoyo a las reformas estructurales para el período comprendido entre 2017 y 2020, y los reglamentos (UE) n.º 1303/2013 y (UE) n.º 1305/2013 que lo modifican.</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que tras la salida del Reino Unido de la Unión Europea, las normas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación pública de la Unión Europea de los operadores económicos establecidos en terceros países se aplicarán a candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido en función del resultado de las negociaciones. En caso de que dicho acceso no se prevea en las disposiciones legales en vigor, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido podrán ser excluidos del procedimiento de contratación.</P><P>(1) Mencione cualquier aspecto específico que pudiera repercutir en las normas de participación (por ejemplo, aspectos geográficos, temáticos o de corto o largo plazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Observaciones:</P><P>Deberán pasar al menos 30 días naturales desde la publicación de este anuncio de información previa hasta la publicación del correspondiente anuncio de licitación.</P><P>De momento, no deberán enviarse solicitudes ni peticiones de información complementaria.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: IPA - Tuki tekniseen tukeen ja tiedonvaihtoon (TAIEX) liittyvien toimien toteuttamista varten: logististen palvelujen ja varainhoidon toimittaminen</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sijainti: maailmanlaajuisesti</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Palveluja koskeva ennakkotietoilmoitus</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Liittymistä valmistelevaan tukivälineeseen (IPA II) kuuluvien useita maita koskevan kokonaisrahoituksen alainen teknistä tukea ja tiedonvaihtoa (Technical Assistance and Information Exchange – TAIEX) koskeva toimintaohjelma vuosille 2018–2020 / Euroopan naapurimaiden laajuisten toimenpiteiden alainen TAIEX-toimintaohjelma vuosille 2018–2020 / Kyproksen turkkilaista yhteisöä koskeva toimintaohjelma / kumppanuusvälineen vuotuinen toimintaohjelma kolmansien maiden kanssa tehtävää yhteistyötä varten / kansainvälisen yhteistyön ja kehitysasioiden PO:n kehityskysymyksien koordinointia ja niitä koskevan tietoisuuden lisäämistä koskeva vuotuinen työohjelma / Euroopan aluekehitysrahasto (EAKR) ja koheesiorahasto teknisen tuen käyttöä varten / ympäristöä koskevan Life-alaohjelman rahoittaminen / rakenneuudistuksen tukiohjelmaa koskeva työohjelma.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan unioni</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio, edunsaajien puolesta, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Palkkiopohjainen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sopimuksen tarkoituksena on tukea teknistä tukea ja tiedonvaihtoa (TAIEX) koskevan välineen toteuttamista. Välineellä tuetaan EU:n jäsenvaltioiden julkisten viranomaisten ja kumppanimaiden viranomaisten välistä vertaisyhteistyötä. Sopimusosapuolen tehtävänä on toimia Euroopan komission antamien ohjeiden mukaisesti ja huolehtia logistisista järjestelyistä erityisesti konferensseja, asiantuntijatehtäviä koskevia työpajoja, mainosmateriaaleja jne. varten. Lisäksi sopimusosapuoli suorittaa logistisiin toimiin liittyvät maksut ja asiantuntijamaksut.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen ennakoitu julkaisemisajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marraskuu 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Alustava enimmäisbudjetti 2 vuoden ajalle on 32 500 000 EUR, ja sitä voidaan muuttaa annettujen rahoitusta koskevien päätösten mukaisesti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 236/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, unionin ulkoisen toiminnan rahoitusvälineiden täytäntöönpanoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöistä ja menettelyistä,</P><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 231/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, liittymistä valmistelevan tukivälineen (IPA II) perustamisesta,</P><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 232/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, Euroopan naapuruusvälineen perustamisesta,</P><P>— neuvoston asetus (EY) N:o 389/2006, annettu 27.2.2006, rahoitusvälineen perustamisesta Kyproksen turkkilaisen yhteisön taloudellisen kehityksen edistämiseksi ja Euroopan jälleenrakennusvirastosta annetun asetuksen (EY) N:o 2667/2000 muuttamisesta,</P><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 234/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, kumppanuusvälineen perustamisesta kolmansien maiden kanssa tehtävää yhteistyötä varten,</P><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 233/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, kehitysyhteistyön rahoitusvälineen perustamisesta kaudelle 2014–2020,</P><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 1303/2013, annettu 17.12.2013, Euroopan aluekehitysrahastoa, Euroopan sosiaalirahastoa, koheesiorahastoa, Euroopan maaseudun kehittämisen maatalousrahastoa ja Euroopan meri- ja kalatalousrahastoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöksistä sekä Euroopan aluekehitysrahastoa, Euroopan sosiaalirahastoa, koheesiorahastoa ja Euroopan meri- ja kalatalousrahastoa koskevista yleisistä säännöksistä sekä neuvoston asetuksen (EY) N:o 1083/2006 kumoamisesta; Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 1304/2013, annettu 17.12.2013 , Euroopan sosiaalirahastosta ja neuvoston asetuksen (EY) N:o 1081/2006 kumoamisesta,</P><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 1293/2013, annettu 11.12.2013, ympäristön ja ilmastotoimien ohjelman (Life) perustamisesta ja asetuksen (EY) N:o 614/2007 kumoamisesta,</P><P>— Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) 2017/825, annettu 17.5.2017, rakenneuudistusten tukiohjelman perustamisesta kaudeksi 2017–2020 ja asetusten (EU) N:o 1303/2013 ja (EU) N:o 1305/2013 muuttamisesta.</P><P>On syytä ottaa huomioon, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen lopputuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P><P>(1) Mainitse seikat (kuten esimerkiksi maantieteellinen sijainti tai aihe tai pitkä/lyhyt kesto), joilla voi olla vaikutusta osallistumissääntöihin.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Huom.</P><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja vastaavan hankintailmoituksen julkaisemisen välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai lisätietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IAP - Soutien en vue de l'exécution des activités relatives à l’assistance technique et l’échange des informations (TAIEX) : Fourniture de services logistiques et gestion financière</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lieu d'exécution : Dans le monde entier</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avis de préinformation relatif à un marché de services</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intitulé du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programme d'action 2018-2020 en faveur de l'assistance technique et de l'échange d'informations (TAIEX) au titre de l'enveloppe plurinationale dans le cadre de l'IAP II/programme d'action 2018-2020 TAIEX au titre des mesures prises dans le cadre de la politique européenne de voisinage/programme d'action en faveur de la communauté chypriote turque/programme d'action annuel dans le cadre de l'instrument de partenariat pour la coopération avec les pays tiers/programme de travail annuel de DEVCO relatif à la coordination et à la promotion de la sensibilisation sur les questions de développement/FEDER et Fonds de cohésion pour le recours à l’assistance technique/financement du sous-programme Life pour l’environnement/programme de travail relatif au programme d’appui à la reforme structurelle.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Union européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, représentée par la Commission européenne, agissant au nom et pour le compte des bénéficiaires, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgique</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du contrat</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>À prix unitaires.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L’objectif du marché est de soutenir l'exécution de l’instrument d’assistance technique et d’échange d’informations (TAIEX) qui soutient la coopération d'égal à égal entre les autorités publiques des Etats membres de l’UE et les autorités des pays partenaires. Le rôle du contractant sera d’exécuter les instructions données par la Commission européenne et de mettre en place la logistique, notamment pour les conférences, les ateliers, les missions d’experts, le matériel promotionnel, etc. Le contractant effectuera également les paiements relatifs aux activités logistiques et des honoraires des experts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date de publication prévue de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Novembre 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Renseignements complémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le budget maximal indicatif s’élève à 32 500 000 EUR sur 2 ans, sous réserve d’adoption des décisions de financement respectives.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Règlement (UE) n° 236/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 fixant des règles communes et des procédures de mise en œuvre des instruments de l'Union pour le financement de l'action extérieure,</P><P>— règlement (UE) n° 231/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument d'aide de préadhésion (IAP II),</P><P>— règlement (UE) no 232/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument européen de voisinage,</P><P>— règlement (CE) du Conseil n° 389/2006 du 27.2.2006 portant sur la création d'un instrument de soutien financier visant à encourager le développement économique de la communauté chypriote turque et modifiant le règlement (CE) du Conseil n° 2667/2000 relatif à l'Agence européenne pour la reconstruction,</P><P>— règlement (UE) n° 234/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument de partenariat pour la coopération avec les pays tiers,</P><P>— règlement (UE) no 233/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument de financement de la coopération au développement pour la période 2014-2020,</P><P>— règlement (UE) no 1303/2013 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 17.12.2013 fixant des dispositions communes relatives au Fonds européen de développement régional, au Fonds social européen, au Fonds de cohésion, au Fonds européen agricole pour le développement rural et au Fonds européen pour les affaires maritimes et la pêche, fixant des dispositions générales applicables au Fonds européen de développement régional, au Fonds social européen, au Fonds de cohésion et au Fonds européen pour les affaires maritimes et la pêche, et abrogeant le règlement (CE) du Conseil no 1083/2006; règlement (UE) no 1304/2013 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 17.12.2013 relatif au Fonds social européen et abrogeant le règlement (CE) du Conseil no 1081/2006,</P><P>— règlement (UE) n° 1293/2013 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.12.2013 relatif à l'établissement d'un programme pour l'environnement et l'action pour le climat (LIFE) et abrogeant le règlement (CE) n° 614/2007,</P><P>— règlement (UE) no 2017/825 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 17.5.2017 relatif à l’établissement du programme de soutien à la réforme structurelle pour la période 2017-2020 et modifiant les règlements (UE) no 1303/2013 et (UE) no 1305/2013.</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de passation des marchés de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, en fonction du résultat des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure de passation des marchés.</P><P>(1) Veuillez indiquer toute spécificité susceptible d’avoir un impact sur les règles en matière de participation (par exemple géographique ou thématique ou à court/long terme).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Remarques :</P><P>Un délai minimal de 30 jours calendaires doit être respecté entre la publication du présent avis de préinformation et celle de l'avis de marché correspondant.</P><P>Aucune candidature ni demande de renseignements complémentaires ne sera envoyée à ce stade de la procédure.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: IPA - Παροχή βοήθειας για την εφαρμογή των δραστηριοτήτων τεχνικής βοήθειας και ανταλλαγής πληροφοριών: Παροχή υλικοτεχνικών υπηρεσιών και χρηματοοικονομικής διαχείρισης</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Τόπος: Ανά τον κόσμο</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Προκαταρκτική ανακοίνωση για υπηρεσίες</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τίτλος προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Πρόγραμμα δράσης τεχνικής βοήθειας και ανταλλαγής πληροφοριών (TAIEX - Technical Assistance and Information Exchange) 2018–2020, στο πλαίσιο του πολυκρατικού κονδυλίου του ΜΠΒ II/Πρόγραμμα δράσης TAIEX 2018–2020 στο πλαίσιο του προγράμματος δράσης/των μέτρων σε όλη την περιφέρεια της Ευρωπαϊκής Γειτονίας για την τουρκοκυπριακή κοινότητα/Ετήσιο πρόγραμμα δράσης του Μέσου Εταιρικής Σχέσης για τη συνεργασία με τρίτες χώρες/DEVCO ετήσιο πρόγραμμα εργασίας σχετικά με τον συντονισμό και την προώθηση της ευαισθητοποίησης σε θέματα ανάπτυξης/ΕΤΠΑ και Ταμείο Συνοχής για τη χρήση της τεχνικής βοήθειας/Χρηματοδότηση του υπο-προγράμματος Life για το περιβάλλον/Πρόγραμμα εργασίας για το πρόγραμμα υποστήριξης διαρθρωτικής μεταρρύθμισης.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, εκ μέρους και για λογαριασμό των δικαιούχων, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τύπος σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Βάσει αμοιβής.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Σκοπός της σύμβασης είναι η υποστήριξη της εφαρμογής του μέσου τεχνικής βοήθειας και ανταλλαγής πληροφοριών (TAIEX) το οποίο υποστηρίζει την ομότιμη συνεργασία μεταξύ των δημοσίων αρχών των κρατών μελών της ΕΕ και των αρχών των χωρών εταίρων. Ο ρόλος του αναδόχου θα είναι να εκτελεί τις οδηγίες που θα δίνει η Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή και να εφαρμόσει υλικοτεχνική υποστήριξη ιδίως για συνέδρια, εργαστήρια, αποστολές εμπειρογνωμόνων, προωθητικά υλικά, κ.λπ. Ο ανάδοχος θα πραγματοποιήσει πληρωμές σχετικά με τις υλικοτεχνικές δραστηριότητες και τις αμοιβές των εμπειρογνωμόνων.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Νοέμβριος 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ο ενδεικτικός ανώτατος προϋπολογισμός είναι 32 500 000 EUR για περίοδο 2 ετών και υπόκειται στη λήψη των αντίστοιχων χρηματοοικονομικών αποφάσεων.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 236/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου της 11.3.2014 για τον καθορισμό κοινών κανόνων και διαδικασιών για την εφαρμογή των μηχανισμών χρηματοδότησης της εξωτερικής δράσης της Ένωσης,</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 231/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τη θέσπιση Μηχανισμού Προενταξιακής Βοήθειας (ΜΠΒ ΙΙ),</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 232/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τη θέσπιση Ευρωπαϊκού Μηχανισμού Γειτονίας,</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΚ) αριθ. 389/2006 του Συμβουλίου, της 27.2.2006, για τη σύσταση μέσου χρηματοδοτικής στήριξης για την προαγωγή της οικονομικής ανάπτυξης της τουρκοκυπριακής κοινότητας και για τροποποίηση του κανονισμού (ΕΚ) αριθ. 2667/2000 σχετικά με την Ευρωπαϊκή Υπηρεσία Ανασυγκρότησης,</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 234/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, σχετικά με τη θέσπιση Μέσου Εταιρικής Σχέσης για τη συνεργασία με τρίτες χώρες,</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 233/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, περί μηχανισμού χρηματοδότησης της αναπτυξιακής συνεργασίας την περίοδο 2014-2020,</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 1303/2013 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 17.12.2013, περί καθορισμού κοινών διατάξεων για το Ευρωπαϊκό Ταμείο Περιφερειακής Ανάπτυξης, το Ευρωπαϊκό Κοινωνικό Ταμείο, το Ταμείο Συνοχής, το Ευρωπαϊκό Γεωργικό Ταμείο Αγροτικής Ανάπτυξης και το Ευρωπαϊκό Ταμείο Θάλασσας και Αλιείας και περί καθορισμού γενικών διατάξεων για το Ευρωπαϊκό Ταμείο Περιφερειακής Ανάπτυξης, το Ευρωπαϊκό Κοινωνικό Ταμείο, το Ταμείο Συνοχής και το Ευρωπαϊκό Ταμείο Θάλασσας και Αλιείας και για την κατάργηση του κανονισμού (ΕΚ) αριθ. 1083/2006, κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 1304/2013 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 17.12.2013, για το Ευρωπαϊκό Κοινωνικό Ταμείο και την κατάργηση του κανονισμού (ΕΚ) αριθ. 1081/2006 του Συμβουλίου,</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 1293/2013 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.12.2013, σχετικά με τη θέσπιση Προγράμματος για το Περιβάλλον και τη Δράση για το Κλίμα (LIFE) και για την κατάργηση του κανονισμού (ΕΚ) αριθ. 614/2007,</P><P>— Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 2017/825 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 17.5.2017, για τη θέσπιση του προγράμματος στήριξης διαρθρωτικών μεταρρυθμίσεων για την περίοδο 2017 έως 2020 και την τροποποίηση των κανονισμών (ΕΕ) αριθ. 1303/2013 και (ΕΕ) αριθ. 1305/2013.</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες διαγωνισμού της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν παρέχεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά τον χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο θα μπορούσαν να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία διαγωνισμού.</P><P>1) Παρακαλείσθε να αναφέρετε οποιαδήποτε ιδιαιτερότητα που ενδέχεται να έχει αντίκτυπο στους κανόνες συμμετοχής (όπως γεωγραφική ή θεματική ή σε μακροπρόθεσμο/βραχυπρόθεσμο επίπεδο).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Παρατηρήσεις:</P><P>Μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης θα πρέπει να παρεμβληθεί χρονικό διάστημα τουλάχιστον 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών.</P><P>Κατά το παρόν στάδιο δεν πρέπει να αποστέλλονται υποψηφιότητες ή αιτήματα για παροχή πληροφοριών.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IPA - Assistenza per l’esecuzione delle attività di assistenza tecnica e di scambio di informazioni (TAIEX): Prestazione di servizi logistici e gestione finanziaria</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ubicazione: a livello mondiale</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviso di preinformazione relativo a servizi</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titolo del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma di azione Assistenza tecnica e scambio d'informazioni (TAIEX) per il 2018–2020 nell'ambito della dotazione destinata a più paesi IPA II/programma d'azione TAIEX per il 2018–2020 nell'ambito del programma di azione/misure della politica europea di vicinato per la comunità turco-cipriota/programma d'azione annuale dello strumento di partenariato per la cooperazione con paesi terzi/DEVCO Programma annuale di lavoro relativo al coordinamento e alla promozione della consapevolezza sulle questioni relative allo sviluppo/FESR e Fondo di coesione per l'uso dell'assistenza tecnica/Finanziamento del sottoprogramma di LIFE per l'ambiente/Programma di lavoro per il programma di sostegno alle riforme strutturali.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ente appaltante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea, in nome e per conto dei paesi beneficiari, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contratto in base a tariffa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lo scopo del contratto consiste nel supportare l'attuazione dello strumento di assistenza tecnica e di scambio di informazioni (TAIEX) che sostiene la cooperazione tra pari, tra le autorità pubbliche degli Stati membri dell'UE e le autorità dei paesi partner. Il ruolo del contraente consisterà nell’esecuzione delle istruzioni impartite dalla Commissione europea e nell’attuazione della logistica in particolare per conferenze, missioni di esperti in seminari, materiali promozionali, ecc. Il contraente effettuerà anche pagamenti relativi alle attività logistiche e agli onorari degli esperti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Importo indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara d'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Novembre 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il bilancio massimo indicativo è pari a 32 500 000 EUR in un periodo di 2 anni, soggetto all'adozione delle rispettive decisioni di finanziamento.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 236/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che stabilisce norme e procedure comuni per l'attuazione degli strumenti per il finanziamento dell'azione esterna dell'Unione,</P><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 231/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento di assistenza preadesione (IPA II),</P><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 232/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento europeo di vicinato,</P><P>— Regolamento (CE) n. 389/2006 del Consiglio, del 27.2.2006, che istituisce uno strumento di sostegno finanziario per favorire lo sviluppo economico della comunità turco-cipriota e che modifica il regolamento (CE) n. 2667/2000 del Consiglio relativo all'agenzia europea per la ricostruzione,</P><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 234/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento di partenariato per la cooperazione con i paesi terzi,</P><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 233/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento per il finanziamento della cooperazione allo sviluppo per il periodo 2014-2020,</P><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 1303/2013 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, del 17.12.2013, recante disposizioni comuni sul Fondo europeo di sviluppo regionale, sul Fondo sociale europeo, sul Fondo di coesione, sul Fondo europeo agricolo per lo sviluppo rurale e sul Fondo europeo per gli affari marittimi e la pesca e disposizioni generali sul Fondo europeo di sviluppo regionale, sul Fondo sociale europeo, sul Fondo di coesione e sul Fondo europeo per gli affari marittimi e la pesca, e che abroga il regolamento (CE) n. 1083/2006 del Consiglio; regolamento (UE) n. 1304/2013, del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, del 17.12.2013, relativo al Fondo sociale europeo e che abroga il regolamento (CE) n. 1081/2006 del Consiglio,</P><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 1293/2013 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.12.2013, sull'istituzione di un programma per l'ambiente e l'azione per il clima (LIFE) e che abroga il regolamento (CE) n. 614/2007,</P><P>— Regolamento (UE) n. 2017/825 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'17.5.2017, sull'istituzione di un programma di sostegno alle riforme istituzionali per il periodo 2017-2020, e che modifica i Regolamenti (UE) n. 1303/2013 e n. 1305/2013.</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o agli offerenti provenienti dal Regno Unito verranno applicate le regole di accesso alle procedure di appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti in paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito delle negoziazioni. Nel caso in cui tale accesso non sia previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche vigenti al momento dell'aggiudicazione del contratto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito potranno essere esclusi dalla procedura d'appalto.</P><P>(1) Indicare qualsiasi specificità che possa avere un impatto sulle regole di partecipazione (come ad esempio geografica o tematica o a lungo/breve termine).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Osservazioni:</P><P>Dovrà intercorrere un periodo minimo di 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione dell'avviso di preinformazione e quella del corrispondente bando di gara d'appalto.</P><P>Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di ulteriori informazioni durante questa fase della procedura.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: IPA - Ondersteuning bij de tenuitvoerlegging van de werkzaamheden inzake technische bijstand en informatie-uitwisseling (TAIEX): verstrekking van logistieke diensten en financieel beheer</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locatie: wereldwijd</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vooraankondiging voor diensten</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titel van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Actieprogramma 2018-2020 voor technische bijstand en informatie-uitwisseling (TAIEX) in het kader van de IPA II-meerlandenbegroting/TAIEX-actieprogramma 2018-2020 in het kader van maatregelen voor het gehele Europese nabuurschap/actieprogramma voor de Turks-Cypriotische gemeenschap/jaarlijks actieprogramma van het partnerschapsinstrument voor samenwerking met derde landen/jaarlijks werkprogramma van DEVCO met betrekking tot de coördinatie en bevordering van bewustmaking inzake ontwikkelingskwesties/het gebruik van technische bijstand in het kader van het EFRO en van het Cohesiefonds/ financiering van het subprogramma LIFE inzake milieu/werkprogramma in het kader van het steunprogramma voor structurele hervormingen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie, ten behoeve en voor rekening van de begunstigden, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Opdracht op basis van vergoeding.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het doel van de opdracht is het ondersteunen van de tenuitvoerlegging van het TAIEX-instrument (technische bijstand en informatie-uitwisseling) dat de collegiale samenwerking ondersteunt tussen overheidsinstanties van de EU-lidstaten en autoriteiten in partnerlanden. De contractant moet de instructies van de Europese Commissie uitvoeren en de logistiek beheren, met name voor conferenties, workshops, deskundigheidsmissies, promotiemateriaal, enz. De contractant voert ook betalingen uit met betrekking tot logistieke activiteiten en vergoedingen van deskundigen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum voor bekendmaking van de aankondiging van opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>November 2019.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De indicatieve begroting bedraagt maximaal 32 500 000 EUR voor een looptijd van 2 jaar, afhankelijk van de goedkeuring van de respectieve financieringsbesluiten.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis (1):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Verordening (EU) nr. 236/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van gemeenschappelijke voorschriften en procedures voor de tenuitvoerlegging van de instrumenten van de Unie ter financiering van extern optreden,</P><P>— Verordening (EU) nr. 231/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van een instrument voor pretoetredingssteun (IPA II),</P><P>— Verordening (EU) nr. 232/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van een Europees nabuurschapsinstrument,</P><P>— Verordening (EG) nr. 389/2006 van de Raad van 27.2.2006 tot instelling van een instrument voor financiële steun ter bevordering van de economische ontwikkeling van de Turks-Cypriotische gemeenschap en tot wijziging van Verordening (EG) nr. 2667/2000 betreffende het Europees Bureau voor wederopbouw,</P><P>— Verordening (EU) nr. 234/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van een partnerschapsinstrument voor samenwerking met derde landen,</P><P>— Verordening (EG) nr. 233/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van een financieringsinstrument voor ontwikkelingssamenwerking voor de periode 2014-2020,</P><P>— Verordening (EU) nr. 1303/2013 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 17.12.2013 houdende gemeenschappelijke bepalingen inzake het Europees Fonds voor regionale ontwikkeling, het Europees Sociaal Fonds, het Cohesiefonds, het Europees Landbouwfonds voor plattelandsontwikkeling en het Europees Fonds voor maritieme zaken en visserij en algemene bepalingen inzake het Europees Fonds voor regionale ontwikkeling, het Europees Sociaal Fonds, het Cohesiefonds en het Europees Fonds voor maritieme zaken en visserij, en tot intrekking van Verordening (EG) nr. 1083/2006 van de Raad; Verordening (EU) nr. 1304/2013 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 17.12.2013 betreffende het Europees Sociaal Fonds en tot intrekking van Verordening (EG) nr. 1081/2006 van de Raad,</P><P>— Verordening (EU) nr. 1293/2013 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.12.2013 inzake de vaststelling van een programma voor het milieu en klimaatactie (LIFE) en tot intrekking van Verordening (EG) nr. 614/2007,</P><P>— Verordening (EU) nr. 2017/825 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 17.5.2017 inzake de vaststelling van het steunprogramma voor structurele hervormingen voor de periode 2017-2020, tot wijziging van Verordening (EU) nr. 1303/2013 en (EU) nr. 1305/2013.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat, na de uitstap van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van het resultaat van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die gevestigd zijn in derde landen van toepassing zullen zijn op gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P><P>(1) Vermeld elke specificiteit die een effect kan hebben op de deelnameregels (zoals geografische of thematische specificiteiten op korte of lange termijn).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Opmerkingen:</P><P>Er moet een minimumtermijn van 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van deze vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de overeenstemmende aankondiging van een opdracht.</P><P>In dit stadium mogen er geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: IPA - Assistência para a implementação das atividades de Intercâmbio de Informações sobre Assistência Técnica (TAIEX): Prestação de serviços logísticos e gestão financeira</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Localização: Globalmente</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anúncio de pré-informação de serviços</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de ação de Intercâmbio de Informações e Assistência Técnica (TAIEX) 2018-2020 ao abrigo da dotação multinacional do IPA II/programa de ação TAIEX 2018-2020 ao abrigo das medidas ao nível da Vizinhança Europeia/programa de ação para a comunidade cipriota turca/programa de ação anual do Instrumento de Parceria para a cooperação com países terceiros/Programa de trabalho anual da DEVCO relativo à coordenação e promoção da conscientização sobre questões de desenvolvimento/FEDER e Fundo de Coesão para a utilização da assistência técnica/Financiamento do subprograma Vida para o ambiente/Programa de trabalho para o programa de apoio à reforma estrutural.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>União Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada pela Comissão Europeia, em nome e por conta dos beneficiários, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Baseado em honorários.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O objetivo do contrato é apoiar a implementação do instrumento de Intercâmbio de Informações sobre Assistência Técnica (TAIEX), que apoia a cooperação entre pares entre autoridades públicas dos Estados-Membros da UE e autoridades de países parceiros. O papel do contratante será executar as instruções emitidas pela Comissão Europeia e implementar a logística, especialmente para conferências, missões de peritos em oficinas, materiais de promoção etc. O contratante também realizará pagamentos relacionados com atividades logísticas e honorários de peritos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Novembro de 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Outras informações</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O orçamento máximo indicativo é de 32 500 000 EUR durante 2 anos, sujeito à adoção das respetivas decisões de financiamento.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Regulamento (UE) n.º 236/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que estabelece regras e procedimentos comuns para a execução dos instrumentos da União de financiamento da ação externa,</P><P>— Regulamento (UE) n.º 231/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que cria um instrumento de assistência de pré-adesão (IPA II),</P><P>— Regulamento (UE) n.º 232/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que cria um instrumento europeu de vizinhança,</P><P>— Regulamento (CE) n.º 389/2006 do Conselho, de 27.2.2006, que estabelece um instrumento de apoio financeiro para a promoção do desenvolvimento económico da comunidade cipriota turca e que altera o Regulamento (CE) n.º 2667/2000 do Conselho relativo à Agência Europeia de Reconstrução,</P><P>— Regulamento (UE) n.º 234/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que cria um Instrumento de Parceria para a cooperação com países terceiros,</P><P>— Regulamento (UE) n.º 233/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que institui um instrumento de financiamento da cooperação para o desenvolvimento para o período de 2014-2020,</P><P>— Regulamento (UE) n.º 1303/2013 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 17.12.2013, que estabelece disposições comuns relativas ao Fundo Europeu de Desenvolvimento Regional, ao Fundo Social Europeu, ao Fundo de Coesão, ao Fundo Europeu Agrícola de Desenvolvimento Rural e ao Fundo Europeu dos Assuntos Marítimos e das Pescas, que estabelece disposições gerais relativas ao Fundo Europeu de Desenvolvimento Regional, ao Fundo Social Europeu, ao Fundo de Coesão e ao Fundo Europeu dos Assuntos Marítimos e das Pescas, e que revoga o Regulamento (CE) n.º 1083/2006 do Conselho; Regulamento (UE) n.º 1304/2013 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 17.12.2013, relativo ao Fundo Social Europeu e que revoga o Regulamento (CE) n.º 1081/2006 do Conselho,</P><P>— Regulamento (UE) n.º 1293/2013 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.12.2013, que estabelece um Programa para o Ambiente e a Ação Climática (LIFE) e que revoga o Regulamento (CE) n.º 614/2007,</P><P>— Regulamento (UE) 2017/825 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 17.5.2017, que estabelece o programa de apoio às reformas estruturais para o período de 2017 a 2020 e altera os Regulamentos (UE) n.º 1303/2013 e (UE) n.º 1305/2013.</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros aplicar-se-ão aos candidatos ou proponentes provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do concurso.</P><P>(1) Indique qualquer especificidade que possa ter impacto sobre as regras de participação (tais como geográficas ou temáticas ou a longo/curto prazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Observações:</P><P>Deve ser respeitado um período mínimo de 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de pré-informação e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente.</P><P>Não devem ser enviadas candidaturas ou efetuados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: IPA - Söd vid implementering av tekniskt stöd och informationsutbyte (Technical Assistance and Information Exchange - TAIEX): Tillhandahållande av logistiktjänster och ekonomisk förvaltning</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Plats: Hela världen</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Förhandsmeddelande om tjänster</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmets namn</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Handlingsprogram 2018–2020 för tekniskt bistånd och informationsutbyte (Taiex) inom ramen för IPA II:s program för flera länder/Taiex handlingsprogram 2018–2020 inom ramen för åtgärder inom det europeiska grannskapet/handlingsprogrammet för den turkcypriotiska befolkningsgruppen/partnerskapsinstrumentets årliga handlingsprogram för samarbete med tredjeländer/Eruf och Sammanhållningsfonden för användning av tekniskt stöd/finansiering av Life-delprogrammet för miljö/arbetsprogram för stödprogrammet för strukturreformer.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska unionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen, till förmån för och på uppdrag av mottagarländerna, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Typ av kontrakt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Arvodesbaserat.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Syftet med avtalet är att stödja implementeringen av instrumentet för teknisk stöd och informationsutbyte (TAIEX) som stöder kollegialt samarbete mellan offentliga myndigheter i EU:s medlemsstater och myndigheter i partnerländer. Uppdragstagarens roll kommer att vara att utföra instruktioner som utfärdats av Europeiska kommissionen och ordna med logistik särskilt för konferenser, seminarier expertuppdrag, marknadsföringsmaterial, etc. Uppdragstagaren kommer också att genomföra betalningar rörande logistisk verksamhet och arvode till experterna.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminär budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerad tidsplan för publicering av meddelandet om upphandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>November 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Den preliminära högsta budgeten är 32 500 000 EUR under 2 år, under förutsättning att respektive finansieringsbeslut antas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 236/2014 av den 11 mars 2014 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser och förfaranden för genomförandet av unionens instrument för finansiering av yttre åtgärder,</P><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 231/2014 av den 11 mars 2014 om inrättande av ett instrument för stöd inför anslutningen (IPA II),</P><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 232/2014 av den 11 mars 2014 om inrättande av ett europeiskt grannskapsinstrument,</P><P>– Rådets förordning (EG) nr 389/2006 av den 27 februari 2006 om införande av en stödordning för att stimulera den ekonomiska utvecklingen inom den turkcypriotiska befolkningsgruppen och om ändring av förordning (EG) nr 2667/2000 om den Europeiska byrån för återuppbyggnad,</P><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 234/2014 av den 11 mars 2014 om inrättande av ett partnerskapsinstrument för samarbete med tredjeländer,</P><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 233/2014 av den 11 mars 2014 om upprättande av ett finansieringsinstrument för utvecklingssamarbete för perioden 2014–2020,</P><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 1303/2013 av den 17 december 2013 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser för Europeiska regionala utvecklingsfonden, den Europeiska socialfonden, Sammanhållningsfonden,den Europeiska jordbruksfonden för landsbygdsutveckling och den Europeiska havs- och fiskerifonden, om fastställande av allmänna bestämmelser för den Europeiska regionala utvecklingsfonden, den Europeiska socialfonden, Sammanhållningsfonden och den Europeiska havs- och fiskerifonden samt om upphävande av rådets förordning (EG) nr 1083/2006,</P><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 1293/2013 av den 11 december 2013 om inrättandet av ett program för miljö och klimatpolitik (Life) samt om upphävande av förordning (EG) nr 614/2007,</P><P>– Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) 2017/825 av den 17 maj 2017 om inrättande av stödprogrammet för strukturreformer för perioden 2017–2020 och om ändring av förordningarna (EU) nr 1303/2013 och (EU) nr 1305/2013.</P><P>Observera att efter det Förenade kungarikets utträde ur EU kommer reglerna om tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer etablerade i tredjeländer att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från det Förenade kungariket, beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte fastslås av rättsliga bestämmelser som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från det Förenade kungariket komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P><P>(1) Ange om det finns något som kan påverka reglerna för deltagande (såsom geografiskt läge, tema eller tid på lång eller kort sikt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Anmärkningar:</P><P>En period på minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publikationen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publikationen av motsvarande meddelande om upphandling.</P><P>Inga ansökningar eller förfrågningar om information ska skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: NPP - Podpora při provádění činností technické pomoci a výměny informací (TAIEX): Poskytování logistických služeb a finanční management</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalita: Celosvětově</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oznámení předběžných informací o službách</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Akční program „Technická pomoc a výměna informací“ (TAIEX) na léta 2018 – 2020 v rámci balíku NPP II zahrnujícího několik zemí / akční program TAIEX 2018–2020 v rámci opatření týkajících se celého prostoru Evropského sousedství / akční program pro společenství kyperských Turků/ / roční akční program nástroje partnerství pro spolupráci s třetími zeměmi / roční akční program DEVCO týkající se koordinace a propagace informovanosti o záležitostech rozvoje / ERDF a Fond soudržnosti pro využívání technické pomoci / financování dílčího programu LIFE pro životní prostředí / pracovní program pro program na podporu strukturálních reforem.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastoupená Evropskou komisí jménem a ve prospěch příjemců, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Placená.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cílem zakázky je podpora provádění nástroje technické pomoci a výměny informací (TAIEX), který podporuje vzájemně rovnocennou spolupráci mezi veřejnými orgány členských států EU s orgány v partnerských zemích. Role zhotovitele bude splnit pokyny vydané Evropskou komisí a zavést logistiku především pro konference, workshopy, odborné mise, propagační materiály atd. Zhotovitel bude rovněž provádět platby související s logistickými činnostmi a poplatky za znalce.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlené datum zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>listopad 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Další informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Orientační maximální rozpočet je 32 500 000 EUR po dobu 2 let za podmínky přijetí příslušných rozhodnutí o financování.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 236/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se stanoví společná pravidla a postupy pro provádění nástrojů Unie pro financování vnější činnosti,</P><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 231/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zřizuje nástroj předvstupní pomoci (NPP II),</P><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 232/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zřizuje evropský nástroj sousedství,</P><P>– nařízení Rady (ES) č. 389/2006 ze dne 27. února 2006, kterým se vytváří nástroj finanční podpory na posílení hospodářského rozvoje tureckého společenství na Kypru a mění nařízení (ES) č. 2667/2000 o Evropské agentuře pro obnovu,</P><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 234/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zakládá nástroj partnerství pro spolupráci se třetími zeměmi,</P><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 233/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zřizuje finanční nástroj pro rozvojovou spolupráci pro období 2014-2020,</P><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 1303/2013 ze dne 17. prosince 2013, o společných ustanoveních o Evropském fondu pro regionální rozvoj, Evropském sociálním fondu, Fondu soudržnosti, Evropském zemědělském fondu pro rozvoj venkova a Evropském námořním a rybářském fondu, o obecných ustanoveních o Evropském fondu pro regionální rozvoj, Evropském sociálním fondu, Fondu soudržnosti a Evropském námořním a rybářském fondu a o zrušení nařízení Rady (ES) č. 1083/2006; nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 1304/2013 ze dne 17.12.2013 o Evropském sociálním fondu a zrušení nařízení Rady (ES) č. 1081/2006,</P><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 1293/2013 ze dne 11. prosince 2013 o zřízení programu pro životní prostředí a oblast klimatu (LIFE) a o zrušení nařízení (ES) č. 614/2007,</P><P>– nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 2017/825 ze dne 17. května 2017 o zřízení programu na podporu strukturálních reforem na období 2017-2020, kterým se mění nařízení (EU) č. 1303/2013 a (EU) č. 1305/2013.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P><P>(1) Uveďte prosím jakoukoli specifičnost, která by mohla mít dopad na pravidla účasti (např. zeměpisnou, tematickou nebo dlouhodobou/krátkodobou).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Poznámky:</P><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním odpovídajícího oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout minimálně 30 kalendářních dnů.</P><P>V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: IPA - Abi järgmiste tehnilise abi ja teabevahetuse (TAIEX) tegevuste rakendamisel: logistikateenuste osutamine ja finantsjuhtimine</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Asukoht: kogu maailm</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Teenuste eelteade</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi pealkiri</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tehnilise abi ja teabevahetuse (TAIEX) tegevusprogramm aastateks 2018–2020 IPA II mitme riigi paketi raames / TAIEX tegevusprogramm aastateks 2018–2020 kogu Euroopa naabruskonna meetmete raames / tegevusprogramm Küprose türgi kogukonna jaoks / partnerluse rahastamisvahendi aastane tegevusprogramm kolmandate riikidega koostöö tegemiseks / DEVCO iga-aastane tööprogramm seoses koordineerimise ja teadlikkuse suurendamisega arenguvaldkonnas / ERDF ja Ühtekuuluvusfond tehnilise abi kasutamiseks / LIFE’i keskkonna alaprogrammi rahastamine / struktuurireformi tugiprogrammi tööprogramm.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Liit</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon, abisaajate eest ja nimel, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tasupõhine.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lepingu eesmärk on toetada tehnilise abi ja teabevahetuse (TAIEX) rahastamisvahendi rakendamist, mis toetab ELi liikmesriikide riigiasutuste vastastikust koostööd partnerriikide asutustega. Töövõtja roll on Euroopa Komisjoni väljastatud juhiste täitmine ja eelkõige konverentside, töötubade, eksperdimissioonide, reklaammaterjalide jms logistika paikapanemine. Lisaks teostab töövõtja logistiliste tegevustega seotud makseid ja eksperditasusid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Soovituslik eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise kavandatud ajastus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>November 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Soovituslik maksimaalne eelarve on 32 500 000 EUR 2 aasta kohta ja see sõltub vastavate rahastamisotsuste vastuvõtmisest.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 236/2014, milles sätestatakse liidu välistegevuse rahastamisvahendite rakendamise ühised eeskirjad ja menetlused;</P><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 231/2014, millega luuakse ühinemiseelse abi rahastamisvahend (IPA II);</P><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 232/2014, millega luuakse Euroopa naabruspoliitika rahastamisvahend;</P><P>– nõukogu 27.2.2006 määrus (EÜ) nr 389/2006, millega luuakse rahalise toetuse programm Küprose türgi kogukonna majandusarengu soodustamiseks ja millega muudetakse nõukogu määrust (EÜ) nr 2667/2000 Euroopa Ülesehitusameti kohta;</P><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 234/2014, millega luuakse partnerluse rahastamisvahend koostööks kolmandate riikidega,</P><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 233/2014, millega luuakse arengukoostöö rahastamisvahend aastateks 2014–2020;</P><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 17.12.2013 määrus (EL) nr 1303/2013, millega kehtestatakse ühissätted Euroopa Regionaalarengu Fondile, Euroopa Sotsiaalfondile, Ühtekuuluvusfondile, Maaelu Arengu Euroopa Põllumajandusfondile ning Euroopa Merendus- ja Kalandusfondile; kehtestatakse üldsätted Euroopa Regionaalarengu Fondile, Euroopa Sotsiaalfondile, Ühtekuuluvusfondile ning Euroopa Merendus- ja Kalandusfondile; tunnistatakse kehtetuks Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu määrus (EÜ) nr 1083/2006, Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 17.12.2013 määrus (EL) nr 1304/2013 Euroopa Sotsiaalfondi kohta ning nõukogu määrus (EÜ) nr 1081/2006;</P><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.12.2013 määrus (EL) nr 1293/2013, millega luuakse keskkonna- ja kliimameetmete programm (LIFE) ning tunnistatakse kehtetuks määrus (EÜ) nr 614/2007;</P><P>– Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 17.5.2017 määrus (EL) nr 2017/825, millega luuakse struktuurireformi tugiprogramm ajavahemikuks 2017–2020 ning muudetakse määrusi (EL) nr 1303/2013 ja (EL) nr 1305/2013.</P><P>Palun võtke teadmiseks, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemustest kohaldatakse pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivaid ELi hankemenetlustele juurepääsu käsitlevaid eeskirju. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole tagatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätete kaudu, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P><P>(1) Märkige kõik erijooned, mis võivad mõjutada osalemise tingimusi (näiteks geograafilised erijooned, valdkond, lühike või pikk tähtaeg).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Märkused</P><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva.</P><P>Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: IPA - Támogatás a „technikai segítségnyújtás és információcsere“ (TAIEX) program tevékenységeinek végrehajtásához: logisztikai szolgáltatások biztosítása és pénzügyi irányítási feladatok megvalósítása</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Helyszín: világszerte</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Szolgáltatásra irányuló előzetes tájékoztató hirdetmény</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program címe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018–2020 közötti technikai segítségnyújtás és információcsere (TAIEX) cselekvési program a több országra kiterjedő IPA II. cselekvési program keretében/2018–2020. közötti TAIEX cselekvési program az Európai Szomszédságpolitikai országokat érintő intézkedések/a ciprusi török közösséget érintő cselekvési program keretében/Partnerségi Eszköz – harmadik országokkal folytatott együttműködésre irányuló éves cselekvési program/DEVCO – a fejlesztési kérdésekkel kapcsolatos figyelemfelhívás koordinációjára és előmozdítására irányuló éves munkaprogram/Európai Regionális Fejlesztési Alap (ERFA) és Kohéziós Alap a technikai segítségnyújtás felhasználásához/a LIFE környezetvédelmi alprogramjának finanszírozása/a strukturálisreform-támogató program munkaprogramja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Az Európai Unió</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, amelyet az Európai Bizottság képvisel, a kedvezményezett országok nevében és megbízásából, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüsszel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Díjalapú.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A szerződés célja a technikai segítségnyújtás és információcsere (TAIEX) eszköz végrehajtásának támogatása, amely támogatja az EU-tagállamok állami hatóságai és a partnerországok hatóságai közötti partneri együttműködést. A nyertes ajánlattevő szerepe az Európai Bizottság által kiadott utasítások végrehajtása, valamint logisztika kialakítása lesz különösen konferenciák, workshopok, szakértői kiküldetések, promóciós anyagok tekintetében. A nyertes ajánlattevő feladata a logisztikai tevékenységekkel és szakértői díjakkal kapcsolatos kifizetések teljesítése is.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlati felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2019. november</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A 2 évre szóló maximális költségvetési előirányzat 32 500 000 EUR, ami a vonatkozó finanszírozási határozatok elfogadásától függ.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Az Európai Parlament és Tanács 236/2014/EU rendelete (2014. március 11.) a külső tevékenységek finanszírozására vonatkozó uniós eszközök végrehajtására vonatkozó közös szabályok és eljárások megállapításáról,</P><P>— az Európai Parlament és Tanács 231/2014/EU rendelete (2014. március 11.) az IPA II Előcsatlakozási Támogatási Eszköz létrehozásáról,</P><P>— az Európai Szomszédsági és Partnerségi Támogatási Eszköz létrehozásáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű, 232/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet,</P><P>— a ciprusi török közösség gazdasági fejlődésének ösztönzését elősegítő pénzügyi támogatási keret létrehozásáról és az Európai Újjáépítési Ügynökségről szóló 2667/2000/EK tanácsi rendelet módosításáról szóló 389/2006/EK tanácsi rendelet (2006. február 27.),</P><P>— a harmadik országokkal folytatott együttműködésre irányuló Partnerségi Eszköz létrehozásáról szóló 234/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet (2014. március 11.),</P><P>— a 2014-2020-ra szóló fejlesztési együttműködés finanszírozási eszközének létrehozásáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 233/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet,</P><P>— az Európai Regionális Fejlesztési Alapra, az Európai Szociális Alapra, a Kohéziós Alapra, az Európai Mezőgazdasági Vidékfejlesztési Alapra és az Európai Tengerügyi és Halászati Alapra vonatkozó közös rendelkezések megállapításáról, az Európai Regionális Fejlesztési Alapra, az Európai Szociális Alapra és a Kohéziós Alapra és az Európai Tengerügyi és Halászati Alapra vonatkozó általános rendelkezések megállapításáról és az 1083/2006/EK tanácsi rendelet hatályon kívül helyezéséről szóló, 17.12.2013 keltezésű 1303/2013/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet; az Európai Szociális Alapról és az 1081/2006/EK tanácsi rendelet hatályon kívül helyezéséről szóló, 17.12.2013 keltezésű, 1304/2013/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet,</P><P>— a környezetvédelmi és éghajlat-politikai program (LIFE) létrehozásáról és a 614/2007/EK rendelet hatályon kívül helyezéséről szóló, 11.12.2013 keltezésű 1293/2013/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet,</P><P>— az Európai Parlament és a Tanács (EU) 2017/825 rendelete (2017. május 17.) a strukturálisreform-támogató program 2017–2020-as időszakra vonatkozó létrehozásáról, valamint az 1303/2013/EU és az 1305/2013/EU rendelet módosításáról.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplőire érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben az ilyen eljárásokban való részvételről nem rendelkezik a szerződés odaítélésének időpontjában hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságban székhellyel rendelkező jelentkezőket, illetve ajánlattevőket kizárhatják a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P><P>(1) Kérjük, jelezzen bármely olyan sajátosságot, amely hatással lehet a részvételi szabályokra (például földrajzi, tematikai vagy hosszú/rövid távú sajátosság).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Megjegyzések:</P><P>Legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie a jelen előzetes összesített hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között.</P><P>Ezen időszak alatt jelentkezések benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: PNPP - Pagalba įgyvendinant techninės pagalbos ir informacijos mainų (TAIEX) veiklą: Logistinių paslaugų teikimas ir finansų valdymas</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta: Visame pasaulyje</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Išankstinis informacinis skelbimas apie paslaugas</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribotas konkursas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018–2020 m. Techninės pagalbos ir informacijos mainų veiksmų programa (TAIEX) pagal PNPP II daugiašalį paketą / 2018–2020 m. TAIEX veiksmų programa pagal priemones Europos kaimynystės mastu / turkų kilmės kipriečių bendruomenės veiksmų programą / partnerystės priemonės metinė veiksmų programa, skirta bendradarbiauti su trečiosiomis šalimis / Tarptautinio bendradarbiavimo ir vystymosi GD metinė darbo programa, susijusi su informuotumo, susijusio su plėtros klausimais, koordinavimu ir skatinimu / ERPF ir Sanglaudos fondas, skirti techninei pagalbai teikti / Aplinkos ir klimato politikos šalutinės programos finansavimas / struktūrinės reformos paramos programos darbinė programa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Sąjunga</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos, paramą gaunančių šalių vardu ir jų naudai, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Briuselis</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mokama.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sutarties tikslas yra pagalba įgyvendinant techninės pagalbos ir informacijos mainų (TAIEX) veiklos priemonę, kuri remia tarpusavio bendradarbiavimą tarp ES valstybių narių valdžios institucijų su šalių partnerių valdžios institucijomis. Rangovas turės vykdyti Europos Komisijos instrukcijas ir spręsti logistikos klausimus, ypač konferencijoms, praktiniams seminarams, ekspertų misijoms, tvarkyti reklaminę medžiagą ir kt. Rangovas taip pat atliks mokėjimus, susijusius su logistine veikla ir ekspertų užmokesčiu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatomas biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatoma skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2019 m. lapkričio mėn.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Preliminarus didžiausias biudžetas – 32 500 000 EUR per 2 metus, jei bus priimti atitinkami sprendimai dėl finansavimo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 236/2014, kuriuo nustatomos bendros Sąjungos išorės veiksmų finansavimo priemonių įgyvendinimo taisyklės ir procedūros,</P><P>— 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 231/2014, kuriuo nustatoma Pasirengimo narystei paramos priemonė (PNPP II);</P><P>— 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 232/2014, kuriuo sukuriama Europos kaimynystės priemonė;</P><P>— 27.2.2006 Tarybos reglamentas (EB) Nr. 389/2006, nustatantis finansinės paramos priemonę Kipro turkų bendruomenės ekonominei plėtrai skatinti, ir iš dalies keičiantis Tarybos Reglamentą (EB) Nr. 2667/2000 dėl Europos rekonstrukcijos agentūros;</P><P>— 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 234/2014, kuriuo nustatoma bendradarbiavimo su trečiosiomis šalimis partnerystės priemonė;</P><P>— 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 233/2014, kuriuo nustatoma vystomojo bendradarbiavimo finansavimo priemonė 2014–2020 m. laikotarpiui.</P><P>— 17.12.2013 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 1303/2013, kuriuo nustatomos Europos regioninės plėtros fondui, Europos socialiniam fondui, Sanglaudos fondui, Europos žemės ūkio fondui kaimo plėtrai ir Europos jūros reikalų ir žuvininkystės fondui bendros nuostatos ir Europos regioninės plėtros fondui, Europos socialiniam fondui, Sanglaudos fondui ir Europos jūros reikalų ir žuvininkystės fondui taikytinos bendrosios nuostatos ir panaikinamas Tarybos reglamentas (EB) Nr. 1083/2006; 17.12.2013 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 1304/2013 dėl Europos socialinio fondo, kuriuo panaikinamas Tarybos reglamentas (EB) Nr. 1081/2006;</P><P>— 11.12.2013 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 1293/2013 dėl aplinkos ir klimato politikos programos (LIFE) įsteigimo ir kuriuo panaikinamas Reglamentas (EB) Nr. 614/2007;</P><P>— 17.5.2017 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) 2017/825 dėl 2017–2020 m. struktūrinių reformų rėmimo programos sudarymo, kuriuo iš dalies keičiami reglamentai (ES) Nr. 1303/2013 ir (ES) Nr. 1305/2013.</P><P>Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad, Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsikūrusių trečiosiose šalyse, prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams ar konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės, priklausomai nuo derybų rezultato. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P><P>1) Nurodykite bet kokias aplinkybes, galinčias turėti įtakos dalyvavimo taisyklėms (pvz., geografines ar temines, ilgalaikes ar trumpalaikes).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Pastabos:</P><P>Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo iki atitinkamo skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo turi praeiti mažiausiai 30 kalendorinių dienų.</P><P>Šiuo etapu negalima siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: IPA - Atbalsts Tehniskās palīdzības un informācijas apmaiņas instrumenta (TAIEX) darbību īstenošanai – loģistikas pakalpojumu un finanšu pārvaldības nodrošināšana</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta: visa pasaule</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Iepriekšējs informatīvs paziņojums par pakalpojumu līgumu</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tehniskās palīdzības un informācijas apmaiņas instrumenta (TAIEX) rīcības programma 2018.–2020. gadam IPA II daudzvalstu finansējuma ietvaros / TAIEX rīcības programma 2018.–2020. gadam Eiropas kaimiņreģiona mēroga pasākumu ietvaros / rīcības programma Kipras turku kopienai / Partnerības instrumenta ikgadējā rīcības programma sadarbībai ar trešām valstīm / DEVCO ikgadējā darba programma par informētības par attīstības jautājumiem koordināciju un veicināšanu / ERAF un Kohēzijas fonds tehniskās palīdzības sniegšanai / LIFE apakšprogrammas videi finansēšana / Darba programma Strukturālo reformu atbalsta programmas vajadzībām</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Savienība</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ko saņēmēju vārdā un interesēs pārstāv Eiropas Komisija, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brisele</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līgums, kura pamatā ir samaksa par pakalpojumiem</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līguma mērķis ir atbalstīt Tehniskās palīdzības un informācijas apmaiņas instrumenta (TAIEX) īstenošanu, ar kuru tiek atbalstīta savstarpēja sadarbība starp ES dalībvalstu iestādēm un iestādēm partnervalstīs. Darbuzņēmēja uzdevums būs īstenot Eiropas Komisijas izdotās instrukcijas un veikt ar loģistiku saistītus pasākumus, proti, konferenču, darbsemināru, ekspertu uzdevumu, reklāmas materiālu utt. vajadzībām. Darbuzņēmējs arī veiks maksājumus saistībā ar loģistikas pasākumiem un ekspertu izmaksām.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma par līgumu paredzamais publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2019. gada novembris</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Paredzamais maksimālais budžets uz 2 gadiem ir 32 500 000 EUR, kas ir atkarīgs no attiecīgo finansēšanas lēmumu pieņemšanas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 236/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus un procedūras, lai īstenotu Savienības instrumentus ārējās darbības finansēšanai</P><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 231/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido Pirmspievienošanās palīdzības instrumentu (IPA II)</P><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 232/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido Eiropas kaimiņattiecību instrumentu</P><P>— Padomes Regula (EK) Nr. 389/2006 (2006. gada 27. februāris), ar ko izveido finansiāla atbalsta instrumentu, lai veicinātu Kipras turku kopienas ekonomisko attīstību, un ar ko groza Padomes Regulu (EK) Nr. 2667/2000 par Eiropas Rekonstrukcijas aģentūru</P><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 234/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido Partnerības instrumentu sadarbībai ar trešām valstīm</P><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 233/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido finanšu instrumentu sadarbībai attīstības jomā 2014.–2020. gadam</P><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 1303/2013 (2013. gada 17. decembris), ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus par Eiropas Reģionālās attīstības fondu, Eiropas Sociālo fondu, Kohēzijas fondu, Eiropas Lauksaimniecības fondu lauku attīstībai un Eiropas Jūrlietu un zivsaimniecības fondu un vispārīgus noteikumus par Eiropas Reģionālās attīstības fondu, Eiropas Sociālo fondu, Kohēzijas fondu un Eiropas Jūrlietu un zivsaimniecības fondu un atceļ Padomes Regulu (EK) Nr. 1083/2006; Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 1304/2013 (2013. gada 17. decembris) par Eiropas Sociālo fondu un ar ko atceļ Padomes Regulu (EK) Nr. 1081/2006</P><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 1293/2013 (2013. gada 11. decembris) par vides un klimata pasākumu programmas (LIFE) izveidi, un ar ko atceļ Regulu (EK) Nr. 614/2007</P><P>— Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) 2017/825 (2017. gada 17. maijs), ar ko laikposmam no 2017. gada līdz 2020. gadam izveido Strukturālo reformu atbalsta programmu un groza Regulas (ES) Nr. 1303/2013 un (ES) Nr. 1305/2013</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem un pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti vai pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P><P>(1) Lūdzam norādīt visus specifiskos iemeslus (piemēram, ģeogrāfiskus, tematiskus, īstermiņa vai ilgtermiņa), kas var ietekmēt dalības noteikumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Piezīmes</P><P>Starp šī iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: SGħQD - Għajnuna għall-Implimentazzjoni ta' Attivitajiet ta' Għajnuna Teknika u Skambju ta' Informazzjoni (TAIEX): Provvista ta' Servizzi Loġistiċi u Mmaniġġjar Finanzjarju</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Il-post: Madwar id-dinja</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviż ta' Tagħrif minn Qabel dwar Servizz</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-titlu tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-programm ta' azzjoni għall-Għajnuna Teknika u l-Iskambju ta' Tagħrif (TAIEX) bejn l-2018 u l-2020 fil-qafas tal-envelopp ta' diversi pajjiżi tal-IPA II/il-programm ta' azzjoni tat-TAIEX mill-2018 sal-2020 skont il-miżuri mferrxa mal-Inħawi tal-Madwar Ewropej/il-programm ta' azzjoni għall-komunità Torka Ċiprijotta/il-programm ta' azzjoni annwali tal-Istrument tas-Sħubija għall-kooperazzjoni ma' pajjiżi terzi/il-Programm ta' Ħidma Annwali DEVCO marbut mal-koordinazzjoni u l-promozzjoni tal-għarfien dwar kwistjonijiet ta' żvilupp/il-FEŻR u l-Fond ta' Koeżjoni għall-użu tal-għajnuna teknika/l-Iffinanzjar tas-subprogramm Life għall-ambjent/il-Programm ta' ħidma għall-Programm ta' Appoġġ għar-Riforma Strutturali.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-Awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L-Unjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea, f'isem u għall-benefiċjarji, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussell</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bil-ħlas ta' miżata.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-iskop tal-kuntratt hu li jappoġġja l-implimentazzjoni tal-istrument ta' Għajnuna Teknika u Skambju ta' Informazzjoni (TAIEX) li jappoġġa l-kooperazzjoni bejn il-pari fost l-awtoritajiet pubbliċi tal-Istati Membri tal-UE ma' awtoritajiet f'pajjiżi sħab. Ir-rwol tal-kuntrattur se jkun li jwettaq istruzzjonijiet maħruġa mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea u jimplimenta loġistika b'mod partikolari għal konferenzi, sessjonijiet ta' ħidma, missjonijiet ta' esperti, materjali promozzjonali, eċċ. Il-kuntrattur se jwettaq ukoll pagamenti marbuta ma' attivitajiet loġistiċi u miżati ta' esperti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Iż-żmien maħsub għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż dwar kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Novembru 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-baġit massimu indikattiv huwa ta' 32 500 000 EUR għal sentejn (2), skont l-adozzjoni tad-deċiżjonijiet ta' ffinanzjar rispettivi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 236/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi regoli u proċeduri komuni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-istrumenti tal-Unjoni għall-finanzjament tal-azzjoni esterna,</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 231/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi Strument għall-Assistenza ta' Qabel l-Adeżjoni (IPA II),</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 232/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi Strument Ewropew tal-Viċinat,</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (KE) Nru 389/2006 tas-27 ta' Frar 2006 li jistabbilixxi strument ta' sostenn finanzjarju għall-inkoraġġiment tal-iżvilupp ekonomiku tal-komunità Turko-Ċiprijotta u li jemenda r-Regolament tal-Kunsill (KE) Nru 2667/2000 dwar l-Aġenzija Ewropea għar-Rikostruzzjoni,</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 234/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi Strument ta' Sħubija għal kooperazzjoni ma' pajjiżi terzi,</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 233/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi strument ta' finanzjament tal-kooperazzjoni għall-iżvilupp għall-perjodu 2014-2020,</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 1303/2013 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tas-17 ta' Diċembru 2013 li jistabbilixxi dispożizzjonijiet komuni dwar il-Fond Ewropew għall-Iżvilupp Reġjonali, il-Fond Soċjali Ewropew, il-Fond ta' Koeżjoni, il-Fond Agrikolu Ewropew għall-Iżvilupp Rurali u l-Fond Marittimu u tas-Sajd Ewropew u li jistabbilixxi d-dispożizzjonijiet ġenerali dwar il-Fond Ewropew għall-Iżvilupp Reġjonali, il-Fond Soċjali Ewropew, il-Fond ta' Koeżjoni u l-Fond Ewropew għall-Affarijiet Marittimi u s-Sajd u li jħassar ir-Regolament tal-Kunsill (KE) Nru 1083/2006; ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 1304/2013 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsil tas-17 ta' Diċembru 2013 dwar il-Fond Soċjali Ewropew u li jħassar ir-Regolament tal-Kunsill (KE) Nru 1081/2006,</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 1293/2013 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Diċembru 2013 dwar l-istabbiliment ta' Programm għall-Ambjent u l-Azzjoni Klimatika (LIFE) u li jħassar ir-Regolament (KE) Nru 614/2007,</P><P>— Ir-Regolament (UE) 2017/825 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tas-17 ta' Mejju 2017 dwar l-istabbiliment ta' Programm ta' Appoġġ għal Riformi Strutturali għall-perijodu mill-2017 sal-2020 u li jemenda r-Regolamenti (UE) Nru 1303/2013 u (UE) Nru 1305/2013.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri tal-ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess mhux ipprovdut minn dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fil-ħin tal-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jiġu mwarrba mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P><P>(1) Jekk jogħġbok niżżel kwalunkwe speċifiċità li jista' jkollha impatt fuq ir-regoli għas-sehem (bħal dik ġeografika jew tematika jew fuq żmien qasir/fit-tul).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Kummenti:</P><P>Irid ikun hemm perijodu minimu ta' 30 jum kalendarju bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż dwar kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu.</P><P>M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: IPA - Wsparcie we wdrażaniu działań z zakresu pomocy technicznej i wymiany informacji (TAIEX): usługi logistyczne i zarządzanie finansami</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalizacja: cały świat</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Wstępne ogłoszenie informacyjne dotyczące zamówienia na usługi</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program działania 2018–2020 instrumentu pomocy technicznej i wymiany informacji (TAIEX) w ramach puli dla kilku krajów IPA II / program działania TAIEX 2018–2020 w ramach środków dla całego obszaru objętego europejską polityką sąsiedztwa / program działania na rzecz tureckiej wspólnoty cypryjskiej / roczny program działania Instrumentu Partnerstwa dla współpracy z państwami trzecimi / roczny program działania Dyrekcji Generalnej ds. Współpracy Międzynarodowej i Rozwoju w (DEVCO) w związku z koordynacją i zwiększaniem świadomości w kwestiach dotyczących rozwoju / EFRR i Fundusz Spójności na rzecz wykorzystania pomocy technicznej / Finansowanie programu szczegółowego w dziedzinie środowiska w ramach programu Life / Program prac na rzecz Programu wspierania reform strukturalnych.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unia Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską, w imieniu i na rzecz beneficjentów, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruksela</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Według stawek jednostkowych.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Celem zamówienia jest pomoc we wdrażaniu instrumentu pomocy technicznej i wymiany informacji (TAIEX), który wspiera partnerską współpracę organów publicznych państw członkowskich UE z organami w krajach partnerskich. Do zadań wykonawcy będzie należało wypełnianie wytycznych wydawanych przez Komisję Europejską oraz obsługa logistyczna, w szczególności konferencji, delegowania ekspertów na warsztaty, materiałów promocyjnych itp. Wykonawca będzie również dokonywał płatności związanych z działaniami logistycznymi i kosztami ekspertów.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planowana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Listopad 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje dodatkowe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Orientacyjny maksymalny budżet zamówienia wynosi 32 500 000 EUR na 2 lata, w zależności od przyjęcia odpowiednich decyzji finansowych.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 236/2014 z dnia 11 marca 2014 r. ustanawiające wspólne zasady i procedury wdrażania unijnych instrumentów na rzecz finansowania działań zewnętrznych.</P><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 231/2014 z dnia 11 marca 2014 r. ustanawiające Instrument Pomocy Przedakcesyjnej (IPA II).</P><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 232/2014 z dnia 11 marca 2014 r. ustanawiające Europejski Instrument Sąsiedztwa.</P><P>— Rozporządzenie (WE) nr 389/2006 z dnia 27 lutego 2006 r. ustanawiające instrument wsparcia finansowego w celu stymulowania rozwoju gospodarczego tureckiej wspólnoty cypryjskiej i zmieniające rozporządzenie Rady (WE) nr 2667/2000 w sprawie Europejskiej Agencji Odbudowy.</P><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 234/2014 z dnia 11 marca 2014 r. ustanawiające Instrument Partnerstwa na rzecz Współpracy z Państwami Trzecimi.</P><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (WE) nr 233/2014 z dnia 11 marca 2014 r. ustanawiające Instrument Finansowania Współpracy na rzecz Rozwoju na lata 2014–2020.</P><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 1303/2013 z dnia 17 grudnia 2013 r. ustanawiające wspólne przepisy dotyczące Europejskiego Funduszu Rozwoju Regionalnego, Europejskiego Funduszu Społecznego, Funduszu Spójności, Europejskiego Funduszu Rolnego na rzecz Rozwoju Obszarów Wiejskich oraz Europejskiego Funduszu Morskiego i Rybackiego oraz ustanawiające przepisy ogólne dotyczące Europejskiego Funduszu Rozwoju Regionalnego, Europejskiego Funduszu Społecznego, Funduszu Spójności i Europejskiego Funduszu Morskiego i Rybackiego oraz uchylające rozporządzenie Rady (WE) nr 1083/2006; rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 1304/2013 z dnia 17 grudnia 2013 r. w sprawie Europejskiego Funduszu Społecznego i uchylające rozporządzenie Rady (WE) nr 1081/2006.</P><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 1293/2013 z dnia 11 grudnia 2013 r. w sprawie ustanowienia programu działań na rzecz środowiska i klimatu (LIFE) i uchylające rozporządzenie (WE) nr 614/2007.</P><P>— Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 2017/825 z dnia 17 maja 2017 r. w sprawie utworzenia Programu wspierania reform strukturalnych na lata 2017–2020 oraz zmiany rozporządzeń (UE) nr 1303/2013 i (UE) nr 1305/2013.</P><P>Należy mieć świadomość, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z UE brytyjscy kandydaci i oferenci będą podlegać zasadom dostępu do unijnych procedur udzielania zamówień podmiotom gospodarczym w państwach trzecich w zależności od wyniku negocjacji. W sytuacji gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać wykluczeni z postępowania o udzielenie zamówienia.</P><P>(1) Uprasza się o wskazanie wszelkich okoliczności, które mogą mieć wpływ na warunki udziału (takie jak uwarunkowania geograficzne, tematyczne lub kwestie długo- lub krótkoterminowe).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Uwagi:</P><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją odpowiedniego ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na tym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: IPA - Pomoc pri vykonávaní činností technickej pomoci a výmeny informácií (TAIEX): poskytovanie logistických služieb a finančného riadenia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Miesto: celý svet</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Predbežné oznámenie o obstarávaní služieb</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Akčný program nástroja technickej pomoci a výmeny informácií (Technical Assistance and Information Exchange – TAIEX) na roky 2018 – 2020 v rámci viacnárodného programu IPA II/akčného programu TAIEX na roky 2018 – 2020 v rámci opatrení európskeho susedstva/akčného programu pre komunitu cyperských Turkov/ročného akčného programu v rámci partnerského nástroja na spoluprácu s tretími krajinami/ročného pracovného programu DEVCO týkajúceho sa koordinácie a zvyšovania informovanosti o otázkach rozvoja/EFRR a Kohézneho fondu na použitie technickej pomoci/financovania podprogramu Životné prostredie/pracovného programu pre Program podpory štrukturálnych reforiem.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska únia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastúpená Európskou komisiou v mene a záujme užívateľov, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Odplatné.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Účelom obstarávania je podpora uplatňovania nástroja technickej pomoci a výmeny informácií (TAIEX), ktorým sa podporuje vzájomná spolupráca medzi verejnými orgánmi členských štátov EÚ s orgánmi v partnerských krajinách. Úlohou dodávateľa bude vykonávať pokyny vydané Európskou komisiou a zavádzať logistiku najmä pre konferencie, workshopy, misie expertov, propagačné materiály atď. Dodávateľ tiež bude realizovať platby súvisiace s logistickými činnosťami a nákladmi na odborníkov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plánovaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>november 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Orientačný maximálny rozpočet je 32 500 000 EUR na 2 roky, pričom podlieha prijatiu príslušných rozhodnutí o financovaní.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 236/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovujú spoločné pravidlá a postupy pre vykonávanie nástrojov Únie na financovanie vonkajšej činnosti,</P><P>— nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 231/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj predvstupovej pomoci (IPA II),</P><P>— nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 232/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj európskeho susedstva,</P><P>— nariadenie Rady (ES) č. 389/2006 z 27.2.2006, ktorým sa vytvára nástroj finančnej podpory na stimulovanie hospodárskeho rozvoja komunity cyperských Turkov, ktorým sa mení a dopĺňa nariadenie Rady (ES) č. 2667/2000 o Európskej agentúre pre obnovu,</P><P>— nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 234/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj partnerstva pre spoluprácu s tretími krajinami,</P><P>— nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 233/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj financovania rozvojovej spolupráce na obdobie rokov 2014 – 2020,</P><P>— nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 1303/2013 zo 17.12.2013, ktorým sa stanovujú spoločné ustanovenia o Európskom fonde regionálneho rozvoja, Európskom sociálnom fonde, Kohéznom fonde, Európskom poľnohospodárskom fonde pre rozvoj vidieka a Európskom námornom a rybárskom fonde a ktorým sa stanovujú všeobecné ustanovenia o Európskom fonde regionálneho rozvoja, Európskom sociálnom fonde, Kohéznom fonde a Európskom námornom a rybárskom fonde, a ktorým sa zrušuje nariadenie Rady (ES) č. 1083/2006; nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 1304/2013 zo 17.12.2013 o Európskom sociálnom fonde a o zrušení nariadenia Rady (ES) č. 1081/2006,</P><P>— nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 1293/2013 z 11.12.2013 o zriadení programu pre životné prostredie a ochranu klímy (LIFE) a o zrušení nariadenia (ES) č. 614/2007,</P><P>— nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 2017/825 zo 17.5.2017 o zriadení programu podpory štrukturálnych reforiem na obdobie rokov 2017 až 2020, ktorým sa menia a dopĺňajú nariadenia (EÚ) č. 1303/2013 a (EÚ) č. 1305/2013.</P><P>Pripomíname, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa na záujemcov alebo uchádzačov zo Spojeného kráľovstva v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní budú uplatňovať pravidlá prístupu k postupom obstarávania EÚ zo strany hospodárskych subjektov so sídlom v tretích krajinách. V prípade, že takýto prístup sa nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojeného kráľovstva by mohli byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P><P>(1) Uveďte akékoľvek špecifiká, ktoré by mohli mať vplyv na pravidlá účasti (napríklad geografické alebo tematické, dlhodobé alebo krátkodobé).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Poznámky:</P><P>Medzi uverejnením predbežného oznámenia a uverejnením príslušného oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť minimálne 30 kalendárnych dní.</P><P>V tomto období sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: IPA - Pomoč pri izvajanju dejavnosti tehnične pomoči in izmenjave informacij (TAIEX): Zagotavljanje logističnih storitev in finančnega upravljanja</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija: globalno</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Predhodno informativno obvestilo o naročilu storitev</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka objave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Akcijski program izmenjave informacij in tehnične pomoči (TAIEX) za obdobje 2018–2020 v okviru večdržavnih sredstev iz IPA II/akcijski program TAIEX za obdobje 2018–2020 v okviru ukrepov na območju celotnega evropskega sosedstva/akcijski program za turško skupnost na Cipru/letni akcijski program instrumenta partnerstva za sodelovanje s tretjimi državami/letni delovni program DEVCO za usklajevanje in spodbujanje ozaveščenosti o razvojnih vprašanjih/ESRR in Kohezijski sklad za uporabo tehnične pomoči/financiranje podprograma Life za okolje/delovni program za program podpore strukturnih reform.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija, v imenu in za račun držav upravičenk, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselj</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Na podlagi plačila</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Namen naročila je podpreti izvajanje instrumenta tehnične pomoči in izmenjave informacij (TAIEX), ki podpira medsebojno sodelovanje med javnimi organi držav članic EU in organi v partnerskih državah. Vloga izvajalca bo izvrševanje navodil, ki jih izda Evropska komisija, in vzpostavitev logistike, zlasti za konference, delavnice in strokovne misije, zagotovitev promocijskega gradiva itd. Izvajalec bo opravil tudi plačila v zvezi z logističnimi dejavnostmi in honorarji strokovnjakov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>November 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Okvirni najvišji proračun znaša 32 500 000 EUR za obdobje 2 let, pod pogojem, da bodo sprejeti ustrezni finančni sklepi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Uredba (EU) št. 236/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o določitvi skupnih pravil in postopkov za izvajanje instrumentov Unije za financiranje zunanjega delovanja,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) št. 231/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi instrumenta za predpristopno pomoč (IPA II),</P><P>— Uredba (EU) št. 232/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi evropskega instrumenta sosedstva,</P><P>— Uredba Sveta (ES) št. 389/2006 z dne 27.2.2006 o oblikovanju instrumenta finančne podpore za spodbujanje gospodarskega razvoja turške skupnosti na Cipru in o spremembah Uredbe Sveta (ES) št. 2667/2000 o Evropski agenciji za obnovo,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) št. 234/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi instrumenta partnerstva za sodelovanje s tretjimi državami,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) št. 233/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi instrumenta za financiranje razvojnega sodelovanja za obdobje 2014–2020,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) št. 1303/2013 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 17.12.2013 o skupnih določbah o Evropskem skladu za regionalni razvoj, Evropskem socialnem skladu, Kohezijskem skladu, Evropskem kmetijskem skladu za razvoj podeželja in Evropskem skladu za pomorstvo in ribištvo, o splošnih določbah o Evropskem skladu za regionalni razvoj, Evropskem socialnem skladu, Kohezijskem skladu in Evropskem skladu za pomorstvo in ribištvo ter o razveljavitvi Uredbe Sveta (ES) št. 1083/2006; Uredba (EU) št. 1304/2013 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 17.12.2013 o Evropskem socialnem skladu in razveljavitvi Uredbe Sveta (ES) št. 1081/2006,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) št. 1293/2013 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.12.2013 o vzpostavitvi programa za okolje in podnebne ukrepe (LIFE) in razveljavitvi Uredbe (ES) št. 614/2007,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) 2017/825 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 17.5.2017 o vzpostavitvi programa za podporo strukturnim reformam za obdobje 2017–2020 ter o spremembi uredb (EU) št. 1303/2013 in (EU) št. 1305/2013.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva veljala pravila o dostopu do razpisnih postopkov EU, ki veljajo za gospodarske subjekte s sedežem v tretjih državah, odvisno od izida pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne bodo zagotavljale tovrstnega dostopa, so lahko kandidati ali ponudniki iz Združenega kraljestva izločeni iz razpisnega postopka.</P><P>(1) Navedite kakršno koli posebnost, ki bi lahko vplivala na pravila o sodelovanju (na primer geografsko ali tematsko ali dolgo-/kratkoročno).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Opombe:</P><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo ustreznega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči vsaj 30 koledarskih dni.</P><P>V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: IPA - Cabhair chun gníomhaíochtaí um chúnamh teicniúil agus faisnéise a chur chun feidhme (TAIEX): Soláthar seirbhísí lóistíochta agus bainistíochta airgeadais</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Láthair: Ar fud an domhain</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Fógra réamhaisnéise seirbhíse</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teideal an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Clár gníomhaíochta 2018–2020 um Chúnamh Teicniúil agus um Malartú Faisnéise (TAIEX) faoi chlúdach iltíre IPA II/faoi chlár gníomhaíochta TAIEX 2018–2020 faoi na bearta Eorpacha uile-Chomharsanachta/faoin gclár gníomhaíochta do phobal Turcach na Cipire/do chlár gníomhaíochta bliantúil na hIonstraime Comhpháirtíochta maidir le comhar le tríú tíortha/clár oibre bliantúil DEVCO a bhaineann le comhar agus cur chun cinn feasachta ar shaincheisteanna forbartha/CFRE agus an Ciste Comhtháthaithe chun cúnamh teicniúil a úsáid/fochlár LIFE a mhaoiniú don chomhshaol/clár oibre don chlár tacaíochta um athchóiriú struchtúrach.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás Conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An tAontas Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach, thar ceann agus chun cuntais na dtairbhithe, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bunaithe ar tháille.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is é cuspóir an chonartha tacú le cur chun feidhme na hionstraime um Malartú Cúnaimh Theicniúil agus Faisnéise (TAIEX) a thacaíonn le comhar piaraí le piaraí i measc údaráis phoiblí Bhallstáit AE le húdaráis i dtíortha comhpháirtíochta. Is é ról an chonraitheora treoracha arna n-eisiúint ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach a chur i bhfeidhm agus lóistíocht a chur i bhfeidhm go háirithe do chomhdhálacha, do shainmhisin cheardlainne, d'ábhair bolscaireachta, etc. Déanfaidh an conraitheoir íocaíochtaí freisin a bhaineann le gníomhaíochtaí lóistíochta agus táillí saineolaithe.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An sprioc atá beartaithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Samhain 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is é 32 500 000 EUR an buiséad uasta táscach thar 2 bhliain, faoi réir ghlacadh na gcinntí maoinithe faoi seach.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 236/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena leagtar síos rialacha agus nósanna imeachta comhchoiteanna le haghaidh cur chun feidhme ionstraimí an Aontais chun an ghníomhaíocht sheachtrach a mhaoiniú,</P><P>— Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 231/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena mbunaítear Ionstraim um Chúnamh Réamhaontachais (IPA II),</P><P>— Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 232/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena mbunaítear Ionstraim Eorpach um Chomharsanacht,</P><P>— Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 389/2006 ón gComhairle an 27.2.2006 lena mbunaítear ionstraim um thacaíocht airgeadais chun forbairt eacnamaíoch phobal Turcach na Cipire a spreagadh agus lena leasaítear Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 2667/2000 ón gComhairle maidir leis an nGníomhaireacht Eorpach um Athchóiriú,</P><P>— Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 234/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014, lena mbunaítear Ionstraim Chomhpháirtíochta le haghaidh comhoibriú le tríú tíortha,</P><P>— Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 233/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014, lena mbunaítear ionstraim mhaoinithe le haghaidh comhar um fhorbairt don tréimhse 2014-2020,</P><P>— Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 1303/2013 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 17.12.2013 lena leagtar síos forálacha comhchoiteanna maidir le Ciste Forbraíochta Réigiúnaí na hEorpa, Ciste Sóisialta na hEorpa, an Ciste Comhtháthaithe, an Ciste Eorpach Talmhaíochta um Fhorbairt Tuaithe agus an Ciste Eorpach Muirí agus Iascaigh agus lena leagtar síos forálacha ginearálta maidir le Ciste Forbraíochta Réigiúnaí na hEorpa, Ciste Sóisialta na hEorpa, an Ciste Comhtháthaithe agus an Ciste Eorpach Muirí agus Iascaigh agus lena n-aisghairtear Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 1083/2006 ón gComhairle; Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 1304/2013 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 17.12.2013 maidir le Ciste Sóisialta na hEorpa agus lena n-aisghairtear Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 1081/2006 ón gComhairle,</P><P>— Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 1293/2013 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.12.2013 maidir le Clár faoin gComhshaol agus faoi Ghníomhaíocht i leith na hAeráide (LIFE) a bhunú agus lena n-aisghairtear Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 614/2007,</P><P>— Rialachán (AE) 2017/825 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 17.5.2017 maidir leis an gclár tacaíochta um athchóiriú struchtúrach a bhunú don tréimhse 2017 go 2020 agus lena leasaítear Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 1303/2013 agus Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 1305/2013.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta soláthair AE ag oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha i bhfeidhm ar iarrthóirí nó ar thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe tar éis di tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na hidirbheartaíochta. Sa chás nach gcuirfear a leithéid de rochtain ar fáil trí fhorálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm an tráth a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí iarrthóir nó tairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe a dhiúltú ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P><P>(1) Luaigh aon tsainiúlacht a d’fhéadfadh tionchar a bheith aige ar rialacha na rannpháirtíochta (amhail sainiúlacht thíreolaíoch nó théamach, nó sainiúlacht fhadtéarmach/ghearrthéarmach).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nótaí:</P><P>Ní mór tréimhse 30 lá féilire ar a laghad a bheith idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise seo agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh.</P><P>Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: ИПП - Съдействие при осъществяването на дейности по техническа помощ и обмен на информация (TAIEX): Предоставяне на логистични услуги и финансови управление</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Местоположение: Глобално</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Обявление за предварителна информация за услуги</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Заглавие на програма</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Програма за действие „Техническа помощ и обмен на информация“ (TAIEX) за 2018–2020 по многонационалния пакет средства на ИПП II/програма за действие TAIEX за 2018–2020 по мерките в целия регион на европейското съседство/програма за действие за кипърската турска общност/Годишна програма за действие от инструмент за партньорство за сътрудничество с трети държави/Годишна работна програма на DEVCO, свързана с координирането и насърчаването на осведоменост по въпроси на развитието/ ЕФРР и Кохезионен фонд за ползване на техническа подкрепа/Финансиране на подпрограма Life за околната среда/Работна програма за Програмата за подкрепа на структурната реформа.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейски съюз</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, представляван от Европейската комисия, от името и за сметка на бенефициерите, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Брюксел</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Комисионна поръчка.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Целта на поръчката е да се подпомогне реализирането на инструмента за техническа помощ и обмен на информация (TAIEX), който подкрепя партньорското сътрудничество на обществените органи на държавите — членки на ЕС с органите в партньорските държави. Ролята на изпълнителя ще бъде да се изпълнят инструкциите, издадени от Европейската комисия и да се въведе логистика, по-конкретно за конференции, семинари, мисии на експерти, промоционални материали, т.н. Изпълнителят ще извършва и плащания, свързани с логистичните дейности и таксите за експерти.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Очакван срок за публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ноември 2019 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Приблизителният максимален бюджет е 32 500 000 EUR за 2 години, в зависимост от приемането на съответните финансови решения.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Регламент (ЕС) № 236/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за определяне на общи правила и процедури за изпълнението на инструментите на Съюза за финансиране на външната дейност;</P><P>— Регламент (ЕС) № 231/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на Инструмент за предприсъединителна помощ (ИПП II),</P><P>— Регламент (ЕС) № 232/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на Европейски инструмент за съседство,</P><P>— Регламент (ЕО) № 389/2006 на Съвета от 27.2.2006 г. за създаване на инструмент за финансова помощ за насърчаване на икономическото развитие на кипърската турска общност и изменен Регламент (ЕО) № 2667/2000 на Съвета относно Европейската агенция за възстановяване,</P><P>— Регламент (ЕС) № 234/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на Инструмент за партньорство за сътрудничество с трети държави,</P><P>— Регламент (ЕС) № 233/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на финансов инструмент за сътрудничество за развитие за периода 2014—2020 г.,</P><P>— Регламент (ЕС) № 1303/2013 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 17.12.2013 г. за определяне на общоприложими разпоредби за Европейския фонд за регионално развитие, Европейския социален фонд, Кохезионния фонд, Европейския земеделски фонд за развитие на селските райони и Европейския фонд за морско дело и рибарство и за определяне на общи разпоредби за Европейския фонд за регионално развитие, Европейския социален фонд, Кохезионния фонд и Европейския фонд за морско дело и рибарство, и за отмяна на Регламент (ЕО) № 1083/2006 на Съвета; Регламент (ЕС) № 1304/2013 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 17.12.2013 г. относно Европейския социален фонд и за отмяна на Регламент (ЕО) № 1081/2006 на Съвета,</P><P>— Регламент (ЕС) № 1293/2013 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.12.2013 г. за създаване на Програма за околната среда и действията по климата (LIFE) и за отмяна на Регламент (ЕО) № 614/2007,</P><P>— Регламент (ЕС) 2017/825 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 17.5.2017 г. за създаването на Програмата за подкрепа на структурните реформи за периода 2017—2020 г. и за изменение на регламенти (ЕС) № 1303/2013 и (ЕС) № 1305/2013.</P><P>Моля, имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС, правилата за достъп до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС за икономически оператори, установени в трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство могат да бъдат отхвърлени от процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P><P>(1) Моля, посочете всяка особеност, която може да окаже въздействие върху правилата за участие (напр. географска или тематична, или кратък/дълъг срок).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Забележки:</P><P>Трябва да има минимален период от 30 календарни дни между публикуването на настоящото обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на съответното обявление за поръчка.</P><P>На този етап не трябва да се изпращат никакви молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IPA - Asistență pentru punerea în aplicare a activităților de asistență tehnică și schimb de informații (TAIEX): Prestarea de servicii logistice și management financiar</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locație: la nivel global</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anunț de intenție privind un contract de achiziții publice de servicii</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programul de acțiune 2018-2020 pentru asistență tehnică și schimb de informații (TAIEX) în baza pachetului multinațional al IPA II/programul de acțiune TAIEX 2018-2020 în baza măsurilor Instrumentului european de vecinătate/programul de acțiune pentru comunitatea cipriotă turcă/programul anual de acțiune pentru cooperarea cu țările terțe/ Programul anual de lucru al DEVCO privind coordonarea și promovarea conștientizării pe probleme de dezvoltare / FEDR și Fondul de coeziune pentru utilizarea asistenței tehnice / Finanțarea subprogramului „Viața pentru mediu” / Programul de lucru pentru Programul de sprijin al reformei structurale.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Uniunea Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană, în numele și în favoarea beneficiarilor, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bazat pe onorarii.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Scopul contractului este de a sprijini punerea în aplicare a instrumentului de asistență tehnică și schimb de informații (TAIEX) care sprijină cooperarea de la egal la egal între autoritățile publice ale statelor membre ale UE cu autoritățile din țările partenere. Rolul contractantului va fi să execute instrucțiuni emise de Comisia Europeană și să pună la punct logistica în special pentru conferințe, misiuni de experți în ateliere, materiale de promovare etc. Contractantul va efectua, de asemenea, plăți legate de activități logistice și taxe de expertiză.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută pentru publicarea anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Noiembrie 2019</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bugetul maxim indicativ este de 32 500 000 EUR pe parcursul a 2 ani, sub rezerva adoptării deciziilor de finanțare respective.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Baza juridică (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Regulamentul (UE) nr. 236/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de stabilire a normelor și procedurilor comune pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentelor Uniunii pentru finanțarea acțiunii externe,</P><P>— Regulamentul (UE) nr. 231/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument de asistență pentru preaderare (IPA II),</P><P>— Regulamentul (UE) nr. 232/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument european de vecinătate,</P><P>— Regulamentul (CE) nr. 389/2006 al Consiliului din 27.2.2006 privind crearea unui instrument de sprijin financiar în scopul de a încuraja dezvoltarea economică a comunității cipriote turce și de modificare a Regulamentului (CE) nr. 2667/2000 al Consiliului privind Agenția Europeană pentru Reconstrucție,</P><P>— Regulamentul (UE) nr. 234/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument de parteneriat pentru cooperarea cu țările terțe,</P><P>— Regulamentul (UE) nr. 233/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument de finanțare a cooperării pentru dezvoltare în perioada 2014-2020,</P><P>— Regulamentul (UE) nr. 1303/2013 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 17.12.2013 de stabilire a unor dispoziții comune privind Fondul european de dezvoltare regională, Fondul social european, Fondul de coeziune, Fondul european agricol pentru dezvoltare rurală și Fondul european pentru pescuit și afaceri maritime, precum și de stabilire a unor dispoziții generale privind Fondul european de dezvoltare regională, Fondul social european, Fondul de coeziune și Fondul european pentru pescuit și afaceri maritime și de abrogare a Regulamentului (CE) nr. 1083/2006 al Consiliului; Regulamentul (UE) nr. 1304/2013 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 17.12.2013 privind Fondul social european și de abrogare a Regulamentului (CE) nr. 1081/2006 al Consiliului,</P><P>— Regulamentul (UE) nr. 1293/2013 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.12.2013 privind instituirea unui program pentru mediu și politici climatice (LIFE) și de abrogare a Regulamentului (CE) nr. 614/2007,</P><P>— Regulamentul (UE) 2017/825 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 17.5.2017 privind instituirea programului de sprijin al reformei structurale pentru perioada 2017-2020 și de modificare a Regulamentelor (UE) nr. 1303/2013 și (UE) nr. 1305 / 2013.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Marii Britanii din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții ale UE se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Regatul Unit în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care accesul nu este prevăzut de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Regatul Unit ar putea fi respinși de la procedura de achiziții publice.</P><P>(1) Vă rugăm să precizați orice specificitate care ar putea avea un impact asupra regulilor de participare (cum ar fi de ordin geografic sau tematic sau pe termen lung / scurt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Observații:</P><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de minimum 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător.</P><P>În această etapă nu se acceptă candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S04.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IPA - Pomoć aktivnostima provedbe Instrumenta tehničke pomoći i razmjene informacija (TAIEX): Pružanje usluga logistike i financijskog upravljanja</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija: Globalno</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Prethodna informacijska obavijest o uslugama</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/140471/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Akcijski program Tehničke pomoći i razmjene informacija (TAIEX) za 2018.–2020. u okviru omotnice IPA-e II za više država/akcijskog programa TAIEX-a za 2018.–2020. u okviru mjera diljem europskog susjedstva/akcijskog programa za tursku zajednicu/godišnjeg akcijskog programa u okviru Instrumenta partnerstva za suradnju s trećim zemljama/DEVCO Godišnji radni program koji se odnosi na koordinaciju i promidžbu svijesti o razvojnim pitanjima/ERDF i Kohezijskog fonda za korištenje tehničke pomoći/Financiranje Life potprograma za životnu sredinu/Radni program za Program potpore strukturnim reformama.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>22.020401/22.040102/22.040202/13.070100/19.050100/21.080200/13.036501/13.046101/07.020300/13.080200.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, koju predstavlja Europska komisija, u ime i za račun korisnika, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Temeljen na naknadama.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Svrha je ugovora podržati provedbu instrumenta tehničke pomoći i razmjene informacija (TAIEX) kojim se podržava uzajamna suradnja između javnih tijela država članica EU-a s vlastima u partnerskim zemljama. Uloga ugovaratelja bit će izvršavanje uputa koje je izdala Europska komisija i uspostavljanje logistike posebice za konferencije, misije stručnjaka za radionice, promotivne materijale itd. Ugovaratelj će također vršiti plaćanja u vezi s logističkim aktivnostima i naknadama stručnjaka.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>32 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>studeni 2019.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Indikativni najveći proračun je 32 500 000 EUR tokom 2 godine, koji podliježe donošenju odgovarajućih odluka o financiranju.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna osnova(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 236/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o utvrđivanju zajedničkih pravila i postupaka za provedbu instrumenata Unije za financiranje vanjskog djelovanja,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 231/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o uspostavi Instrumenta pretpristupne pomoći (IPA II),</P><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 232/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o uspostavi Europskog instrumenta za susjedstvo,</P><P>— Uredba Vijeća (EZ) br. 389/2006 od 27.2.2006. o uspostavi instrumenta financijske potpore za poticanje gospodarskog razvoja turske zajednice na Cipru i o izmjeni Uredbe Vijeća (EZ) br. 2667/2000 o Europskoj agenciji za obnovu,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 234/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o uspostavi Instrumenta za partnerstvo za suradnju s trećim zemljama,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 233/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o uspostavi Instrumenta financiranja za razvojnu suradnju za razdoblje 2014.-2020.,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 1303/2013 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 17.12.2013. o utvrđivanju zajedničkih odredbi o Europskom fondu za regionalni razvoj, Europskom socijalnom fondu, Kohezijskom fondu, Europskom poljoprivrednom fondu za ruralni razvoj i Europskom fondu za pomorstvo i ribarstvo i o utvrđivanju općih odredbi o Europskom fondu za regionalni razvoj, Europskom socijalnom fondu, Kohezijskom fondu i Europskom fondu za pomorstvo i ribarstvo te o stavljanju izvan snage Uredbe Vijeća (EZ) br. 1083/2006; Uredba (EU) br. 1304/2013 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 17.12.2013. o Europskom socijalnom fondu i stavljanju izvan snage Uredbe Vijeća (EZ) br. 1081/2006.,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 1293/2013 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.12.2013. o uspostavi Programa za okoliš i klimatske aktivnosti (LIFE) i stavljanju izvan snage Uredbe (EZ) br. 614/2007,</P><P>— Uredba (EU) br. 2017/825 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 17.5.2017. o uspostavi programa potpore strukturnim reformama za razdoblje od 2017. do 2020. i o izmjeni Uredbi (EU) br. 1303/2013 i (EU) br. 1305/2013.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon povlačenja Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine primjenjivati pravila pristupa postupcima nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte s poslovnim nastanom u trećim zemljama, ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen pravnim odredbama koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P><P>(1) Navedite sve pojedinosti koje bi mogle utjecati na pravila sudjelovanja (poput geografskih ili tematskih ili dugoročnih/kratkoročnih).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Napomene:</P><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana.</P><P>U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ni zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>