<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.9/publication" xmlns:n2016="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="http://publications.europa.eu/resource/schema/ted/R2.0.9/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" VERSION="R2.0.9.S03.E01" DOC_ID="425055-2019" EDITION="2019174"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>19-434070-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20191215</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>174</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20190910</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2019/S 174-425055</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:425055-2019:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>https://tavistockandportman.nhs.uk/</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72300000">Data services</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UK">UNITED KINGDOM</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKI31">Camden and City of London</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS><n2016:TENDERER_NUTS CODE="UK">UNITED KINGDOM</n2016:TENDERER_NUTS><VALUES><VALUE TYPE="PROCUREMENT_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">815015.00</VALUE></VALUES></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20190906</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="V">Voluntary ex ante transparency notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="T">Negotiated without a prior call for competition</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>01C15</HEADING><INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Лондон</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Услуги по предаване и обработка на данни</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londýn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Datové služby</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Datatjenester</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Datendienste</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Λονδίνο</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Υπηρεσίες δεδομένων</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Data services</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servicios relacionados con datos</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Andmeteenused</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lontoo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Datapalvelut</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Services de commutation de données</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londain</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Data services</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Podatkovne usluge</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Adatkezelési szolgáltatások</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servizi di elaborazione dati</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londonas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Duomenų paslaugos</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londona</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Datu pakalpojumi</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servizzi tad-data</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londen</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Uitwerken van gegevens</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londyn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Usługi w zakresie danych</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Serviços relacionados com dados</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Servicii de înlocuire de date</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Londýn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Dátové služby</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Podatkovne storitve</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT><P>Datatjänster</P></TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Tavistock and Portman NHS Foundation Trust</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><F15_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F15" LG="EN"><LEGAL_BASIS VALUE="32014L0024"/><CONTRACTING_BODY><ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY><OFFICIALNAME>Tavistock and Portman NHS Foundation Trust</OFFICIALNAME><ADDRESS>120 Belsize Lane</ADDRESS><TOWN>London</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>NW3 5BA</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><E_MAIL>procurement@tavi-port.nhs.uk</E_MAIL><n2016:NUTS CODE="UKI31"/><URL_GENERAL>https://tavistockandportman.nhs.uk/</URL_GENERAL></ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY><CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/><CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/></CONTRACTING_BODY><OBJECT_CONTRACT><TITLE><P>Family Nurse Partnership Data System</P></TITLE><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="72300000"/></CPV_MAIN><TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/><SHORT_DESCR><P>Contract for the provision of data hosting services to fulfil the national requirements for the family nurse partnership (FNP) programme in England. The provider will host and maintain a data system to collate and analyse programme data for use by the FNP National Unit as part of its obligatory requirements to deliver the FNP Programme.</P><P>The provider will work with the FNP National Unit in the migration of data into its existing bespoke FNP Scotland application.</P></SHORT_DESCR><VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">815015.00</VAL_TOTAL><NO_LOT_DIVISION/><OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1"><n2016:NUTS CODE="UK"/><SHORT_DESCR><P>The FNP National Unit has sought the provision of a new data hosting service for the FNP data system for England to include hosting of the FNP England application; Bulk user onboarding; technical support, Power BI Embedded and ongoing inclusive development time, to fulfil a contract for up to 5 (five) years.</P><P>The current data system is provided and hosted by NHS Digital on a legacy platform which requires a high level of resource and costs to maintain. NHS Digital has notified the FNP National Unit that as of 31.3.2020 they will decommission the platform which hosts the current FNP data system. The FNP National Unit has since initiated an urgent procurement for a new FNP data system to mitigate the risk of disruption and termination of the FNP programme in England. Further, the FNP National Unit is at risk of breaching the licence agreement with the University of Colarado if a new FNP data system is not procured and implemented by end March 2020.</P><P>Initial market research by the FNP National Unit resulted in identifying NHS Education Scotland as the most technically suitable delivery partner as they have developed and currently host a bespoke data system for the FNP programme in Scotland. NHS Education Scotland has a deep and detailed knowledge of the FNP programme, its delivery and workforce needs and proven expertise in providing an FNP specific data system.</P><P>Data migration is required from the current FNP Information System to existing ‘target’ data structures already in place in the NHS Education Scotland system, which allows the Trust to start with data migration activities immediately. A separate procurement is being followed for the data migration, via established UK Government frameworks.</P></SHORT_DESCR><DIRECTIVE_2014_24_EU><AC><AC_QUALITY><AC_CRITERION>Technical</AC_CRITERION><AC_WEIGHTING>80</AC_WEIGHTING></AC_QUALITY><AC_PRICE><AC_WEIGHTING>20</AC_WEIGHTING></AC_PRICE></AC></DIRECTIVE_2014_24_EU><NO_OPTIONS/><NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/></OBJECT_DESCR></OBJECT_CONTRACT><PROCEDURE><DIRECTIVE_2014_24_EU><PT_NEGOTIATED_WITHOUT_PUBLICATION><D_ACCORDANCE_ARTICLE><D_TECHNICAL/><D_EXTREME_URGENCY/></D_ACCORDANCE_ARTICLE><D_JUSTIFICATION><P>The Tavistock and Portman NHS Foundation Trust (The Trust) considers that the data hosting services required can only be provided by NHS Education Scotland (NHSES) because competition is absent for technical reasons. Alternatively, the award of the contract is extremely urgent. The Trust therefore relies on Regulations 32(2)(b)(ii) and/or 32(2)(c) of the Public Contracts Regulations 2015.</P><P>Competition is absent for technical reasons as a result of several factors:</P><P>(1) System similarities. NHSES currently provides data hosting services for the FNP programme in Scotland. Complex reporting workflows and datasets configured to support the Scottish FNP programme are already in place and will be applied to the data to support safe clinical roll out of the FNP programme in England from the ‘go live’ date. Minimal development or configuration of the solution is required meaning that the data hosting service can be switched to NHSES without disruption. Due to the importance of the service, it is a fundamental requirement that the ‘go live’ date is achieved without disruption and with minimal risk;</P><P>2) Data migration and timing. The Trust current supplier (NHS Digital) confirmed in March 2019 that it would decommission the platform which underpinned the existing system, in March 2020. All data hosted in the existing application must have migrated to the new solution before 1.4.2020 (an absolute requirement). NHSES’s solution is already in place. As a result, target data structures already exist meaning data migration can begin immediately upon signature of the contract. Due to the amount to time required for data migration (6 months) only NHSES can meet the requirements in this respect. The Trust does not consider that any other solution can be designed, configured and mobilised in the time available;</P><P>3) Expertise. NHSES knowledge of the programme, understanding of its delivery and workforce needs and ability to provide support and development cannot be matched by other suppliers.</P><P>Alternatively, the award is justified as a result of extreme urgency because it is estimated that data migration may take 6 months. It is a fundamental requirement that the new solution be finalised as soon as possible so that mapping for data migration can begin. Given the similarities between The Trust current system and NHSES’s solution data mapping can begin immediately upon signature of the contract allowing sufficient time for migration to complete before the current system is decommissioned in March 2020. One of the stipulations of the FNP’s programme licence with Colorado University is that the FNP National Unit are able to analyse programme data, therefore failure to complete data migration in time would breach this condition putting the whole FNP programme at risk of cancellation.</P><P>The Trust has considered the market and concluded that no provider other than NHSES can meet the requirements within the timescale required. As such The Trust considers that use of the negotiated procedure without prior publication of a call for competition in the OJEU is justified because competition is absent for technical reasons and/or for reasons of extreme urgency.</P></D_JUSTIFICATION></PT_NEGOTIATED_WITHOUT_PUBLICATION></DIRECTIVE_2014_24_EU><CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/></PROCEDURE><AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1"><TITLE><P>Family Nurse Partnership Data System</P></TITLE><AWARDED_CONTRACT><DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2019-08-01</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT><CONTRACTORS><NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/><CONTRACTOR><ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR><OFFICIALNAME>NHS Education for Scotland</OFFICIALNAME><ADDRESS>Westport 102, West Port</ADDRESS><TOWN>Edinburgh</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>EH3 9DN</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><n2016:NUTS CODE="UK"/></ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR><NO_SME/></CONTRACTOR></CONTRACTORS><VALUES><VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">815015.00</VAL_TOTAL></VALUES></AWARDED_CONTRACT></AWARD_CONTRACT><COMPLEMENTARY_INFO><INFO_ADD><P>The FNP programme is currently hosted by the Tavistock and Portman NHS Foundation Trust. This programme and the staff working for the national unit will be transitioning over to Public Health England (PHE) on 1.4.2020. Therefore, the contract will need to be novated to PHE on 1.4.2020.</P><P>The Tavistock and Portman NHS Foundation Trust will enter into a contract with NHS Education Scotland on the 17.9.2019 for the provision of services outlined in this notice.</P></INFO_ADD><ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY><OFFICIALNAME>Royal Courts of Justice</OFFICIALNAME><ADDRESS>Strand</ADDRESS><TOWN>London</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>WC2A 2LL</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/></ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY><REVIEW_PROCEDURE><P>In accordance with Part 3, Chapter 6 of the Public Contracts Regulations 2015.</P></REVIEW_PROCEDURE><ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO><OFFICIALNAME>The Tavistock and Portman NHS Foundation Trust</OFFICIALNAME><ADDRESS>120 Belsize Lane</ADDRESS><TOWN>London</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>NW3 5BA</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/></ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO><DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2019-09-06</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFO></F15_2014></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>